Barney is crazy if he thinks
this is gonna work.
I think it's
gonna work.
I hope it doesn't work.
Shh. Here he comes.
You there, what's your name?
Excuse me?
Your name, woman,
what's your name?!
Cindy.
I knew it.
You're the Cindy,
the one who can change
everything,
or spell our inevitable doom.
Now listen to me, Cindy.
I am Barney Stinson,
and I am on an urgent mission
from the future.
The future?
The future, and I can
prove it to you.
In exactly four seconds,
the woman at that booth
is going to slap that man.
(clears throat)
Ow! What the hell?
Wow.
In a few minutes,
the young me from your time
is going to come
through that door.
Now, Cindy,
I know this sounds insane,
but in order to save the planet,
you need to sleep with him
tonight.
What? I...
Sleep with Barney Stinson
tonight,
in whatever way he wants it,
or he won't be able to find
the solution to global warming
that saves the human race.
What are you talking about?
I have no time to explain.
I have to get back
to the reality accelerator
before the vortex closes.
Only you can save us, Cindy.
I must away!
Okay, guys, the movers
are coming in 14 hours.
We gotta get back upstairs
and finish packing.
You guys still
aren't finished packing?
How is this taking so long?
Hey, all the great memories
of our 20s
took place in that apartment.
It's not like throwing
stuff in a box.
You start to reminisce.
Not me. The key?
Throw stuff out and never
look back.
I'm moving to Japan.
It took me a half hour to pack.
A half hour?
Well, it would have taken
me 20 minutes,
but a friend called me in tears.
Moving is really
emotional, okay?
It is.
I mean, everything is changing.
I'm gonna be living
in New Jersey with Stella,
you guys will be in
your new place.
You're starting a new job
in Tokyo.
It's the end of an era.
I think we should have a toast,
but not our usual crap.
Hey, uh, Wendy,
your most expensive
bottle of scotch.
That's 50-year-old
Glen McKenna, and it's $2,500.
Excellent. A bottle of that
with beer chasers,
and what do you think,
cancel the scotch?
ALL:
Yeah.
Vodka rocks.
It's not gonna work.
Oh, my God, you're...
Oh, my God!
Can I buy you a drink?
I suppose I have time
for one drink
and 45 minutes to an hour
of some other activity,
but after that,
I have to get back
to a top-secret research project
I'm working on.
Global warming?
My God, how did you know that?
Sync By GeR - http://gerdiffuse.free.fr
Hey, look at this.
A photo from the first day
we moved into this place.
BOTH:
Aw...
So many great memories.
See? That is exactly the type
of crap you should be trashing.
So you don't keep
any photos?
No, they're like love letters
or yearbooks or someone's ashes.
They just take up space.
Besides, Stella's not gonna
let you keep half of this junk.
Why wouldn't she?
(both chuckle)
Oh, Ted, oh, sweetie.
Okay, here's the thing
that guys only learn
after they move in
with a woman.
All of your stuff is stupid.
Like what?
Um, like anything you bought
at a Renaissance Faire.
Hey, hey, there's not enough
mead in the world
to make me get rid
of my flail.
Oh, hey, uh, Ted,
since we're clearly not getting
our security deposit back,
I thought maybe you could
reimburse me for my half.
Wait a second--
why should I
have to pay more than you?
Because you treated this
apartment the way John Bonham
treated his central nervous
system.
That's not true.
Exhibit A.
Hey.
What's that?
A 1986 World Book
encyclopaedia.
It's exactly the one
I grew up with.
Encyclopaedia?
Oh, you think it should
be pronounced encyclo-pee-dia.
It's a common mistake.
But if you look at that squished
together "ae" symbol
in this here encyclopaedia,
you'll learn that
it's a ligature derived
from the Anglo-Saxon
rune ash...
You know, you're gonna have
to paedia for that.
But you never did.
And then there's Exhibit B.
Good morrow, fair gentles.
Look what I won
at the Renaissance Faire.
Ooh!
And you're also responsible
for any damage Robin did
when she was your girlfriend.
Whoa. What damage did I cause?
Do you remember that night
when you drank
the 12'er of Molson
and you got all super Canadian?
(Canadian accent):
Stanley Cup, game six, eh?
The Rangers are
about to be sorry they ever
played shinny with the Canucks.
Hey, hey, Robin.
Yeah?
I'll give you 20 bucks if you
can shoot it through
this front door.
Oh, you're nuttier than
a Tim Horton's maple log.
Timmy Ho!
That's it, Robin.
Give me the stick.
I'll give you summer teeth.
Some are here, some are there.
Robin, give me the stick,
Take off, hoser.
GUYS:
Whoa!
That's it!
Hey, hey!
Get her, boys, get her!
Scrap?! I'll scrap!
Guys, come on!
For America.
All right, break it,
break it up!
Ted, no!
You never break up a girl fight!
Never! (groans)
Entirely Barney's fault.
As, by the way, is the big
scorch mark over the fireplace.
NARRATOR:
Kids, to understand
the story of the scorch mark,
I first need to tell you
the story of the intervention
for our friend Stewart.
What's going on?
Stewart, this is
an intervention.
The alcohol changes
you, Stewart.
It makes you a
different person.
And I'm in love with
the man that I married.
Thank you.
(voice breaking):
This is just the push I need.
I love you guys.
Hey, hey!
There's the birthday boy.
Time to let the party monster
out of its cage, Stewie!
No!
Come on, buddy.
People don't want to see
Bruce Banner, dude.
They want to see the Hulk.
Hulk, Hulk, Hulk... What?
Oh...
(chuckles)
That's what I get for skimming
the E-vite.
TED:
Later that day, we celebrated
our first successful
intervention.
I am really proud of us
for helping Stewart.
Yeah, what an amazing
honest, human moment.
I agree. Yay us.
Marshall, are you really gonna
keep wearing that hat?
Yeah, it's been two weeks,
Marshall.
Two awesome weeks...
and heck, yeah,
I'm gonna keep wearing it.
Hey.
Marshall,
this is
an intervention.
It's about the hat.
Huh? No...
I have it under control, okay?
I can take it off
whenever I want to.
Dear Marshall,
I do not like
that stupid hat.
I want to beat it
with a bat.
Or maybe stab it
with a fork.
It makes you look
like such a dork.
TED:
After that,
interventions became
a pretty regular thing
around our apartment.
Shh.
(English accent):
Cor blimey.
This is a nice bloody surprise.
What's this about then?
Lily...
it's about the weird
fake English accent.
Oh, bollocks.
Oh... (clears throat)
Spray tan?
(sobbing):
They reel you in with a coupon,
and then you just get hooked.
Oh, we know, sweetie, we know.
No, no, no, no--
this is a new sweater.
What?
The magic tricks.
Specifically, those
involving fire.
Magic tricks?
Guys, interventions are
supposed to help people,
not attack every little thing
you don't like about them.
I'm sorry, but that
really steams me.
That really burns me up!
I mean, I am filled
with a white-hot rage!
(growling)
(all scream)
Thank you.
Oh, shoot.
I smell hair!
TED:
And that's the story
of the scorch mark.
Wait, that's weird.
When I was going
through the closet,
I thought I saw
the intervention banner.
S-So?
So, the banner burned up.
Why is there a new one?
And there are sealed letters
here from all of you
that say "Ted."
Were you guys planning
an intervention for me?
Oh, that--
that was stupid.
Yeah, just, just forget
about that.
Wh-What was it for?
The Crocs?
The hair product?
Not Stella.
Oh, my God,
this was about Stella.
I just said "Not Stella."
So maybe it was about
your poor listening skills, Ted.
What?
It's out of control. See?
Ted, we do.
We're all really happy
for you.
Yeah. Like I said,
it was stupid.
Well, obviously, it wasn't,
because we agreed
not to have any more
stupid interventions
at our intervention
intervention.
We're having
too many interventions.
So, what was your big, serious
oblem with me and Stella?
Yes!
Yes! In everyone's face!
You all said
the "future Barney" thing
wouldn't work.
You told me I was crazy.
My shrink told me I was crazy.
Well, who's the narcissist
with severe attachment disorder
now, Dr. Grossbard?!
Intervention banner?
What's that for?
Stella.
Ah.
"Ted, I cannot stand idly by..."
You've just been
carrying that around?
Please, Ted?
"I cannot stand idly by
while you make
"the biggest mistake any man
can make-- getting married.
"Mark my words,
"this whole thing is gonna go
up in flames!"
Oh, damn!
I put the flame cue too early.
I had so many more
important things to say, and...
The point is, Ted,
marriage is stupid.
Every year, there are
a million new hot 22-year-olds
walking into bars,
and call me "glass half full,"
but I think
they're getting dumber.
Oh, come on, Barney,
even you aren't still gonna be
hitting on 22-year-olds
when you're 80.
I accept that challenge.
What challenge?
To prove to you that
I will be exactly this awesome
when I'm 80, I will hook up
with a 22-year-old
while in my old-man makeup.
I didn't remotely
challenge you to that.
I mean, I definitely
want to see it.
But I didn't remotely
challenge you to that.
I want to hear
the other letters.
Ted, this is ridiculous.
W-We changed our minds.
And suppose
you change them back?
Lily, come on,
let's hear yours.
(sighs)
"Gilbert's reading skills have
improved drastically since..."
Wait, this is a letter
I meant to send home
with one of
my kindergarteners.
Uh-oh.
Gilbert,
are things moving too fast
between you and a girl
named Stella?
I wish.
Robin, could I hear yours?
(sighs)
"Dear Ted,
it's 'encyclo-pee-dia,'
not 'encyclo-pay-dia.'
"Why do you always
say things
"in the most pretentious
way possible?
"It makes you sound douchey--
and that's 'douchey,'
not 'douch-ay.'"
Yeah, you already read that one
at my pronunciation
intervention.
Where's the letter
about Stella?
I didn't write one--
I-I'm your ex-girlfriend;
I figured anything I said on
the subject would sound catty.
Plus, I'm hotter than her,
so who cares?
Marshall?
Dude, it's water
under the bridge...
Please.
(sighs)
"Dear Ted, Stella seems
like a wonderful person.
"But you don't know her
well enough to get married.
"You certainly
"don't know her well enough
"to commit to raising
a seven-year-old with her.
"You're not
"doing her, her child
"or yourself any favors
by rushing into this.
Just give it some more time."
Dude, that was months
ago, all right?
That was before we
got to know Stella
and see how awesome
she is and what a great
couple you guys are.
That's why we decided not
to even have that intervention.
Thank you.
Because I-I really need you guys
to be on board with this.
And we are.
And we hope you're
not mad at us.
Course not.
I mean, it's not like
what you said was crazy.
Y-You had a lot
of valid concerns.
Yeah,
but concerns we have
completely moved on from.
But you had a point.
I mean, this whole thing
has moved pretty fast.
Well, you know what?
Maybe that's because, uh,
when it's right,
yojust know.
Yeah, I guess,
but-but we are still,
you know, getting
to know each other.
And, Lily, maybe
you're right.
Maybe Stella won't like
any of my stuff.
Like the robot cookie jar.
This was, like,
the first thing
we bought for this place,
remember?
Of course I do.
(robot voice):
Marshall, my sensors indicate
that your pecan sandy levels
are dangerously low.
Ah. My collection
of James Bond movies.
Remember? We watched
them all in order,
and then Lily spoke
in that weird English accent
for, like, the next month?
It was sophisticated.
No.
Nope.
Oh!
My signed Bernie Kosar cleats.
My elephant lamp.
The English phone booth.
My sombrero!
(laughs)
Ted, what are you doing?
Unpacking.
No, no, Ted,
stop unpacking.
You're just freaking out.
I'm not ready for all
the responsibility.
And-And I'm certainly
not ready to be a step-dad
to a seven-year-old.
I mean, if I get married
and move to the suburbs,
in the blink of an eye,
I've become an old man!
Why, hello, young lady.
You want a butterscotch candy?
What do you mean,
"nothing in common"?
We're both seniors.
(cackling)
(laughs)
You're cute.
How old are you?
83. How old are you?
Thirty-one.
(groans):
Oh-oh...
Okay,
Ted has officially snapped.
There are moving men
coming in ten hours.
His fianc閑 is waiting for him
in New Jersey.
We have to do something.
I got this.
Hey, bud?
Hey.
Why don't you come
here for a minute.
What?
Look, I want you to know
this is all totally normal.
Big transitions can be
scary, and cold feet--
well, they're just
part of the deal.
So... how about you
give me the knife?
Give me the knife.
Come on.
So I can start unpacking, too.
I'm staying here right by
your side forever, buddy!
Yeah!
Marshall!
Lily,
our lives have
been good here.
That's why we've been
putting off packing.
Because subconsciously,
we both know that
it would be stupid to leave.
It's safe and warm here.
There's a bar downstairs,
and a cookie robot
in the kitchen.
This is my home,
and I'm never leaving!
Listen to you!
You sound like that
fat, dweeby kid at camp.
"Mom, Dad, I want to come home.
The cool kids are playing
keep-away with my inhaler."
I can't believe
my dad read that letter
at our wedding.
Marshall, you can't
do this to Lily.
Yes, I know your new place
has had some problems,
with the slanted floors
and the nearby
sewage treatment plant,
but you're gonna
turn it into a great home.
Tell him, Lily.
It's a black hole
where dreams go to die.
I'm not moving, either.
Oh, come on!
Yes!
Okay, you guys finish unpacking.
I'm gonna go
bake some cookies
to fill
R2-Sweet Tooth.
Oh, my God, look at you cowards!
So afraid of any kind of change.
So terrified of anything new.
So-so desperate to cling
to anything
comfortable and familiar.
I can't move to Japan.
Yes!
Whoa!
What was I thinking?
It's so far away.
And I don't speak the language.
(crying):
I didn't even have
any good pictures of you guys.
Oh, sweetie.
Everybody says
change is so great, right?
But what's so great
about change?
Hey, who wants
to walk down to our
same old bar,
sit in our regular booth
and order the usual?!
Yeah!
The usual!
My favorite!
Oh, my God.
(disgusted groan)
Well, well, well.
I believe
someone owes me $200.
Barney, this was
never a bet-- nobody...
This proves that I will be
this awesome when I'm 80.
Arthritis five.
I'm moving to New Jersey.
What?
And you and
Marshall
should move to your new place,
and Robin should go to Japan.
Why?
Because we're gonna get older
whether we like it or not,
so the only
question is
whether we want
to get on with our lives
or desperately cling to the past
and end up like that.
You mean awesome?
I'm 80, dude,
and I'm making out
with a 22-year-old.
(French accent):
Take me to your
place, cheri.
I want to see your
World War II medals.
(chuckles):
In a minute, mon petite.
All right, so that
doesn't count.
What? Why?
She's French--
that's like
playing tennis
with the net down.
You know what?
I'll cover the security deposit.
I'm glad to, because...
every dent in that place
represents a memory
that I'll cherish forever.
But on one condition:
we all put aside ten bucks
every week for the next year,
and we come back here and we
buy that 50-year-old scotch,
and we toast
the incredible
life-changing year
we've all had.
(quietly):
Get out of our booth.
Me with my new family,
Marshall and Lily in their
new apartment, and Robin
as the number one
English-speaking journalist
in the Pacific Rim,
visiting us
here in New York
to celebrate this day--
the day we closed
an incredible chapter
in our lives,
only to open up a new one.
Mm.
Um, I think I
left my cell...
Get out of here.
NARRATOR:
And one year later,
that's exactly what we did.
And so let's raise a glass
of $2,500 scotch
to one hell of a year.
Mm.
Amazing.
Mm-mm!
That's unbelievable.
It's kind of smoky,
with a hint of aged cedar and...
Do you guys taste the difference
and ten-dollar scotch?
Not at all.
No difference.
I want to cut mine
with Red Bull.
Oh, Wendy, can you
take a picture?
NARRATOR:
A lot of things
did change that year,
but some things
stayed the same.
So, uh, what do you say
we move this party
upstairs to the apartment?
Yeah.
Great idea.
I got the scotch.
What the...?
Barney, this is
an intervention.
(old man voice):
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
Enough with
the "old man" bit.
What about the old sand pit?
Let it go.
"Let It Snow"?
I love that old ditty!
I'm getting my flail.
You're setting sail?
www.tvsubtitles.net