Kids, Stella Zenman was the girl
I thought I'd spend
the rest of my life with.
Until she left me at the altar,
smashing my heart
to smithereens.
So when I ran into her
seven months later,
there was only one way
to deal with her.
Stella!
Great to see you!
You, too.
And Tony!
Hey.
Hey!
What a nice surprise.
"What a nice surprise"?
No, a nice surprise
would be if a safe fell
from 40 stories
and smushed them both.
I mean, you didn't
let them have it?
No, we had a nice
friendly chat,
then they went their
way and I went mine.
Ted, you blew it.
He blew it, right?
Well played, sir.
Bravo.
What?!
You see, Robin,
Ted played it cool,
which is exactly what
he should have done.
As a matter of fact, I'd say
on a scale ranging from...
(sobbing):
And I kept this sweater
of yours...
...and sometimes I just
sit in the bathtub
for hours just, you know,
just sniffing it.
...all the way to...
This is my new fianc?.
She's basically Stella,
except she's French and,
as you can see,
she's got enormous cans.
Enchant?
(giggles)
...I'd say you nailed it.
I'll do you one better.
You, sir,
got Stella thinking.
"Gosh, Ted seemed
so cool today.
Did I choose
the wrong guy?"
Give it a week;
you'll get her back.
And her front.
(shudders):
Oh.
Oh, did you just feel that?
I think we just had
a "what up" quake.
TED:
I don't want her back.
Or her front.
I just want to move on.
And this was an important
step towards that.
To moving on.
(all murmur)
NARRATOR:
And you know,
I really meant it.
But still, that night,
my mind began to wander.
(knocking on door)
(harp glissando plays)
I made a terrible mistake.
I know.
I'm a better person
than you are.
You totally are.
Let's get back together
and have way more sex
than before.
Deal!
(both moaning)
(knocking on door)
Hello, Ted.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
CBS
and VOLKSWAGEN.
It's what the people want.
(sighs)
No, come in. It's
not weird at all.
Ted, Teddy Ted Ted Ted.
(sighs)
I knew it was wrong
to steal somebody's fianc?.
I mean, I grappled with it.
I was up nights.
And not for the good reason.
Well, sometimes
for the good reason.
I mean, Stella and I
hadn't seen each other
in five years,
so, as you can imagine,
the beginning,
it was just fast and furious.
Lamps breaking,
furniture moving.
You see this bald patch?
Yeah, Tony...
Anyway, we moved on.
Me, Lucy, Stella--
we were gonna move to L.A.
I was gonna become
a screenwriter.
Then we bumped into you,
and you just looked so... sad.
Sad? No.
I-I think what you're
calling sad was actually
a jovial nonchalance.
Ted, you looked awful, okay?
Like a little dachshund puppy
with a bad back
that's got to pull itself around
on a cart.
Why are you here?
Look, Ted,
I know I can come across
pretty tough,
but I can't bear to have hurt
someone the way I hurt you.
I think fate put me
on that corner
to make this right.
Obviously, I can't fill
that giant crater
that Stella left
in your heart.
I've been dating.
Like, a lot.
And then I heard you got fired.
I transitioned into
small business ownership.
(clears throat)
It's the backbone
of the economy.
No, it's not.
Ted,
my family's got a lot of money.
And I want to use that money
to make this right with you.
Tony is rich?
Oh, Ted.
Oh, Ted, tell me
he wrote you a check.
Tell me he wrote you
a big, fat check.
A check so big
it doesn't take its shirt off
when it goes swimming.
(laughs)
Ha, that is a
big, fat check.
A check so big, if
you had sex with it,
you wouldn't tell
your buddies.
That is a big, fat check.
A check so big that when you sit
next to it on an airplane,
you find yourself wondering
whether the check should have
bought two seats.
That...
Is a big,
fat check!
Yeah! He didn't
write me a check.
Ted, I want to offer you a job.
A job?
Every year, my family gives
a lot of money
to Columbia University,
so I got some pull.
How would you like
to design...
NARRATOR:
My heart leapt into my throat.
A new library?
A new student center?
...your very own curriculum
as a professor of architecture.
(chuckles)
Huh?
No, thanks.
What do you mean,
"No, thanks"?
Ted, you would be
a great professor, okay?
You are knowledgeable,
you're a good talker,
and when you need to,
you can grow
a very handsome neck beard.
(both laugh)
I'm not gonna
be a professor.
Teaching architecture is
what you do when your career
has totally bottomed out and
you need to pay the bills.
(all murmuring)
Hey, hey, hey!
Small business owner.
Backbone of the economy.
I'm not gonna take
that job, all right?
I'm gonna be just fine.
New topic.
Okay, new topic.
I just got a $200
speeding ticket today.
Oh, that sucks, dude.
You couldn't
talk your way out of it?
You can't talk your
way out of a ticket.
I've done it.
It was-- what was it?--
it was 1998.
So where's the fire?
There's no fire.
Actually, uh,
you know, there is a fire
at this barbecue I'm headed to.
Nothing special.
Burgers, ribs.... brats.
Son, do you have any idea
how dangerous it is to be...
Did you say brats?
Yeah, brats.
My mom marinates them
in Belgian beer for two days.
No big.
Funny thing was,
I could've
sworn that one of those thick,
succulent,
hickory-smoked brats
had some writing on it.
Weird. Anyways,
what were you saying?
What-what did it say?
The brat?
It said "Property of Minnesota
State Trooper Jorgensen."
You a... you a brat man,
Officer Jorgensen?
You going to this address?
Mm-hmm.
Follow me and lean on the horn.
We're gonna be running
some reds.
Well, duh.
I would've done that, too,
if I'd have been going
to a barbecue.
Damn, I was.
See, it's all about
sizing up your opponent.
I could tell that the officer
was a brat man
because, well,
he was out of breath just from
walking to my car and he had
mustard on his holster.
Marshall Eriksen!
Manipulating an officer
of the law with your sausage.
MARSHALL:
Mm-hmm.
That is very hot.
You think I can't talk
my way out of a ticket?!
You think I can't
talk my way out of a ticket?
I am Barney
Stinson,
master of manipulation.
If I can talk a stripper
into paying me for a lap dance,
I think I can talk
my way out of a ticket.
Challenge accep-- Wait for it.
(chuckles)
I don't get it.
Oh, "Ted."
"Accep-Ted."
I get it now.
(knocking on door)
What now?
You want to be an architect?
Great.
Guy I went to private school
with wants a new house built.
Job's yours if you want it.
Tony, look,
I don't need your help.
Here's what he's offering you.
That is a big, fat check.
Showtime.
License and
registration.
Oh, of course, Officer.
Right away.
Sir, this is a gift certificate
for a custom-tailored
Italian suit.
So, we done here?
$375!
Ooh!
(chuckles):
Oh.
And he kept
the gift certificates.
Oh, man.
I'm gonna call Emilio
and tell him
to short-sheet him
on the crotch.
You are bad at this, dude.
Oh, whatever, Robin.
Like you've ever
talked your way out of a ticket.
Are you kidding me?
Robin's a pretty girl.
Pretty girls don't get tickets.
I bet Robin's been
pulled over tons of times,
never once gotten a ticket.
That is outrageous!
And factual.
License and regis...
(sobbing)
Oh, honey.
Oh, no, no,
no, don't cry.
It's okay. No
ticket for you.
Oh.
Just, uh, go a little
slower next time, okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah!
Excuse me.
I think I left something
in New Jersey.
Hey!
How did your lunch go
with the rich guy?
Well, uh, it started off great.
TED:
I want to design a house that
celebrates the landscape
without overpowering it.
Mm.
You know,
when Frank Lloyd Wright
designed Fallingwater
in 1935, there's...
Yes, yes, that's all fine.
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
What I'm really worried about
is the basement.
Specifically the laundry room.
The laundry room?
I require a laundry room
of 15 feet by 15 feet,
stain-proof ceramic tile
from floor to ceiling.
I'm a man who likes to do
his own laundry,
and sometimes, it gets messy.
Messy?
Messy.
Steel chains will dangle
from the ceiling
at a height of nine feet.
And that is where
my laundry bags
will hang for three days
and three nights
before I... clean them.
Uh, Ted, it-it kind of
sounds like
what this guy is asking you
to design...
It's a murder house.
It is.
It's totally a murder house.
You know, as a
martial artist,
I'm trained to
trust my instincts,
and my instincts are saying
this... feels very good.
The steak is so rare.
(shudders)
Right? Right?!
One final concern:
soundproofing.
I tend to make a lot of racket
when I launder.
I'll show you what I mean.
I'm gonna go to my laundry room,
and you tell me
if you can hear me.
Tony...
does something feel off
about this guy?
Yeah. Off the hook!
Bro, you are
nailing this.
(chain saw revving)
(maniacal laughter)
Ted, you can't design
a murder house!
I'm not gonna design
a murder house.
Ted, you can't design
a murder house!
I'm not gonna design
(engine accelerating)
(siren blips)
Bring it.
Officer, please,
my wife is about to have a baby!
Her water just broke!
Where's your wife?
She took the other car.
This is Italian leather, so...
I... Oh, come...
I'm sorry about that
murder house thing.
That was my bad.
That's on me.
So, new plan.
You, my friend, are gonna build
the Statue of Liberty a husband.
Now, I got some suction
down at City Hall.
Tony, stop it!
I don't want your help, okay?
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Why?
Because...
when you were with Stella,
I know how much I missed her.
I can only imagine you feel
the same way.
(laughs)
Okay, well,
let me put your mind a
I don't want Stella back, okay?
She lied to me
and left me at the altar.
What kind of person does that?
I'm better off without her.
She's all yours, buddy.
There you go.
Load off my mind.
And that was it. Tony left,
and I began to put this whole
business far behind me.
Or so I thought.
(knocking on door)
Stella...
Tony broke up with me.
Wow. Okay,
Tony broke up with you?
He said it was because
of something you said.
You got Tony
to dump Stella?
I am very sorry,
but I'm going to have to insist
that you bump this.
Let's, um, let's talk
out in the hall.
It'll be waiting.
So, why are you here?
Look, Ted, this is about
seven months too late,
but here goes.
I've been in love with Tony
since high school.
We dated for a long time,
but then I got pregnant,
and I guess for two 19-year-olds
it was just too much to handle,
so we broke up.
And for a long time I just
focused on being a mother.
I forgot about Tony.
I forgot about...
the very idea of being in love.
And then you came along
and reminded me.
And... I loved you for that.
I loved you so much, in fact,
that it was just shy of enough.
But I never stopped loving Tony.
Take him back, honey.
He's sorry.
No, that's-that's not...
that's not what's happening.
Just go back inside,
Mrs. Matsen.
(door closes)
It was good seeing you, Stella.
Can you talk to Tony?
What?
He'd listen to you.
You changed his mind.
You could change it back.
I know it's an awful thing
to ask...
Yeah, it's an awful thing
to ask.
Well, I don't know
what else to do, okay?
I love him.
Oh, you love him.
So what, you're-you're appealing
to the romantic in me?
Is that your strategy?
Because that guy's gone.
You can't pull
those strings anymore.
They're not attached
to anything thanks to you.
Go ahead, honey, kiss him!
Go inside,
Mrs. Matsen!
Mrs. Matsen,
go inside!
Okay, you can do this.
You can do this!
Oh, you can do this.
License and regis...
License and registration.
Excuse me?
I can only assume
you need a license
to have a face that beautiful.
And that body?
I'm guessing something that
explosive has to be registered
with the proper authorities.
Get out of the car.
Why, am I under arrest?
No...
but you're about to be
under me.
No. False.
Did not happen.
That's a line
from a porno.
I've seen that porno.
Hell, I've made
that porno.
When will you guys realize
that the only difference
between my real life and a porno
is my real life
has better lighting?
You're lying.
I am not lying!
I swear on my mother.
I swear
on Goliath National Bank.
I swear on my suits.
I...
am...
not...
lying.
He was lying.
Here's what really happened.
Go ahead, honey, kiss him.
Go inside,
Mrs. Matsen!
Mrs. Matsen,
go inside!
Is there anything I can do
to make this better?
No.
* Let's go to the mall,
everybody! *
Hello.
Ted, it's me! It's Barney
It's me! I need your help!
I'm in big trouble!
Whoa-whoa-whoa, slow down.
What happened?
I'm guessing something
that explosive
has to be registered
with the proper authorities.
Get out of the car.
Why, am I under arrest?
Yes, you are.
I ran your plates.
You've had 15 moving violations
in the last three days.
Get out of the car.
But no, my wife's having a baby!
I have a sausage
with your name on it!
Out of the car now!
(screaming)
I need you to come
to Brazzaville, New Jersey
and bail me out.
I'm kind of in the middle
of something.
Hurry, Ted.
You have no idea of the kind
of the hardened criminals
they've got me in here with.
Are we gonna get
our spray paint back?
Save me, Ted!
You want to do
something for me?
I need a ride to New Jersey.
Okay.
You'll pay for tolls, right?
I'm kidding.
So Stella and I drove
all the way out to New Jersey,
bailed your Uncle Barney
out of jail
and drove all the way home.
Oh, by the way, Ted, how's
that girl you've been seeing?
That super hot French chick
with the big enormous boobs?
Oh, you mean Claudette?
She's, uh,
she's fine.
Man, she's the hottest girl
you have ever been with, Ted.
Ever! Bye, Stella.
Bye.
Ted... I'm so sorry again
about everything.
For what it's worth...
I'll talk to Tony.
Really?
I want you to be happy, Stella.
I'll talk to him.
And I did.
I don't remember
what I said to him,
but I guess I changed his mind
because the next day,
they flew to California.
Stella set up a new dermatology
practice.
And against all odds,
Tony found some success
as a screenwriter.
His movie, The Wedding Bride,
was a big hit.
But we'll get to that later.
Okay, but just
tell me this.
Why Tony?
I mean, is it the money,
the kung fu pajamas?
Like, what...
what is it?
He's the one.
The one.
Yeah, I know it's kinda sappy,
but, yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna say something
out loud that I've been doing
a pretty good job of not
saying out loud lately.
What you and Tony have--
what I thought for a second
you and I had...
...what I know that Marshall
and Lily have...
I want that.
I do.
I keep waiting for it to happen
and waiting for it to happen,
and...
I guess I'm just, um...
I'm tired of waiting.
And that is all I'm going
to say on that subject.
You know, I once talked my way
out of a speeding ticket?
Really?
I was heading upstate
to my parents' house
doing, like, 90
on this country road,
and I got pulled over.
So this cop gets out of his car.
He kind of swaggers on over
and he's, like, "Young lady,
I have been waiting for you
all day."
So I looked up at him and I
said, "I'm so sorry, Officer.
I got here as fast as I could."
(chuckles):
For real?
(laughs softly):
No.
It's an old joke.
I know that you're
tired of waiting,
and you may have to wait
a little while more,
but she's on her way, Ted.
And she's getting here
as fast as she can.
Bye, Stella.
Good-bye, Ted.
* If it ever ends
* And somehow, you have
shattered my defense *
* And this is gonna hurt
* If it ever starts
* So promise you'll be careful
* With my heart
She tracked me down two days
later using a phone book.
And that's the last time I wrote
my name in my undergarments.
(both chuckle)
Hey.
Hey, Lily!
Lily!
You're back!
Barney, when you told me
that peanut butter
and jam joke,
I was completely
disgusted.
But I was in the shower
this morning
and it popped
into my head
and it actually
made me laugh.
Peanut butter.
So I can see now
how I may have overreacted.
Marshall's words,
not mine.
Well, it's good to
see you again, Lily.
Thanks.
So what have you
been up to?
I'm going to an
amnesia ward
with a bunch of photos
of my children
and a wedding ring.
I'm gonna find the hottest
patient/my wife,
and we are going...
Okay, so that's good
enough for tonight.
I gotta ease back
into this.
See you tomorrow!
Sync by honeybunny @addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net