In the spring of 2009,
I'd been hired to design
a new headquarters for
"Goliath National Bank".
And I was eager to add
as much of my voice as an architect
into the plans as possible.
Woodbeams, bathed in natural light
in the atrium.
They're gonna love it!
There was only one problem
and his name -
was Bilson
Wood? Natural light?!
Ah, no!
Natural light reminds the workers
that there's an outside world
where they have family and friends.
We wanna crush that!
You show up in the dark,
you go home in the dark,
You spend your whole damn day in the dark!
I need to hear Lily's voice
Who said you could leave?
Bilson was killing
every original idea I had.
Then, one day
GNB took him off the project
and created a new task force
to oversee my designs
Suddenly, everything changed
We'll have a roof top zen garden
for quiet contemplation
We'll have a reflecting pool in the lobby
where local children
can come to make wishes.
The New GNB,
A place of work -
that you can call "home".
Thank you, and um...
Welcome home.
Everything was going great,
until one day in the elevator..
A yeah, it's Ted
No, no, no, no, no
I did not approve that change
for the blueprints
for the new GNB headquarters
for which I'm head architect,
at only 30 years old..
Yes, I'm single, I'm not gift to charity.
What does that have to do with anything?
Alright, goodbye, Mr. Mayor.
You know that was a fake phone call,
don't you?
Yes, and I also know
that the new GNB headquarters project
was scrapped last month.
Nice try.
Check out Scarlett Johansson at the Oscars.
If I could nail any celebrity
it would definitely be Scarlett Johansson
Hot, talented,
and nobody does that many
Woody Allen's movies
without serious daddy's issues
If I could nail any celebritie,
it would be Lily.
She's the star of my heart.
For me, it would be Hugh Jackman.
You know, I don't know, celebrities,
they're into some really weird sex stuff.
Trust me.
How would you know that?
This is embarassing, but I...
I went home with a celebrity one night.
Oh my god! Seriously?
Yeah, he wanted to do
this really freaky thing with me,
So I left. That's it.
End of story.
No, no, not end of story
I need to know who, what,
when, and-and where. Spill it!
Lily, be calm, please settle down.
You're swallowing to much air.
But before you go any further,
I'm flattered, but technically,
I'm not a celebrity.
Plus, for the last time,
I put the mask on as a joke.
OK, not you Barney.
OK, who is it?
Great, now you gave Lily the hiccups.
Ok, I won't tell you anything specific.
But um, all I'll say
is that he is Canadian born,
but you definitely know this guy.
And he got me back to his place
by offering to show me
a very unique collection.
What do you mean collection
Well, you know some people collects
like stamps or coins, it's like that.
But I'm not telling.
Well, at least tell us
the weird thing he wanted to do.
I don't know what you call it in the States,
but we have a name for it in Canada.
Look, I've already said too much.
So, mystery celebrity
who collects a mystery item
asked you to do a mystery Canadian sex act.
Yes.
TELL US!
OK, I'll tell you.
But only if you guess all three parts correctly.
- Well, that's just impossible.
- Exactly.
I don't even know any Canadian sex acts.
Well, you got your "Sloppy Dog Sled",
your "Alberta Fur Trapper",
your "Full Mountie".
How do you know all these?
Canadiansexacts.org,
it's bookmarked on the top right.
- "Dot org"?
- Yeah.
It's not for profit.
They really just wanna
get the information out there.
Hey, so I just had the weirdest conversation.
This woman at GNB told me
that the new bank-building
was scrapped last month.
It's crazy, right?
Wait, what's that look
- Should we tell him
- I don't wanna tell him.
- I think we should tell him.
- We're not telling him.
There was no look!
Guys, what the hell?!
Ok, it's time that you know the truth.
A few weeks ago,
Bilson called us into his office.
We're scrapping the plan
for the new GNB headquarters.
This recession is killing us.
We're cutting anything non-essential.
And I have a lot of tough choices to make
at the bi-quartely retreat in Saint Croix.
Man, Ted is gonna be devastated.
Not when he hears it coming
from his best friend.
-I have to tell him ?
You should tell him,
you're his best friend.
I'm not, you're his best friend.
Quiet, here he comes.
Look, the white dude or the Asian fellow?
See? I bearly know the guy.
- Hey, Ted, what's up?
- Hey, how are you doing?
I'm frustrated.
Anything innovative I put in my designs
Bilson just hacks out with a machete.
I hate having to answer
to a guy like that.
You should drop the project.
You should totally drop the project.
It's beneath you.
Then it's settled.
To Ted Mosby's new chapter...
Are you kidding?
They just laid off another architect at my firm.
I mean, Bilson is a pain, sure,
But without this project,
I'm probably out of a job.
Right, it's funny that you mentioned the project
- ..because...
- You're nailing it.
Keep up the good work buddy.
Your hair and teeth look fantastic today.
You're shining like a diamond!
Thank you.
I needed that.
All right, I'm going to head upstairs
and keep working.
I got to find a way to introduce some wood
into Bilson's dark atrium.
I think you know what I meant.
- What was that?
- What-
I have a thought.
Okay, we're paying Ted's firm
for two more months of design-work
no matter what,
so couldn't we just let him
keep working and not tell him?
He's had a rough year.
Let's let the guy be happy
a little while longer.
Marshall, what you're suggesting
is an elaborate,long-term lie
that requires tremendous commitment.
A nice guy like you can't pull that off.
Sure I can.
Lie to me right now.
Okay.
I have a spaceship.
What kind of fuel powers your spaceship?
Okay, I don't have a spaceship.
No!
Stand your ground!
If someone questions you,
distract them from the original lie
with more lies.
Here, let me demonstrate.
I own a pony.
Ask me a question.
Okay.
Um, what color is your pony?
Well, when I first got Dandelion,
she was a deep, chestnut brown,
but, sadly, her stable is located
near a chemical plant,
which contaminated the drinking water.
So over time, she's turned a sickly,
grayish-white color
and there's nothing that
the vet can do to fix her.
My God!
That's horrible.
Is Dandelion going to be okay?
Okay.
All right. Huh
You are good!
Dandelion's not even sick, is she?
So the building's really dead
and you guys lied to me!
We, we just did it to protect you, Ted.
I can't believe this.
I just got screwed by my two best friends
and I didn't even know it.
In Canada, that's called a "Sneaky Snowplow".
That building was my dream job,
and now, it's just gone.
We're so sorry, Ted.
Yeah, I need a drink.
Poor Ted.
Would I seem heartless
if I switched us back to Canadian Sex Acts?
- Not at all.
- I'm surprised you waited this long.
What the hell is a "Two-Hand Zamboni"?
Let's just say, the only thing
the woman is wearing
is skates on her hands.
A "Manitoba Milk Bag"?
Okay, it's like a "Chicago Mustache",
but the person on the bottom
is wearing a snowsuit.
A "Newfoundland Lobster Trap"
Don't know,
don't wanna know.
Those Newfies are out of control.
Okay! Okay,
I'm going to make my first guess.
Okay, but I'll only tell you
if you correctly guess the person,
the act and the collection.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Bryan Adams.
He collects baseball cards,
and he wanted to do a "Greasy Kayak."
No.
Wayne Gretzky, vintage Hot Wheels,
a "Squatting Eskimo".
Nah-uh.
Kiefer Sutherland, souvenir shot glasses,
and a "Sticky Flapjack".
No.
That I would have done.
Wait.
Wait, if they pulled the plug
on the project a month ago,
why have I been going in once a week
to meet with the
New Headquarters Task Force?
Well, obviously you couldn't come in
and pitch to Bilson.
So, we.. invented the task force.
Then it was just a question
of putting together the team.
You know Roy Waterman,
Vice President of Capital and Risk?
He's actually...
Roy the janitor.
Hey. Excuse me, Roy.
How'd you like to make a few extra bucks?
How naked do I have to get?
Louisa Mendoza,
Executive Vice President of Assets?
She's actually...
Louisa the lunch lady.
Louisa, I need your help with something,
but you can't tell anybody.
No hablo Ingles.
Exactly.
This is a big secret.
How do you say "secret" in Spanish?
Albondigas?
Ah, yes. Albondigas.
This will be our little albondigas.
Hey, can I, uh,
have a couple of meatballs, please?
And Arthur Nasmith,
the eccentric genius guru
of corporate investments?
He's actually...
Crazy Arty,
15th Street's own one-man band.
Excuse me.
Do you have a minute to talk?
Actually, my assistant Reginald
makes all my appointments.
We rounded out the group
with a few interns
and payed everyone 50 bucks
to act super-interested
in what you were saying.
Reginald, get me out of this for next week.
That was some of the most
inspired design-work
I've done in my entire career.
I was so excited.
Alex Trebek, a "Musty Goaltender",
- Beanie Babies!
- Nope.
Damn it!
Wait.
So that explains the thing
that happened with Louisa.
- Good job, buddy.
- Nice, nice!
Listen, Louisa.
What are we gonna do about.. this..
Don't act like you don't know
what I'm talking about.
I know you feel it too.
Ahh, what the hell!
No, no puedo.
Me voy a casar con el senor Barney.
La vida es una!
No! No!
No, this is wrong!
For God's sake,
you're on the task force!
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
Well, um, you know how you played
third base for the GNB softball team?
There is no GNB softball team.
We just rented out a field,
rounded up a bunch of guys
and told them
to make you the hero.
So my game-winning walk, was a lie?
We're sorry, Ted, but we knew
that you'd be out of work soon,
and we just --
we just wanted to make you feel good.
You know, that's what friends do.
Lie to each other?
Sometimes, yeah,
to protect each other's feelings.
No way!
You never lie to your friends.
I would never not be honest with you.
Really?
What about that open mic night
at the comedy club?
Are you like me, folks
Have you ever thought about how many
different kinds of fish there are,
And the names of those fish?
Let's, uh, let's take a little ride.
"Trout".
Am I right?
"Sturgeon".
I don't think so, pal.
"Salmon".
I'm going to say that again, "salmon".
Who thought that was a good idea, right?
"Bass." This guy over here knows
what I'm talking about.
"Halibut."
Thank you, good night.
How was I?
Oh, you were great.
Really funny.
You killed...
everyone's Thursday night.
Time out.
You didn't like the fish list?
It was horrible!
You just read a list of fish.
Anyway...
You guys just proved my point, okay?
You lied to me, to protect my feelings.
This is completely different!
I just wasted a month of my life
working on a dead project.
That's time I could've spent
trying to bring my firm new business.
Instead, I'm going to go
in there tomorrow morning.
I'm probably going to get fired.
Best case scenario,
my boss is going to ream me out
in front of everybody.
...
Back home, we call that a Sas...
a "Saskatoon Totem Pole."
Yes. It's on here.
Good morning, lying bastards.
Anything you want to lie about
before I head off to work to get fired
- That's a nice shirt.
- You're the devil.
Ted, what if we told you
that we found you
a new project at GNB
where you would be
redesigning part of the 20th floor?
Well, if that's a lie,
it's an incredibly dull one.
What exactly would I be doing?
This is the 18th Floor E.T.R.
Basically,
Bilson wants a room just like this,
only two stories up, on our floor.
Wait, what's an E.T.R.
It's the "Employee Transition Room".
- What does that mean?
- Well, it's a space
where a supervisor and an employee
engage in a knowledge transfer
about an impending vocational paradigm shift.
People get fired in here.
That's horrible!
Why do you need a room
specifically for firing people?
Well, um, GNB feels
that people need a safe,
secure space to deal with the news.
Yeah.
It gets pretty real in here.
So I reluctantly agreed
to design a room
where people would be fired.
But I was determined to make it my own.
Now, when you leave the dismissal space,
you'll exit into what
I'm calling the "Rebirth Tranquility Hallway".
Uh-oh.
Here, you'll find a soothing oval chamber
with a trained grief counselor.
It's right here,
past the New Beginnings Fountain.
Uh-oh.
And there you have it.
Instead of a drab, dark prison cell,
a nurturing womb...
birthing you into a new life.
I love it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Nice work, Ted.
Thank you.
Can you add some of these touches
to the existing 18th Floor E.T.R. as well?
- Absolutely.
- Great.
Let's take a look.
Okay, so I'm thinking this wall..
You're fired!
What!
I wanted this room!
This exact room, two floors up!
But...
You're fired!
Now, get the hell out of here.
Hey, honey.
Anyone from the band Rush,
a "Montreal Meatpie",
and superhero lunch boxes.
No.
Okay. Rick Moranis,
"The Reverse Rick Moranis",
antique Judaica.
- Nah-uh.
- I give up.
I've been guessing for three days.
I-I-I'm done.
If that means I never get to know,
- So be it.
- Fine.
Tell us!  Tell us!
Tell us!
Okay, you really want to know?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
But this information,
does not leave this table.
Oh, my, God.
I am so excited.
- Oh... I'm going to read it.
- Read it.
- I'm going to read it.
I'm going to read it.
Here we go.
"The Frozen Snowshoe,
Old King Clancy, Harvey's trays".
Right?
I don't know what any of those words mean.
Is one of those supposed to be a celebrity?
Yeah, who the hell is "Old King Clancy??
No, that's not the person,
that's the sex act.
It's the same as a "Sacramento Turtleneck",
except with maple syrup.
So the celebrity was Harvey Straze?
No, that's what he collected.
Harvey's trays.
Those classic orange trays you get
whenever you eat at Harvey's?
The restaurant?
Oh, come on, you're road tripping
down the Trans-Canada Highway,
you get a hunger on
between Milverton and Wawa,
where you gonna strap on a feed bag, huh?
Harvey's. Over 12,000 served!
So the celebrity was...
The Frozen Snowshoe.
Oh, my God!
You guys have never heard
of The Frozen Snowshoe?
He's only the most famous
professional wrestler in Canada.
I met him after he defeated
Reckless Rick Rogers
in the Kamloops Memorial Arena
back in '02.
Classic match.
So you're saying The Frozen Snowshoe
invited you back to his place
to look at Harvey's trays,
and asked you to do an Old King Clancy?
Exactly.
And I'm serious, you cannot tell anyone.
Well, my hiccups are gone.
Possibly forever.
Canada!
You did it again.
You even found a way to ruin this.
Why do we let you be a country?
Hey, mister-mister.
Hey. Shouldn't you be upstairs
designing your big, fancy E.T.R.?
- I'm off the project.
- What?
Bilson fired me.
You're kidding me.
So what does this mean
for you  at your firm,
Are you going to get laid off?
Actually, I just quit.
Why?
Because I can't work for big,
heartless corporate clients anymore.
When I was pitching to your "task force",
I was doing the most inspired work
of my career.
In a way, you idiots reminded me
how much fun my job can be,
when I'm not answering
to the Bilsons of the world
So...
I quit.
They fired you, didn't they?
Yes, sir.
But, I got a sweet severance package
and I've made a big decision.
I'm going to start my own firm.
- Whoa, buddy.
- That's exciting.
- Way to go.
- In this economy?
So you're not mad?
As it turns out, I'm grateful.
So how'd it all go down
between you and Bilson?
Well, after he proposed
a vocational paradigm shift,
I made an impromptu presentation
using a four-pronged approach
that really brought him to his knees.
Hit him with a chair?
- Yep.
- That's my boy.
And this one, I got on the drive
from Milverton to Wawa.
That's pretty impressive,
The Frozen Snowshoe.
Please, we're friends.
Just call me "Shoe".
Have a seat.
So, Shoe...
How would you like to give me...
an Old King Clancy?
I think you should go.
www.tvsubtitles.net