You will not believe what happened
at laser tag last night.
People freaked out because
a creepy man in a suit wouldn't leave their kids alone?
No.
Well, yeah, pretty much.
Come on!
Ow! My shoulder!
Come on.
Stinson, my office! Now!
Crap.
Disorderly game play,
three counts of shoving,
and now this!
Stinson, you're a liability!
I know I don't play by your precious rules, McCracken,
but, damn it, I get results!
Look, you're a good laser tag player.
Maybe the best I've ever seen.
But one of these days,you're gonna get someone hurt.
Maybe even yourself.
You just forgot what it's like out there.
You've had your fat ass stuck behind that desk for too long.
That's it!
You're out of here, Stinson!
Hand in your gun and your ID badge!
With pleasure.
Please don't do this.
This game is all I got.
And I've almost got
enough tickets for the remote control helicopter.
Please.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
But I'm gonna give you one last shot.
But so help me,
if you so much as step one toe out of line,
you're gonna be playing Duck Hunt in your mama's basement
so fast it's gonna make your head spin.
Now, get out of here!
You won't regret this.
That's it, Stinson.
You're banned for life!
No...!
I can't believe you got kicked out of laser tag.
What are you gonna do?
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
I'll tell you what Ted and I are gonna do.
We're gonna break in after hours
TP?
and TP the place.
Barney, we are too old to cover a place in toilet paper
just because they won't let you play laser tag.
And for that matter,
too old for laser tag.
Ted, laser tag knows no age restrictions.
Kind of like stripping in the Midwest.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm adding laser tag to the Murtaugh List.
Oh, jeez, not the Murtaugh List
What's the Murtaugh List?
around the time I turned 30.
It all started with your Uncle Marshall's beer bong.
every time we had a party,that beer bong came out.
the next day would go like this.
Then one day, in the throes of the worst hangover of my life,
I realized there was only one person in the world
that I could relate to:
Detective Roger Murtaugh,played by Danny Glover
in the '80s noir masterpiece Lethal Weapon,
known for his often-quoted catchphrase:
I'm too old for this...
Stuff.
He said, "I'm too old for this stuff."
It's sad to admit, but as you get older,
there's just certain things you can't do anymore.
That's why I have this list,
so I never make the mistake of thinking
that I can still pull an all-nighter.
I'm too old for that stuff.
Or  eat an entire pizza in one sitting.
Or hang posters on your wall without frames.
Riggs.
Riggs!
I'm too old for that stuff.
By the way, how good is Lethal Weapon?
Oh, I don't know.It's kind of a rip-off.
Old guy paired up with a young, renegade cop.
Sound familiar?
Mackleroy and LeFleur.
Don't tell me you guys
have never seen Mackleroy and LeFleur.
It's the greatest Canadian action movie of all time.
Mackleroy is a young, renegade Mountie
whose horse was just killed by evil Americans,
while LeFleur, his grouchy,old, African-Canadian partner,
just bought a cozy ice
fishing shack in northern Alberta...
All right, I got to go.
Bye, baby.
Have fun at practice.
Practice?
Is he doing that one-man band thing again?
'Cause that was a bummer.
Actually,
Marshall had just taken over
as coach for Lily's kindergarten basketball team.
He thought it'd be fun,
but Lily saw it as something more--
dad practice.
Hi.
Hey! Oh, my gosh!
Orange slices. That is so sweet.
What are you doing here?
I couldn't resist.
I wanted to see Coach Marshmallow do his thing.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, kids,
who wants to knock off early
and have some of these here orange slices?
Yeah? Well, you can't!
Because oranges are for winners,
and you little turds
haven't even made a single shot yet!
You're embarrassing yourselves,
you're embarrassing Ms. Aldrin, and worst of all,
you're embarrassing me!
That's it!
Suicides! Baseline! Now!
Run.
Ted, there is not a single thing on here
that you are too old to do.
In fact, if you did everything on the Murtaugh List,
I'd call that a pretty fun weekend.
If you did everything on that list, you would die.
-That wasn't a challenge.-Challenge accepted.
I'm going to do every single thing on this list.
And after I do, you will TP the laser tag place with me.
And if you can't do it?
I will spend three hours
listening to you talk about architecture.
You have got yourself a deal.
Robin, will you do the honors?
A gentleman's agreement!
Huzzah!
All right, chumps, let's do this.
Barney Stinson!
You really want to make this bet with him?
You know how he is.
Robin, there is some pretty tough stuff on that list.
I mean, do you really think
Barney's gonna get his ear pierced?
"Get ear pierced."
Check.
All right, I'm off to go
do laundry at Mom's house.
Hey, you guys mind if I crash on your futon tonight?
We don't have a futon.
Put it over there, boys.
What's going on? It's on the Murtaugh List.
"Crash on a friend's futon
instead of getting a hotel room."
Ooh, I am too old for that stuff.
Dude, what's going on with your ear?
Looks like the inside of a jack-o'-lantern on November 3rd.
What, this?
Ah, just a little infecsh.
Nothing a young guy like me can't shake off.
Plus, "Put off going to the doctor," on the list.
Oh, hold on.
Go for Bar...
Keep running!
You know what's funny, is I was
supposed to come here to teach them--
Do not stop running!
This whole time, they've been the ones who are teaching me.
That's not running! That's falling!
The next morning,
Barney woke up on the futon in our living room.
Check.
"Drinking shots with strangers."
You okay, Barney?
It looks like you hurt your back.
Oh, no.
Just rocking a party hunch.
I like it.
Closer to my booze.
To youth.
Can I get a straw?
I must say, there's something admirable
about the way Barney wants to stay young at heart.
I mean, who wants to get old?
This guy.
Robin, life is a meal
and old age is the dessert.
I spend so much of my time worrying about the future.
You know, where's my career going?
Who am I gonna marry?
But when you're old, you don't worry,
'cause that stuff's already happened.
Plus, you get to wear comfy shoes
and a chair takes you up and down the stairs, it's perfect.
That's not perfect. That's pathetic.
You can't just jump to the end.
The journey is the best part.
Oh, Robin.
I used to feel that way, too,
but you'll understand when you're a little bit older.
Marshall, can you try
not to pick on the kids today.
I'm not picking on the kids, Lily.
I'm picking on the culture of losing around here.
I-I got to get them in shape
if they're gonna win that game tomorrow.
Win?
We don't keep score.
What?
You don't keep s...
What's the point of playing if you don't keep score?
How do you know...
Lily, what were you doing with this team before I got here?
I was coaching them.
That's it, my little angels.
You're all luminous wonderful beings of light.
What's the score?
It's all tied up at fun to fun!
Because that's the point of playing-- to have fun.
No.
The point of playing is to win the trophy.
And if you don't know who's winning, who gets the trophy?
Everyone.
It's a participation trophy; everyone gets one.
It's like you're speaking Chinese to me right now.
Hi, this is Barney.
And Robin.
We can't answer the phone right now because...
He's watching sports and I'm...
Probably out shopping.
Leave a message and we'll call you back just as soon...
As...We...
- Can!  - Can!
"Leave an annoying two-person message
on your answering machine."
Check.
Probably gonna cost me some dates but it's okay.
Barney, your ear's starting to smell.
Nah, it's good.
I hate to send it back,
but you did describe the turkey as extremely lean,
and, well, you tell me.
All right.
That's it.
-We have our own list.  -What?
This is a list of things you're too young to do.
Go out and do each one of these things
and then tell me you still want to be an old man.
Remove "colonoscopy"
and "Have sex with an old lady," and this is a cakewalk.
New stakes, then.
If I can finish your list before you finish mine,
you have to come with me to TP laser tag
and you have to buy the toilet paper.
And none of that biodegradable crap.
I want it up there forever.
Fine, but if I finish your list first,
it's a six hour survey
of early 20th century American architecture
and you can never do anything
on the Murtaugh List ever again.
It's for your own good.
You, sir, have got yourself a deal.
A gentleman's agreement!
Huzzah!
Marshall, they're in kindergarten.
This isn't how you teach basketball.
Sure it is. It's the way I learned.
Are you kidding me?
What kind of sociopath taught you this way?
Come on, Dad. I'm tired.
Sleep is for winners.
You can go to bed when you score a basket.
I'm trying.
Oh, let's give you two points for trying.
But negative two points for having a great big head.
My father gave me no quarter
and I asked for no quarter.
I totally got to call that guy.
Keep stretching!
"Put on reading glasses." Check.
"Yell at neighborhood kids."
My pleasure.
What the hell happened to you?
Oh, I just had a very minor
"blew out my knee and it hurts like hell" incident.
How did you blow out your knee?
We, uh, "Helped someone move out of a sixth floor walk-up
in exchange for pizza and beer."
Or we, uh, helped someone rob a sixth floor walk-up.
They were in a big hurry and left all the pictures behind.
Whatevs, it counts.
Now, I am off to
"Dye my hair a funny color,"
and then we are going to, "Go to a rave."
Ooh, 4:00!
Supper time.
Okay.
So, your dad was tough on you.
That stinks,
but you don't have to be like him.
You can learn from his mistakes.
Mistakes? Lily, scoreboard.
The guy nailed it, okay? He taught me how to be a winner.
That's what I'm teaching these kids.
And, for that matter,
that's what I'm gonna teach our kids someday.
Okay, that's it.
This is not how we're gonna raise our kids!
And this is not how you're gonna coach this team!
At tomorrow's game,
if you are anything less
than a teddy bear stuffed with cotton candy and rainbows,
I will silent treatment your ass into the ground!
You'll think the time I found your Internet search history
was a freakin' picnic!
Are we clear?!
Lily, there are many different philo...
Yes, ma'am.
You know, what's ironic is that now...
Just call Ted.
I want to go home.
All right. I'm calling him.
But it's 4:30 in the morning.
He's not going to be awake.
Up at 4:00...
Check.
Is he answering?
I haven't dialed yet.
Oh, please hurry, Robin.
Ooh, perfect.
"Take forever to answer the phone."
Come on, Ted.
Someone gave me some aspirin
and I don't think it was aspirin.
Check.
So, I know that I have been a little tough on you
for the past couple days.
And I apologize for that.
So today, we're not gonna worry about winning.
We're gonna go out there and...
have fun.
Kids, over the years,
your Uncle Marshall has told and retold
the story of this game hundreds of times.
And in reality,
the kids on that other team
were probably only a grade older
But, in telling and retelling the story,
they came to look like this.
Let's go, baby!
Yay! Way to let them score that easily.
Oh, now you're sitting down. Awesome.
Addison, it's not soccer.
You don't kick the ball!
Unless that's something that you think is fun,
in which case, great job having fun.
Whoa, that was a foul, wasn't it, Ref?
My name's not Ref. It's Kenny.
And watch your tone.
Oh, no tone, Kenny.
Great job, Kenny.
Thanks a lot, Kenny.
See you later, Kenny.
All right, Barney.
As your manager,
This bet is over.Your ear looks like
a free Danish
Ow! No.
No. One thing left.
"Beer bong."
Oh! Coming right up.
Oh, I, uh,
found these weird Russian beers in the basement.
Russian beers? I'll take a brewski.
Hey. Brewski. Get it?
Yeah, it's, uh...
It's a little warm.
Hope that's not a problem.
Uh... no.
Uh, no.
Okay.
Ah! I... All right, Ted.
You win. I hate this.
I hate all of it.
My back is killing me.
Everyone at the rave thought I was a narc.
My ear hurts so bad I can hear it...
I can hear my own ear.Think about that.
My clothes...
What is it... What is it...What am I...
Get this stuff off of me!
Ted, I'll pay you double for your finest suit.
Here's, uh, 30 bucks.
And throw in the shoes.
You win, Ted.
I'll never do anything on the Murtaugh List again.
I'm too old for this stuff.
You know, Barney, last night,
because it was on the list,and I couldn't sleep because...
well, it was 8:00.
So I decided to watch Lethal Weapon.
And then, when I still couldn't sleep,
I watched Lethal Weapon 2.
And then I watched 3.
And then, halfway through Lethal Weapon 4,
is when it occurred to me...
Murtaugh kept saying,"I'm too old for this stuff,"
but every time he'd say it,
he'd turn around, make another movie,
and do more stuff.
I guess what I'm saying is...
screw being old.
Let's go TP laser tag, huh?
And then the hospital.
Great job, guys.
At least we're not keeping score, right?
No idea what the score is.
53?0
Could be 53 to zero.
Could be some other score.
It's 53 to zero.
What are we doing wrong, Coach?
You know what? You're not doing anything wrong.
It's great that you guys are losing,
because in life,it doesn't matter
how much effort you put in,
or how hard you try,
people will just give you things.
Like diplomas and jobs and promotions.
So, it doesn't matter what you do out there,
as long as...as long as you have fun.
At that point,
because they didn't want to fight in front of the kids,
your Uncle Marshall and Aunt Lily
had one of their telepathic conversations.
Don't you give me that look.
Lily, I can't take it anymore!
Your way of coaching is crazy!
Stop yelling at me!
Sorry.
But can I please do it my way?
Fine, but I'm going to do it my way, too.
I'm getting my guitar.
I don't know if it was Marshall's tough attitude,
Lily's gentle encouragement,
or some magical combination of the two,
but in the second half of that game,
that ragtag group of little firecrackers...
got beat down even worse.
In fact, according to your Uncle Marshall,
in the second half,the other team got even taller
And one of them turned into a Teen Wolf.
Kenny! There is a Teen Wolf on the court!
That can't be legal.
I know the Teen Wolf looks different, kids,
but try to make sure he feels included.
How is that not traveling, Kenny?!
You are killing me!
You are absolutely killing me!
Hey, watch it, Coach,
or you'll get a technical.
Oh, Kenny.
I am begging you to give me a technical.
When the final horn mercifully blew,
the score was, by Marshall's estimate, 118 to nothing.
And even though they didn't win anything,
everyone, even the coach,got a participation trophy.
I understand if you don't want it.
I love it.
I just... I worked so hard.
It feels good to be appreciated for my effort.
I know, baby.
Maybe-maybe your way is not totally stupid.
Thanks.
Your way is totally stupid
Stinson!
Son...
you have been a pain in my ass
But damn it...
if this ain't some of the finest TP work I've ever seen.
You're reinstated...
effective immediately.
Really?!
Hell, no!
I'm calling the police!
Grown-ass man with pink hair throwing toilet paper.
You've got to be kidding me,you're too old for this...
staff, he said staff
www.tvsubtitles.net