There is something
I wish my dad had told me.
The longest pause you will ever
experience in your life
is the one that follows asking
the question...
Will you marry me?
Your brain goes into overdrive,
imagining every
possible response.
No.
Oh, God, no.
(laughing)
(snorts):
You want me to marry...
No.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ted.
I can't.
Mark Johnson,
the quarterback
from your high school football
team, already asked me.
What's up, Turd?
It's Ted!
But if you're lucky,
she may answer with the single
greatest word
in the English language.
Yes.
Stella and I spent that summer
happily engaged.
Marshall was still coping
with unemployment.
What are you doing?
Lily threw herself
into her painting.
What are you doing?
Barney was rehabilitating
from his bus accident.
What are you doing?
And well, Marshall just kept
coping with unemployment.
What are you doing?
And Robin
continued to uphold
the high journalistic standards
of Metro News 1.
Is your favorite
brand of dental floss
poisoning your entire family?
Tune in at 11:00
for the shocking... tooth.
Okay, I officially
hate my job.
I'm not a reporter,
I'm just someone
who shows up at night
and scares people.
I'm the bogeyman
with a teleprompter.
(laughing)
"Bogeyman
with a teleprompter."
That's hilarious!
Great joke,
Robin, great joke.
Barney, no offense
to Robin,
but that wasn't
that funny.
Are you kidding?
That was a great joke.
It's smart, funny, beautiful,
the whole package.
It's everything you're
afraid to let yourself want.
In a joke.
(laughs):
"Bogeyman with a teleprompter."
Classic.
Okay, what is so urgent
that you called me and begged me
to come over
at 7:22 in the morning?
I could tell you knew
something was up with me,
and you're right.
But I can't
tell you what it is.
I should tell you,
but I can't!
I have to.
I never will!
I'm going to.
Let's just drop it.
What's up with you?
Barney, just say it.
I think I'm in love with Robin.
Hey, Lily needs
some gift ideas
for Stella's
wedding shower.
Does she like to cook?
Um... actually,
I don't know.
Oh, what's her favorite color?
Don't know that either.
Well, does she have any hobbies?
Yes, she's exactly
the kind of person
who would have hobbies.
And interests, too.
I am one lucky son of a bitch.
Dude, you don't know
anything about the woman
you're marrying.
What? You're crazy!
I know plenty.
What color are her eyes?
The color of the ocean
after a storm.
Which is?
Beautiful.
I don't believe it.
I thought
you called me over here
to uncuff you
from your sex swing again,
but you're in love?
That is so sweet!
It's not "sweet."
It's like a disease.
I slept with Robin one time
and I caught feelings.
I caught feelings bad.
I used protection
and everything.
Oh, Barney, you don't
"catch" feelings,
you just have them.
And they're good.
They're terrible!
I can't eat, I can't sleep.
She's all I think about.
I close my eyes, I see Robin.
I, I hear a song;
it reminds me of Robin.
Morning.
I sleep with that chick,
I'm thinking
about Robin.
Okay, so I don't
know every single
detail about Stella.
What's this really about?
Do you not like her
or something?
No, Ted,
I like Stella a lot.
She's a Mets fan.
Really?
It's just that
everything with you guys
has moved so fast.
You've only known
each other a few months.
Don't you think maybe
you should slow things
down a little bit?
Get to know each other better?
I'll have
a whole lifetime
to get to know her better.
Right now, I know
the one thing that I have to:
that I love her.
You love her?
(sighs)
Barney,
how can you be in love,
and still be sleeping
with anything that moves?
I'm sorry,
I don't follow you.
That's like saying,
"How can an ant carry
"20 times its body weight,
but root beer floats
are still delicious?"
Are the two even related?
Really? Ow!
Barney, you're going
to have to stop screwing around
if you want to be
Robin's boyfriend.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
(chuckles):
"Boyfriend"?
I don't want
to be Robin's boyfriend.
Well, what do you want, then?
I don't know.
I just want
to be with her.
All the time.
I want to hear about her day
and tell her
about mine.
I want to hold
her hand and smell her hair.
But I don't want to be
her stupid boyfriend.
Barney, what you
just described
is a relationship
between a boyfriend
and a girlfriend.
And a pretty clingy one at that.
Look, Lily, are you going
to help me out with this or not?
I'm a kindergarten teacher.
I see a confused,
little kid in the corner
trying to eat
the lefty scissors,
I gotta help the poor,
little bastard.
But only if you
stop sleeping around.
Deal?
Deal.
Coming up next,
is your local ice cream man
actually driving a roving
meth lab on wheels?
Stay tuned for the full...
(sighs):
scoop.
Really?
(humming)
Uh-huh...
Mmm...
I know dudes
think it's girlie
for a guy to cook,
but us ladies?
We find it mighty sexy.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
You know, uh...
my grandma
taught me how.
Oh, yeah, she did.
Yeah.
I had a lot
of time after school
to watch her
cook because
(whispers):
I wasn't good at sports.
I'm on fire right now.
Delicious.
What's in this pesto?
Oh, you know, the usual:
basil, garlic, olive oil,
but can you guess
my secret ingredient?
Peanuts.
Yes. How did
you know that?
OK, Let me think. What else?
You know what, sweetie?
I woke up so early and I had
a really long day at work.
And then there
was that whole thing
where you tried to kill me.
Can we please just go to sleep?
No, I clearly need
to know more about you.
Let's do firsts.
Um, first kiss?
Dale Harris, second grade.
Wait, you're talking
like peck on the cheek
or a full-on passionate
making out?
Passionate making out.
Okay, yeah,
Dale Harris, second grade.
Uh, first time you had sex.
Dale Harris, second...
Stop it.
Billy Devito,
sophomore year of college.
Prude.
Molly McKenzie,
junior year of high school.
Slut.
Robin just needs to see
this new see of you.
So just call her up?
Just call her up.
It's...
(high-pitched mumbling):
Hi, Robin.
She wasn't there.
I left a voice mail.
You left a voice,
but it wasn't male.
Barney, I don't get it.
You've called a million
girls a million times.
Yeah, but those
were just booty calls.
On a booty call,
you barely even have to talk.
Around 9:00 p.m., you say...
Hey, baby, it's Barney.
You busy tonight?
Sweet.
See you in half an hour?
Can't wait.
But the later it gets,
the fewer words you need.
Barney. Busy?
Sweet.
And by 3:00 in the morning...
A question mark?
You got laid off
a question mark?
(chuckles)
Ow! Hey!
It's no worse than your
super-obvious code words.
(indistinct chatter)
Rhinoceros.
We have to go.
Great. Now we need
a new code word.
(phone ringing)
Ah, ah, it's her,
it's Robin.
What do I do?
No-no-no-no, aah!
Robin...
great to hear from you.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
You called, went
(mimics gibberish), and hung up.
What do you want?
(chuckles):
Help me!
(whispers):
Uh, just ask
her something.
How are you feeling today?
Fine.
Something personal.
Um...
At what age did you first
get your period?
Did you just ask me
about about my period?
No, I did not.
Look, Barney,
I'm at work right now.
Just ask her out.
Um, Robin,
I was wondering if...
Nothing.
Gotta go. Bye.
Ha, ha!
Ha! That was
just a practical joke.
I'm not really in love
with Robin.
You should've seen the look
on your face.
There's cameras
right there and there
and there. Ah!
What a legendary prank
that we're never going
to speak of again.
Gross.
Uh, first movie
you ever saw.
Benji, 1981.
I watched it recently with Lucy
and I just thought,
"Oh, that dog
is so dead right now."
What about you?
My dad took me
to an old drive-in
to see the original Star Wars.
You know, I've aually
never seen Star Wars.
She's never seen Star Wars?!
Ted, the only people
in the universe who haven't seen
Star Wars are the characters
in Star Wars,
and that's 'cause they
lived them, Ted!
That's 'cause they lived
the Star Wars.
You've got to calm down.
I told you. I told you
you didn't
know this girl well enough.
What if you show it to her
and she doesn't like it?
Dude, it's just a movie.
Ted, Star Wars is your all-time
favorite movie,
and whether or not Stella
likes it is actually important.
It's like, it's a test
of how compatible you guys are.
Marshall, it's just a movie.
It's just a movie.
(movie closing theme flourish
playing)
Okay, if Stella
doesn't like this movie,
I can't marry her.
No, you can't.
Wait, where are the boys? I
thought this was a group thing.
Yeah, I lied.
They're not coming
and I'm about to leave.
Why?
Because...
they're not in love with Robin,
and neither am I.
I mean, she's great and sweet.
I'm not going to pretend
that I haven't noticed her body,
but this is off topic.
Good luck.
Wait, wait, I
can't do this.
She'll never take
me seriously.
She thinks I'm some
womanizing idiot.
Hey.
We both know
you're more than that.
Okay, just show Robin the
Barney I met the other day.
You mean the insecure,
touchy-feely she-male
who sounded alarmingly
close to Ted?
Hey, Ted hit that
for over a year.
Wish me luck.
I just thought it'd be fun
to watch a movie tonight,
and since you've
never seen Star Wars,
I figured why not?
No big deal.
It's pretty good.
Sounds like a plan.
Hmm.
(Star Wars theme playing)
Hey, I'm just gonna
grab a beer.
You want one?
(clearing throat):
Um...
the movie's already
started, so...
Yeah, it's just
some words flying through space.
I mean, I'm not going
to read that anyway.
(high-pitched):
Oh, my God.
Off to a bad start.
What are you doing
down there?
I'm making sure my best friend
is marrying the right woman.
That's what I'm doing.
Dude, what the hell are you
doing, hiding behind the couch?
You need to get a job.
I really do, don't I?
Yeah.
So, Robin...
tell me about your day,
and not just what happened,
how you felt
about what happened.
What?
I'm not looking
to problem-solve,
I'm just looking to listen.
(chuckles)
Why are you acting like this?
Like what?
You're being super nice.
It's freaking me out.
Be gross, be inappropriate.
Be Barney.
Uh,
I'm being Barney,
and I think
tonight's going to be
de-- wait for it-- lightful.
Delightful.
Right.
Hey, um, so I went
to the chiropractor yesterday.
That guy bent me over the table
and pounded me for a good hour.
Is insurance going
to cover that?
Sometimes they don't.
That's it?
Okay.
Well, um,
today I was at the dentist.
That guy drilled me
all day long.
He drilled me hard.
He filled all of my cavities.
Come on, man.
Well, your teeth
look fantastic.
Who are you?
(Star Wars theme playing)
What?
Nothing.
You were staring
at me.
You look really
beautiful tonight.
Mmm.
You don't look
so bad yourself, mister.
Yeah, great scene,
great scene.
Star Wars fun fact
number seven--
George Lucas based
the film's structure
on Akira Kurosawa's
The Hidden Fortress.
Uh, he also owes a debt
to Joseph Campbell's work
with comparative mythology.
Yeah, Ted,
I'm losing wood over here.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Wait, it's really important
to you
that I like this movie,
isn't it?
(scoffing)
No.
Well,
I'm not gonna like it with you
staring at me the whole time.
Go to your room and I will
come get you when it's over.
Stella.
Go.
Should I leave, too?
(screams)
What part,
what part, what part?
Thanks.
Nothing?
Not even
a glance?
I mean, even I was thinking
about rocking a motorboat
on those bad boys.
What the hell
is wrong
with you, Barney?
I don't always want
to be that guy.
Sometimes I want to be
someone you can have
an actual conversation with.
Now,
tell me something about you
that I don't know yet.
Seriously.
Okay.
Um... there's a job opening
at a new cable network
that would be perfect for me--
completely legit
world news, interviews
with people who matter--
uh, but I decided
I'm not going to apply.
Why not?
Because I'm a joke.
I'm just
the scary news lady from
some stupid local news channel.
Hey, we both know
you're more than that.
Promise me you'll apply.
Barney, it's not as easy...
Okay.
I promise.
(Star Wars background music
playing)
Okay, she's up
to the scene
where Luke, Leia,
Han and Chewy escape
from the Death Star's
trash compactor.
Great scene.
Okay, we should
have just heard...
(gasps, yelps)
(cathartic laugh)
(sigh of relief)
...but Stella
didn't make a peep.
I'm gonna take a look.
All right.
* *
She's not even watching.
She's texting.
I'll tell her
you still want to be friends.
I don't believe this.
I don't believe this; she knows
this is important to me.
She's blatantly...
(phone chimes)
"Stop watching me, jackasses."
To taking chances.
(clinking)
Thank you.
You know, Robin, there's
actually something I,
I do want to talk
to you about.
Last call.
Of course it is.
One more for the road?
Yeah, why not?
Hold that thought?
I will.
I loved it.
Yes!
Yes, I am marrying a woman
who is not only hot
but loves Star Wars.
That's the dream.
Yes!
What was that?
I was high-fiving
15-Year-Old Me
through the space-
time continuum.
We did it.
(laughing):
We did it, you masturbating
little bastard.
Champagne for everybody.
(sighs)
It was so good.
You hated it, didn't you?
Ugh, it's so stupid.
I mean, first of all, how do
they understand that walking...
bear they hang around
with all the time?
Wookiee.
Yeah, he goes...
(weird growling)
And they're all like,
"That's a good point, Bear,
let's try that."
Okay, he's a Wookiee,
and his kind is actually
more intelligent
than they appear.
Look, Stella,
that is Ted's favorite movie
of all time.
He watches it
when he's home
sick with the flu.
He watches it on rainy
Sunday afternoons in the fall.
He... he watches it
on Christmas Eve.
Ted watches Star Wars
in sickness and in health,
in good times and in bad.
Do you really think
that you can pretend
to like a movie
that you actually hate
for the rest of your life?
I do.
Well, then, Ted's a lucky guy.
(scoffs)
Bear.
Hey.
So, here's the deal.
April, have...
you met Barney?
Hi, Barney.
Uh, hello.
April just finished
her shift,
and she's looking
to blow off some steam.
Ha.
Hmm.
Would you excuse
us for one sec?
What are you doing?
Well, you were
so nice to me tonight,
I wanted to return the favor,
wingwoman-style.
So, as I was saying,
April, Barney...
is the Yankees'
new second-baseman.
And Barney,
April asked
if tomorrow, you could
hit a goal for her
during the
baseball match.
You can't make
this stuff up.
So, you two kids have fun.
(chuckles)
So are you, uh,
nervous about the game?
Yeah, I'm nervous
for the other team
'cause when I step
up to that plate...
(chuckles)
Look, April, I am not
a New York Yankee.
Any other night,
I would probably
try to convince you
that I am, but I'm not.
I'm just some guy
who's in love with the
girl that just left,
and she's never going
to feel the same way.
So I'm just going to go.
And that was it.
I'm so sorry, Barney.
But you can't give up.
You know,
it may take some time,
but once Robin really sees
the new you...
Barney, um,
when my family gets
to Yankee Stadium,
are the tickets
under your name or mine?
My name, and tell your
nephews to bring their mitts.
They're going to be
in foul ball country.
(chuckles)
(laughing):
Come on.
Okay, well, the Robin stuff
was completely true.
Ow!
Damn it, Barney.
I mean, for the last time,
you can't, you can't
be in love with Robin
and still be sleeping with
every bimbo on the planet.
You have to choose right now.
I choose bimbos.
What?!
Hey, Lily, bimbos
make me happy.
Bimbos make me
feel alive.
Bimbos make me want to
pretend to be a better man.
This whole thing with
Robin was just a fling,
but at the end of the day,
my heart belongs to bimbos.
No, no, this is just
a defense mechanism
because you're afraid
of getting hurt.
You're just confused.
Oh, I'm not
confused, Lily.
You know who is confused?
Bimbos.
They're easily confused.
It's one of the
thousand little things
I love about them.
I love their vacant,
trusting stares;
their sluggish,
unencumbered minds;
their unresolved daddy issues.
I love them, Lily,
and they love me.
Bimbos
have always
been there for me,
through thick and thin.
Mostly thin.
B-man don't do thick crust.
What up?
See you, Barney.
Oh...
(door closes)
(sighs)
www.tvsubtitles.net