Kids, in the fall of 2008,
I had a little problem.
All right, I got
to get to Stella's.
Tonight's the night, guys.
I've tried it before,
I've failed every time.
This time, I am gonna do it.
Tonight...
I pick up a lesbian.
Robin, I need your lipstick.
Oh, man!
Take pictures, all right?
Spicy.
I lived in New York,
but Stella lived across
the river in New Jersey...
Oh, man!
...which meant I was always
taking the train.
What's up, Ted?
Hey, Matisse.
Hey, T-Diddy!
Theodore!
- You missed it.
- Robin got that national anchor job.
And we got a free
bottle of champagne.
Ah, but it's empty now.
Oh, man!
And as result, it seemed like
I was missing out
on everything.
Sorry, we couldn't wait.
It was getting cold.
Oh, man!
Hey, big guy.
What's up, G?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just...
you know, I want to hang out
with you guys.
I want to hang out
with my friends.
I just feel like I'm spending
all my tim the train.
Okay, how about this,
why don't you ask your friends
to come out here sometime?
That's a great idea.
You want us to go
to New Jersey?
Oh, that is rich.
Why?
Well, for starters,
I don't have any of
my gold medallions anymore.
I sold them when they went
out of style 400 years ago.
Lily?
Oh, sorry, Ted.
I'm a born and raised
New Yorker.
I'm programmed to
despise and loathe
New Jersey and all
that it stands for.
Why am I telling you this?
You hate New Jersey
more than anyone.
What?
I don't hate New Jersey.
Why would you think that?
And then he cut
in front of me.
God, I hate line cutters
more than I hate New Jersey.
Well, that's not true.
There's nothing I hate
more than New Jersey.
NO NEW JERSEY
I HATE NEW JERSEY
Right?
Hey, you want
to wait for you?
No, I might be a while.
I got a drop a massive
New Jersey.
Okay,
so New Jersey's
not my favorite place.
But once Stella
and I get married
and she and Lucy
move in with me,
I'll never set foot
in New Jersey again.
Unless I'm going to see
a Giants game or flying out of Newark
or God forbid,
disposing of a body.
Ted, if you murder me and
bury me in New Jersey,
I'll haunt you forever.
But if I murder you and
bury you somewhere else?
Eh, I'll leave you alone.
I'm sure you had
your reasons.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
HOW I MET YOUR MOTHER 403
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:我爱狮心小s
METRO NEWS ONE AT 11:00
Kids, your Aunt Robin was sick
of her jobt Metro News One.
She was sick of the low
production value...
I'm Robin Scherbatsky,
and you're watching...
Etro News One at 11:00.
And again at 1:00.
...sick of the stories
she had to report...
So hurry up and get your votes in
for New York's cutest doggie.
...and most of all,
she was sick of
all the stupid puns.
Four transit workers
were electrocuted
when a subway train
jumped the tracks.
Stay tuned for the...
shocking derails.
Joel, people died.
So when the call came in
that she got
the big national anchor job,
she finally got to say
the words
she'd been dreaming of saying
for years...
Tonight will be
my last broadcast.
I came to Metro News One
as a little caterpillar.
And for four years,
this desk has been my cocoon.
But tonight,
I emerge an ambitious butterfly.
Why does she sound
like an idiot?
- Did she have a stroke?
- Yeah.
A stroke of genius.
This speech is really good.
With one eye on the horizon,
one eye on the truth,
and one eye on all of you.
You wrote it for her,
didn't you?
It's a modified version
of the speech I gave
when I had to leave
the swim team
because of a chronic
inner ear situation.
I thought you were
the towel boy.
It's part of the team.
So that Saturday
as Robin went off
for her first day
at her new job,
we all headed across the river
to experience some of that
crazy New Jersey nightlife.
Okay, Stella couldn't
find a sitter,
so we can't go out.
Instead...
we're all gonna hang out here and it's gonna
be just as awesome.
Right, we got board games,
we got movies.
And I think there may be
some beer out in the garage.
Ted, this is pathetic.
It's Saturday night.
We should be out at a bar.
drinking alcohol.
Now I know that
that sounds depressing,
- bordering on tragic, but it's just a fact.
- Yeah,
and I want another crack
at that chick, Doris.
I know I can land
that lesbian plane.
No snakes on that plane.
Okay, guys.
Come on, you promised.
Let's just hang out here,
try to have fun.
I mean, we're all together,friends hanging out.
Isn't that what really matters?
Okay, if we take the next train,
we can be at MacLaren's
by 11:00.
We can be there
by 10:00.
No, I have
to change first.
I am not walking into MacLaren's
smelling like New Jersey.
You guys really
hate it here, huh?
What?! No!
Stels...
I get it, I mean, you guys
are all New Yorkers.
You need to go
hang out at a bar.
Well, you could just hang out at the coolest
bar in the state,
which is so close
it will blow your mind.
And boom goes the dynamite.
The coolest bar in New Jersey.
Yeah, it probably is.
This is great!
We got darts.
Half a ping-pong table.
A fish bowl.
Look what turned out to be
an awesome night as promised.
Maybe we can drop some Bac-O's in here
and make them fight.
No, thanks.
I don't mess with fish bowls
unless they have my two favorite fish--
the sucker fish
and the blow fish.
What up!
For "blow fish"?
I don't think so.
Marshall.
You're better than that.
Lily.
Not good enough.
Stella?
Sorry.
I am not lowering this until
someone gives me the respect
of another person's knuckles
tapping against mine in a light but decisive manner.
Pretty, pretty...
Pretty... Who's a pretty baby?
Then know this...
until it gets
what it wants,
nay, deserves,
this fist will not yield.
It.
Will. Not. Yield.
So who wants to play Scrabble?
Sure, whatever.
Oh, heads up,
the "X" tile is
a little hard to read because a couple years ago,
it went all the way
through my dog.
You know, maybe we should get
a dog again when you move in.
When I what?
Oh, great.
There's Robin.
I thought they were
moving in with you.
So did I.
Oh, God, am I moving
to New Jersey?
Hey, guys,
I bet that dog was
really flying high after it swallowed a little "X."
Nailed it!
Come on!
I can't live here.
It wouldn't be that bad.
You could put a mini-
fridge over there
and maybe some
knock hockey.
Knock hockey.
Nice one, Big Mon.
I meant New Jersey
in general,
not this basement.
She wants me to move here?
I don't get it.
We discussed this months ago.
So I was thinking
after the wedding,
you and Lucy
could move in here.
Yeah, she could play out
on the fire escape,
maybe make friends
with that guy
who sleeps on that
couch in the alley,
ride her bike up
and down Broadway.
It's a great idea, Ted.
I don't understand why you'd
want to live in New Jersey
when you have a chance
to live in Manhattan?
I thought having a rent-controlled apartment
on the Upper West Side
was half the reason
she agreed to marry me.
Really, I thought it was
the whole reason.
What is up?!
Robin, hey!
Looking good.
Bump the Barnacle.
Stella already
told me not to.
How was your first day?
- It wasn't.
- What?
It wasn't my first day.
I showed up and there
were 20 other people.
It turns out, I didn't
actually get the job.
I only got an audition.
What, how did
that happen?
I don't know.
Because he told me
that I got it.
I got it?!
I got it!
And just to be clear,
when I say "you got it,"
I mean an audition.
You got an audition.
I don't want there to be
any confusion.
You have an audition only.
Not the job.
Thank you!
Okay, I'm going to call
- and beg Joel to give
me my job back.
- No!
You hated that job.
I don't know,
it wasn't so bad.
Robin, what did they make you call Tropical Storm Hector
when it was raining
cats and dogs?
A furricane.
Hey, Ted.
Rock me like a furricane.
Thanks.
Mean.
Okay, yeah, it sucks,
but what can I do?
I mean, I'm not going to get
that other job.
You guys should have seen the other women
at this audition.
They all had more experience than me,
were more ethnic than me.
There was an African-American
chick with blue eyes,
how can I compete with that?
Mm, you can't.
No, you can
compete with anyone.
You're Robin Scherbatsky.
Confident. Strong. Tall.
With crazy long legs
that look great in shorts.
I'm calling Joel.
No, Robin, if you call him right now,
you will hate yourself.
Look, I have slept
with lots of women
who afterwards told me off
and stormed out.
And sometimes they'd pick up the phone
and they'd call me and then we'd hook up again.
And when we were finished,
I could see that look
on their faces,
that look that says
they hate themselves
and they wish
they'd never called.
But if you could
see that look...
Actually, you can see that look,
there's a video.
www-dot...
No! Stop, okay?
I won't call.
Don't drink the beer!
I just remembered
when I bought it.
It was right before
I got pregnant with Lucy.
Ted, would you mind running
to PriceCo and picking some up?
Oh, and while
you're there,
maybe you could sign up
for a card.
I mean, you'll probably end up
going there all the time.
That's the look.
PRICE CO. SUPERSTORE
I can't move here.
I hate it here.
I would kill myself.
Maybe New Jersey's
not that bad.
Stella has a lawn.
You could get
a riding lawn mower.
They sell them over there.
I saw one with a cup holder.
I saw a recliner with
a built-in cup holder.
I even saw a hammock
with a cup holder.
You live in New Jersey,
you never have
to hold a cup again.
I don't think I have
as big a problem holdcups as you do.
I will give you $100
to fist pump me.
$200.
Just put it down, Barney.
Your arm must be
killing you by now.
$10,000.
Look, you'll be
right across the river.
You'll be in New York
all the time.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Um, excuse me.
You guys are from New York,
right?
Yeah, we moved here
from Manhattan.
Do you ever get into the city?
All the time.
See? All the time.
When was the last time
you were there?
We just had dinner
at O'Rourke's.
That's been closed
for six year
It has been awhile.
Funny, we don't miss it.
Well, I guess we're
New Jersey-ians now.
Honey, look,
dog shirts.
I can't do it.
I'm just going to tell Stella
she and Lucy have to move
into the city and that's that.
Okay, what do
you guys think?
Beagle or Boston terrier?
Are those tears?
They're awesome...
manly pain tears.
They're not emotional.
Okay, they're a little
bit emotional.
Where's Robin?
Oh, no.
Hey, Shirley,
it's Robin calling for Joel.
Robin, hang up the phone.
Don't do this.
Sorry, I know, okay?
- If you don't hang up right now...
- Shh. Stop.
Hey, Joel, it's Robin.
So Madam Butterfly wants
to come back to the cocoon.
Yeah, look, I'm sorry
I said all that stuff.
Well, you can stick your sorries
in your sock drawer,
'cause you've
already been replaced.
I've got Brian in makeup
and he couldn't be more excited.
I can't do this.
Uh, okay, look, as much as
I want to see college boy here
wet himself on camera,
if you can get here in time
to read the 11:00 news,
you can have
your old job back.
Okay, I have a half hour
to make it to the studio.
There's no way you can make it to the city
in a half hour.
Robin, don't do this.
I know it's scary
to bet on yourself,
but if you don't,
nobody else will.
And I'm not just saying
that to get a fist bump.
Although, come on, a fist bump would
be great.
But I really mean it.
I am betting on myself.
I am betting that i can make it there
by 11:00.
- Hey, did you get the beer?
- Yeah, I got 144-pack.
The rest is in the trunk.
And did you sign up
for the membership?
No.
Why not?
There was a line
for the photos...
my hair's a mess...
I don't want to move
to New Jersey.
What?
I can't do it.
And I can't see any reason why you and Lucy
shouldn't move to New York.
Well, my daughter goes
to school here.
All of her friends are her I've lived here
my whole life.
My whole family
is here.
This is
my house.
I'm on the PTA.
And as of June 1,
I'm the deputy mayor.
Yes, but my apartment is
really close to the subway.
Ted, we're not moving,
end of discussion.
How can it be end of discussion if there's never been
a discussion?
This is part
of being a parent.
I can't just uproot Lucy.
People with kids
move all the time.
I think it would be really great for Lucy
to grow up in the greatest
city in the world.
Oh, here we go--
New York's the greatest city
in the whole wide world.
It's where dreams come true and pigeon poop
tastes like tapioca.
Want to know
a little secret, Ted?
New Jersey is better
than New York.
Better than...?
You think...? I...
The Empire State Buil...
H and H Bage...
Lincoln Ce...
Zabar's...
Papaya King.
New York is the intellectual and cultural
hub of the planet.
New York is full of weirdoes,
and snobs and mean people.
Ted, do you know that
once, an old lady
actually called me a bitch
and threw a cat in my face?
And you want to know if
that happened in New Jersey?
Uh-uh, 86th and Lex,
right in front of your
beloved little Papaya King.
Ted, people are nice
in New Jersey.
I mean it's the kind of place
where you know your neighbors.
Hey, I know my neighbors.
Oh, yeah? Like who?
Right across the hall,
I got...
Clax... pa... mon...
- Claxpamon?
- His name is Paxton.
Love that dude.
Sorry, in a hurry.
Got to get to the front.
Got to get off first.
Whoa, don't run over Matisse.
Okay, so this is crazy.
You can't actually think that New Jersey
is better than New York.
New York has Broadway.
We win right there.
Oh, no, she did not.
Knuckle up for safety.
We have Atlantic City.
Can't beat the A.C.
Pretty please?
No one has to know.
New York has
Greenwich Village.
New Jersey has The Shore.
Woody Allen.
Oscar-winning chronicler
of urban neuroses.
Bump it!
- Bruce Springsteen.
- Sinatra.
He's from Hoboken...
New Jersey.
Yeah, but what city
is he singing about?
It's not "Secaucus, Secaucus."
Come on...
Now you kids can either
believe this or not,
but this is how your Aunt Robin
swears it happened.
Look, Stella, I understand
that coming from New Jersey
you don't picture
yourself loving New York,
but trust me, Marshall
didn't expect to,
and now he wouldn't think
of living anywhere else.
I hate New York!
I'm sorry, but it's true.
Okay, today I was walking
around PriceCo.
Have you ever been there?
It's huge.
All the stores in New York
are so cramped.
Every time I turn,
I knock something over.
I'm like some huge monster
that came out of the ocean to destroy bodegas.
But, Marshall,
you love New York.
Yeah, I do,
except that I hate it.
I'm too big
for New York, okay?
I'm always trying to fit into
cramped little subway seats
or duck under doorways
that were built 150 years ago.
Hey, guess what?
People are bigger now.
Build bigger doorways. What the
hell is the matter with you?
Small city, big man--
give it up.
And it's so loud,
all the time.
Yes, it's the city
that never sleeps.
Well, guess what,
I like to sleep.
I've been tired
for eight years.
Tired and scared with black
and blue marks on my elbows
from trying to fit through
all these tiny elf doorways.
New Jersey's great.
It's got
huge stores,
and lawns and you never have
to carry a cup again.
Not for the rest
of your life.
I'm not afraid
to say it--
I love New Jersey.
I'm just kidding.
Look, Stella...
I get it, okay?
I see what
you're saying.
I guess...
we could live in Brooklyn.
You know what, Ted...
live wherever you want.
I don't care.
Awkward silence. Tap it.
Oh, hey, Lucy.
What are you doing up?
There was some loud noises
in the basement.
Sorry about that. Why don't
you got back to bed, sweetie.
I can't go to sleep
without a story.
Okay, I'll just get your mom...
Why don't you
read it to me?
Okay, come on.
I'm moving here.
Really?
Really.
New Jersey wins.
Oh! Oh, thank you!
Wait...
METRO NEWS 1
Good evening, New York.
Hey, look, she made it.
Our top story night--
the newborn panda at the Central Park Zoo
got its first tooth today.
I guess that makes her a...
molar bear.
Molar bear.
You know what?
I really am done.
Good night, New York.
Wow, she really quit.
You think we had
anything to do with that?
Yeah, I think we did.
Nice job, Barney.
Oh, my God!
Thank you!
Oh, that was
killing my arm.
My arm hasn't been this sore
since I was 13 years old
and figured out how
to lock a bathroom.
Up top.
Oh, no.
- Hey.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Well, I officially
didn't get that job.
- Aw.
- I'm so sorry.
That's okay.
They, um, they offered
me another one.
Hey, that's great.
What are you going
to be doing?
Foreign correspondent.
I'm, uh...
moving to Japan.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
www.tvsubtitles.net