I remember one time we all gathered
at my apartment to watch the Super Bowl.
Well, not all of us.
Welcome back
to Super Bowl XLIV in Miami.
Get a load of that guy.
You think that's his real number?
- Well, that explains where Barney is.
- Dibs on his wings.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, -Titou-
www.sous-titres.eu
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Does anyone know
who won the Super Bowl?
- You were there. It was the...
- I won,
because I am now
in possession of a magic phone
that always rings.
And do you know who's always
usually on the other end?
A chick.
So how many chicks
do I have calling me now?
Infinity.
- You guys remember Ranjit.
- Hello.
Ranjit, good to see you.
I've enlisted Ranjit's services
as my personal driver
because for the next week,
I'll be sleeping with hundreds of women,
and I don't want to take the subway,
'cause you know, germs.
You're actually gonna hook up
with these girls that call you?
Indubitably.
I'm meeting the first one here.
Keep your eyes peeled for a red sweater.
Based on her texts, she's dirty,
dyslexic, and wants to 96 me.
Semicolon, end parentheses.
This ought to be good. I can only
imagine the quality of girl that...
You are the guy from the Super Bowl.
Magic phone, guys, magic phone.
- Hey, guys, hey, Ranjit.
- How's it going?
- That beer looks a little flat.
- It's Scotch.
Something troubling you, kiddo?
Don was Aunt Robin's co-host
on her morning show.
Now, even though her show
was on so early that no one watched,
Aunt Robin was a consummate
professional,
but Don was not.
But that morning,
Don had gone too far.
Now, that's what I call having
a "woof" over your head.
Why is Ulee's Gold
in every crossword?
It's me? Sorry, sorry.
Next Sunday is Valentine's Day,
and one lucky patient
will be receiving
a very special chocolate heart,
a human heart.
That reminds me.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Do you have any,
Valentine's Day plans?
He asked you out?
- He asked me out.
- That's crazy.
And they use "Ulee"
'cause of the vowels.
What did you say?
We were on the air,
I was on the spot, so I said okay.
Robin, you are going to marry
this guy so freaking hard.
Right in the butt.
What?! No, I hate Don,
and now I can't cancel because I said
I would go out with him on the air.
What would your viewer think?
You said you'd go out with him
on Valentine's? I thought we had plans.
Getting drunk
and cleaning the apartment was a plan?
I did not
say it was a good plan.
Guys, guys, guys, we're on me now,
and it is getting interesting.
Look at these texts. Read this one.
Now, look at this one.
Does she text
her mother with those fingers?
Now, look at this one.
Or this one,
or this one.
Buddy, how about you do this?
Go nail that girl,
then read your texts.
I can't do that.
I just can't hook up with a girl
if there is a hotter girl out there
with whom up can be hooked.
Isn't there always a hotter girl?
I know.
Isn't it wonderful?
Go for Barney.
Cut to the chase, what's your cup size?
Hi, Mom.
There's always a hotter girl.
Isn't that the problem in a nutshell?
There's too many options,
you got Internet dating, you got bars...
Holding up your phone number
on national TV.
I never had that problem.
When I was 18,
I had an arranged marriage,
and I love my wife
more and more every day.
It is true. It's, it's very rare
that two people just meet
and fall madly in love,
like Robin and Don.
We're not even, like,
going out for dinner.
We're just hanging out at his place.
It's not like that. It's just us
and a bunch of other people.
Wait, Robin, what exactly did
Don say when he asked you out?
I'm having some friends
for a little party. You should
come by if you want.
Robin, Don didn't ask you out.
- Of course he asked me out.
- No, he didn't.
Yes, he did.
He did.
He did, he did!
Well, dog my cats.
I think I know what's going on here.
Did you want Don to ask you out?
What?!
No, I hate Don.
I can't stop thinking
about how much I hate him.
It's like, it's like all the time.
I just want to attack him
and rip his stupid clothes off,
just spank him with his little paddle
until his bum's all red.
Shut up!
See? That right there
is what free will gets you...
Constant, ego-shattering
uncertainty.
I'm done with that.
I want what Ranjit has.
I've spent my entire adult life
looking for the perfect woman,
and I'm spending Valentine's Day
scrubbing the toilet.
I need someone else
to find me that woman.
Arranged marriage me.
Or this one or this one or this one.
You want us
to arrange your marriage?
Absolutely.
There's two sides to dating, right?
Picking and getting picked.
Getting picked I'm good at.
Ladies love Teddy West Side.
You're waiting for me to comment
on your self-assigned nickname.
Here's my comment.
- I love it.
- Really?
Teddy West Side, continue.
It's the picking I suck at.
I pick the wrong girls.
But you're the best pickers I know.
You picked each other.
With a slight assist
from the Wesleyan Housing Department.
And a healthy splash
of Drakkar Noir.
Get out there, find me a girl.
We'll double-date on Valentine's Day.
If I like her, I will marry her...
if she's cool with it,
and she will be...
Cause I'll wear my nice blazer.
I love that blazer
almost as much as Robin loves Don.
I do not love Don.
Neurologically speaking,
the part of the human brain
that makes you hate people
is located right next
to the part of the brain
that makes you want to jump them.
The two responses are so similar,
it's hard to tell them apart.
You know what it's like?
I have to get a book.
Give me 30 seconds!
This is fun.
Look at this picture.
It's a rabbit.
You can look at it for hours
and be absolutely sure
it's a rabbit,
but then one day you look at it
and you realize... wait a second...
it's a duck.
A rabbit, a duck.
Isn't this fun?
It sure was.
Relationships are like that.
When you first met Don,
you hated him.
You thought, "This guy is a duck",
but one of these days,
you're going to realize,
"This is actually something I love.
"He's a rabbit."
You got it backwards there.
The duck is the thing you love,
the rabbit is the thing you hate.
I gotta agree;
ducks up, rabbits down.
Definitely.
Ducks are better than rabbits.
Ducks are...
Rabbits are adorable!
Ducks are, like...
Have you ever been
in a fight with a duck?
I mean, ducks are jerks!
This led to one of the most
intense arguments
our group has ever had.
Duck is delicious!
Rabbit is all gamey!
We're not talking about flavor!
Flavor counts!
Who carries around a duck's foot
for good luck! Anyone!
You wrap yourself
in a comforter stuffed with rabbit hair!
I'll wrap myself in one
stuffed with duck feathers!
Who's cozier?
But who's cozier?!
Hold on! I have to get another book!
Why don't we take a rabbit, a duck,
stick 'em in a cardboard box,
and let them fight it out?!
Because it's illegal, Ted!
Only if we bet on it, Marshall!
Fine!
I concede!
You win!
Say it.
You have to say it.
Ducks good...
rabbits are bad.
Thank you. And Don is...
And always will be... a rabbit.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Think about it. Don?
Donald?
Donald...
Duck?
And what, I wonder,
does Donald Duck never wear?
- Pants.
Don's a duck.
- Can I say "lawyered"?
- I'll allow it.
Yes, kids, sometimes
there's a fine line
between love and hate.
Case in point:
There is no place
I would rather be...
and no one I'd rather be with.
I should get that.
Go for Barney.
I'm sort of in the middle of someone...
something right now, and I...
You're a hot lady bullfighter?
You gotta go.
MacLaren's Pub.
There is no place I would rather be
and no one I would rather be...
Would you excuse me for one moment?
Go for Barney.
You're a gold medalist
Japanese figure skater?
Adios, muchacha!
No place I'd rather be,
no one I'd rather...
For Pete's sake!
You're a hot chick?
Sayonara!
I realize that you're very busy,
so I'll just get straight
to the point.
Shakah!
And that's my bad leg.
Very bad.
Are you okay?
Of course.
Why wouldn't I be?
Go for Barney.
Barney had been sure
that phone was something he loved,
but now,
he realized it wasn't that at all.
It was something else entirely.
I'm free.
Now this feels right.
There is no place I would rather be.
And no one I would rather be...
What's wrong?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
Go for Barney.
D cups?
Really?
Finally Valentine's Day arrived,
the deadline for Marshall and Lily
to find me a wife.
An important job they had,
well, forgotten to do.
Aren't we go
on a double date with Ted.
Ted?
No, he's not seeing anyone.
Remember he asked us to find a...
Want to get married?
I don't know what kind of architect!
Houses, buildings, that kind of crap.
Want to marry my friend Ted?
What, you can be choosy?
You're in a bar on Valentine's Day!
Just real quick...
You want to marry my friend Ted?
Man, Ted's right.
It's tough out there.
This is stupid.
You know what? We forgot about this.
I'm sure Ted did, also.
Here comes the groom,
in his favorite blazer,
gonna meet my wife and I...
Blazer, Tazer.
Gazer, Ta... Bazer?
Before you go meet your future wife,
why don't you come
to Don's party with me?
You're wearing this?
Why?
He's a duck.
That dude be straight duckin'.
And I think that I'll amaze her.
Nailed it!
So we went to Don's party.
I don't want to crowd you
on your little date here,
- so if things start to get hot...
- They're not gonna get hot...
I'm just saying, if they do,
I'll just say,
"Well, I got a dinner rez", and then...
It's the best part.
I've been working on this for a while.
I'll duck out.
It's not gonna happen.
But do that.
Well, I got a dinner rez.
Don, what the hell are you doing?
It's something called The Naked Man.
I read about it on some guy's blog.
I'm so stupid.
Why did I think
it would work on you?
'cause I would never...
Could, like... standards,
so, you know.
I thought this was a party.
I said that to get you to come.
I didn't think you'd bring a date.
Ted's not my date.
He's a friend.
You think
I'm some kind of playboy now.
You could say that.
So he's a rabbit.
At least you know for sure.
This may hurt a little.
I'm recycling
your old Architecture Weekly Magazines.
- What are you doing?
- Cleaning.
You go on your date.
Happy Valentine's Day.
You're here.
I've been thinking.
Maybe we should call this off.
- We got her.
- What?
We got her.
It's crazy.
We were searching all week,
and then, a couple hours ago...
Trudy?
Married.
- Blah, blah?
- Committed.
- Relationship?
- Bellevue.
Natalie?
Ted's her least favorite person
in the world.
Well, she's not getting any younger.
Get rid of it!
- What?
- This phone is cursed.
Cursed, I tell you!
I try to ignore it,
but it just never stops ringing!
It's ruining my life!
I should get that.
Please!
Let me answer it.
It could be an emergency.
She could be trapped in a giant bra!
Let it go... to voice mail.
We have to find a wife.
We're being too choosy.
It doesn't matter who it is.
It's a phone girl?
I know, but no.
Then we met her, and Ted,
she's a world-class violinist,
she's a gourmet cook, and...
she can quote
every line from Caddyshack.
"And what brings you
to this nape of the woods?"
"Neck of the wape?"
Why are you here?
So we all had dinner.
And kids, Lily ans Marshall's hard work
had paid off,
because that girl was terrific.
In fact...
But Natalia, tell Ted the problem.
Tell him!
Unfortunately, I'm going to have
to leave the country soon
because my visa is about to expire.
She needs to get married!
Federal law expressly dictates
that a foreign national
can't maintain residency for longer
than six months without a work visa.
But when it came down...
And you, sir?
The rabbit or the duck?
What?
It's a prix-fixe menu,
we're out of steak, fish and chicken.
So, rabbit or duck?
Rabbit.
Sorry, guys.
I got to go.
Why would Ted order rabbit
if he was gonna run out?
I need it back!
Where's the phone?
I met you already.
It's hidden.
Where?
Where had Lily hidden the phone?
To answer that question,
we have to back up a little bit.
You go on your date.
Happy Valentine's Day.
It's Barney's phone.
I wonder how it got in there.
Come on.
Big date.
What's the harm?
And just like that, I was hooked.
Terrific, I will see you there.
I'll be the guy in the awesome blazer.
I think you'll know the blazer
when you see it.
I gotta go.
You're here.
So... rabbit or duck?
Rabbit.
Sorry, guys.
I gotta go.
Sorry, babe.
I gotta take this.
Barney's phone.
- Teddy West Side speaking.
- It's my phone!
I am taking it back!
And I'm taking your cool nickname, too!
Barney West Side speaking.
I love it so much!
It just keeps ringing.
Give it to me.
Being single sucks.
It turns you into a crazy person.
I know.
So much running around and freaking out,
and for what?
It's all so you can find someone
you can sit on a couch
and put off cleaning
the bathroom with.
The joke's on the rest of the world,
because we can do that on our own.
Exactly.
- I have to apologize...
- Just save it. Let's do the news.
No, listen.
After you left the other night,
I was embarrassed.
Not because I was naked.
I'm actually okay with my body.
Clearly.
I got married in college.
I just got divorced three months ago.
I have no idea how to be single.
But that's not why
I was embarrassed.
I was embarrassed about my behavior
right here at Channel...
It starts with a one.
12.
I mean, just look at your mug.
Right.
Well, no. You look at this mug.
You are a tremendous news anchor.
And you deserve a co-anchor
who gives a crap.
And from here on out,
that's gonna be me.
I'll believe that when I see it.
You'll see it right now.
I'll go get you coffee.
You're wearing pants.
Well, look at that.
Duck.
www.tvsubtitles.net