y of my stories
I'm a starry-eyed romantic
on a noble search
for true love.
In this one, I'm just a jerk.
Well, guys,
tonight is the night.
to see my antique
camera collection.
Ah!
It's Ted's bait.
"Bait"?
A true gentleman
invents a pretense
to lure an honorable lady
into his apartment.
Some item of interest
or beauty you can both
pretend to admire
for five minutes
before she hops
on your disco stick.
Like she's coming up
to "borrow a book"
or "check out an album
on vinyl."
Or to see your
new rap poster.
"Rap poster"?
Who would that work on?
It was the first
week of college.
I was really
into Wu-Tang Clan.
Yeah, bait is tricky.
It has to be something interesting
enough to get the girl upstairs,
but not so interesting
that it overpowers the night.
BARNEY: I found that a
slot machine was too fun.
(coins clinking)
(yelling)
And a trampoline...
turned out to be too dangerous.
But then I found
the perfect bait:
a teacup pig.
"A teacup pig"?
Who's that working on?
You have a teacup pig?! I
didn't know you had a teacup pig!
Can we see the teacup pig?!
Hey, can I borrow
your teacup pig?
Yes, you can borrow
my teacup pig.
You have a teacup pig?!
Oh, my gosh!
I can't believe
you have a teacup pig!
You're just so cute!
Yes, you are the cutest
piggy ever!
What?
Were you always this pretty?
Or are you going
to give me that whole,
"Oh, in high school I was
really shy and awkward" line?
I was shy and awkward.
I was, like,
a hundred pounds heavier
and I had these crazy
buck teeth. Seriously?
No, I've always been hot.
What are you going to do?
(chuckles)
Do you know who else
would love this teacup pig?
Hmm?
My boyfriend.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
You have a boyfriend?
Ugh, I know.
So annoying, right?
I mean, he's
not really my boyfriend.
Oh, good.
I mean,
technically, he kind of is.
Well, is he or isn't he?
Some of both,
but definitely not either.
Are you getting any of this?
Look, I really like you.
I just need you
to be patient.
I don't want to lose you,
Big Brown Eyes.
Yup. Somebody doesn't
want to lose
Big Brown Eyes.
ROBIN:
Oh, Ted.
She's got you
on the hook.
What? What?
I'm not on the hook.
Oh, you are totally on the hook.
She's stringing
you along.
She's not
committing to you,
but she's keeping you
around just in case,
like an old can of chili
in the pantry.
Um, who's buying
canned chili
and not eating it
immediately? Amen, sister.
Ted, don't feel bad.
We've all been there.
I've been on both
sides of it.
I've been a hookey
and a hooker.
Move past it, guys.
I've been a little
bit loose,
but money never
changed hands.
I've been on the hook.
Lisa Walker.
Picture it:
1994, St. Cloud, Minnesota.
So I was, like,
thinking, Lisa-
do you maybe want to,
like, go out with me?
That sounds great.
But I'm sort
of seeing this guy.
He's got
a LeBaron convertible
and an "in"
at the roller rink,
so I'd hate
to burn that bridge.
I understand.
But how about this?
You can be
my secret boyfriend
who does all my
homework for me.
A'ight.
You want to see
my rap poster?
Poster whore.
MARSHALL:
Anyway...
Lisa Walker strung me
along for months
until one night,
I went to go tell her
how much I loved her.
BOTH: Aww. Hmm. Ugh.
In song.
(all groaning)
MARSHALL:
She wasn't home yet,
so I waited.
And waited.
I woke up four hours later,
covered in snow.
And that's when I saw it.
Lisa's footsteps.
She had walked right over me
and into the house.
It was the best thing
that could have happened.
It got me off her hook.
Okay, that is
definitely not
what's going on
with me and Tiffany.
Listen to this.
I'm really into you.
I just can't be
with you right now.
Huh?! Huh?!
Ted, "right no"
is the classic
on-the-hook catchphrase.
MARSHALL: Yup.
"Right now" paints a picture of
some sort of magical future time
when everything will work out,
but the truth is,
that will never happen.
BARNEY:
It's like this.
"I can't be with you." Boom!
"Right now."
(creaking)
LILY:
Yeah.
I think my high school
boyfriend, Scooter,
is still sort of
on the hook for me.
Sort of?
He totally is.
The poor guy showed up at our
wedding hoping to win you back.
LILY:
Yeah.
It's still sometimes weird
when I see him at work.
Wait. What?
Scooter works in
the school cafeteria.
We've talked about this.
Hey, Lily.
Nice dress.
Tater-tots?
(mouthing)
We most certainly have
not talked about this!
Yes, we have.
I've mentioned it
tons of times.
"Lunch Lady Scooter."
I thought that
you were referring
to some sort of long overdue
device that carries around
those poor,
underappreciated lunch ladies!
This explains a lot.
Lunch Lady Scooter
was there again today.
Oh, yeah? Did you
jump on that thing?
Give it a ride?
No!
Really? If it were me,
I'd be riding that scooter
all day long until I broke
that thang in half.
So those poor women still
have to walk everywhere?
Wait. Scooter is working
at your school?!
Are you jealous?
No, I just feel bad
for Scooter.
'Cause the only reason
he took that job
is he thinks
he has a shot with you.
You have to make it clear
that he doesn't,
so that he can move on
and a real lunch lady
can get her
job back. Damn!
I've tried.
Hey, Lily.
I saw you had seventh period
free. So do I.
You want to run away together?
Let me be clear, Scooter.
There is no way you and I
can ever be together.
Right now.
I'll see you tomorrow, Lily.
It's Tijuana Tuesday.
"Right now"?
You right-now'd Scooter?
You need to let Scooter
off the hook once and for all.
LILY:
You're right.
Day after tomorrow,
that's exactly what
I'm going to do.
Why not tomorrow?
Baby, I can't ruin
Tijuana Tuesday.
Really?
You're really going to sit here
all night watching the door
because Tiffany said
she'll "try to stop by"?
Barney, I'm not going
to just give up on her.
NARRATOR:
I should have given up on her.
This girl is special.
She was the devil.
Things are going
to work out with Tiffany.
No, they're not, dumbass.
Ted, let me be clear:
this girl is a poison
and you need to cut her
out of your life forever.
Hey, there she is.
Oh, she brought
some of her coworkers.
Hang on to this girl, Ted.
Hang on to her
and never let go!
these are some of the
hottest girls I've ever seen.
And they all work with Tiffany?
Yup.
There could only be
one explanation for this.
Ted...
is Tiffany a ph-ph-ph...
pharmaceutical sales rep?
Yeah, how did you know that?
And you never thought
to mention that?
What? It's just a job.
(stammers)
Just a j... just a jah...
Ted, throughout time
there has always been one
cutting-edge profession
to which hot girls,
like Tiffany, have flocked.
Shall I walk you
through the history?
I'm gonna explicitly say no.
It all started
2.5 million years ago.
BARNEY:
Man was a hunter.
So, the hottest
profession of the day?
Gatherer.
Homo erectus indeed.
As man mastered technology,
the hottest profession
of the day evolved.
I'm pretty sure
it's a hernia.
Can you check again?
And then,
man took to the skies.
And so, hot women
put on high heels
and became stewardesses.
I am in the upright
and locked position.
And then man said,
"Life is hard.
I should start taking
lotsf prescription drugs."
And so, hot girls
rolled into doctors' offices,
looking sexy enough to render
the very erection pills
they peddled
ironically redundant.
So now,
pharma girls are today's
hottest profession.
Hey, Big Brown Eyes.
How you doing?
I'm good.
Hey, by the way, you, uh,
you ditch that
loser boyfriend yet?
No, sir.
Touched my nose.
Dude, ditch Tiffany
and join the Barnacle
in a pharma girl free-for-all.
Side effects may include
loss of clothing, rug burn,
shortness of breath and sore
abdominals the next morning.
What in the world is up?!
Hey. So...
I know that you've
been having trouble
letting Scooter off the hook.
Well, I decided what you need
is practice.
Now, you say the problem
is his cute, sad eyes?
Well...
Aww!
All right, shut it, woman.
Now, I want you
to look at this
teacup pig and tell him
that there's no way
that you could ever be with him.
Teacup Pig, there is no way
I can ever be with you.
Right now.
Oh, come on!
Grow a pair!
I'm sorry, but he's
just so freakin' cute.
I just want to cuddle him
all day long.
Yes, I do.
You know that's funny.
I remember when you used to say
things like that about me.
Oh, I still do.
Yeah, not as much, Lily.
Not as much.
(laughs)
♪ Ain't no party like
a pharma girl party ♪
♪ 'Cause a pharma girl
party don't stop! ♪
Dude, I have already hooked
up with three of them.
Fantasmo.
Plus, my cholesterol
is down.
My restless legs
syndrome is cured.
I've never felt
more alive- oh.
Guys, great news.
Tiffany broke up
with her boyfriend.
Proof that I am
not on the hook.
Oh, you're still on the
hook. (Lily chuckles)
Ah, uh-uh, listen
to how we spent last night.
First, we cuddled.
Then, we shared chocolate cake.
Then, well, I don't usually
join in on locker room talk,
but I gave her
a pretty sensual foot rub.
And let me guess: it didn't
go any further than that.
Well, no, but...
And tell me,
did you by any chance
make that chocolate cake?
It was a mix.
Dude.
There's no shame
in admitting it, Ted.
We've all been
on people's hooks
and we've all kept
someone on the hook.
Um, I most certainly
have not.
(scoffing):
What?!
Are you joking?
What about that girl from
the university library?
Um, Henrietta?
Henrietta and I
are just friends.
Oh, she is so
on your hook.
Absolutely not.
NARRATOR:
She totally was.
I mean...
we cuddled.
(sighs)
We shared chocolate cake.
(chuckles)
She gave me foot rubs-
long ones.
I'm not proud, kids.
You like having Henrietta
around for the same reason
that Tiffany likes
having you around:
it's a nice
little ego boost.
No wonder
you're such an expert
about keeping people
on the hook.
What about that poor
camera guy you work with?
Mike and I are
just friends.
Come on.
Mmm...
Oh, yeah, that's the stuff.
Robin, have you
ever thought
about taking us
to the next level?
Well, if you're talking
about doing my laundry,
I'm on board.
You got yourself a deal.
Hmm.
What?!
I- I am not keeping
Mike on the hook.
You are Captain Hook.
Dude, I'm a girl.
Okayour girl parts
are like a spiderweb.
Sometimes you're gonna
catch stuff you don't want.
That doesn't
make it okay.
Oh, a-and Henrietta
is in, in no way
wasting her time
with you, right?
Henrietta knows
that we're just friends.
In fact,
I'm gonna call her up
and hang out with her tonight
as friends.
Hey, Ted.
Hey.
I love you.
What?
Uh, do you want a foot massage?
'Cause I've been practicing
on myself.
No, I'm good.
I didn't know
if you were hungry,
so I just threw together some...
it's not a big deal.
Kids, looking back,
I don't know how I didn't see
that Henrietta was madly
in love with me.
(phone rings)
Oh.
Hello.
Hey, Ted.
Hey, Tiffany.
I'm going out of town
this weekend
for my friend's wedding.
Want to be my date?
I would love to.
Hey, what are you doing
right now?
Oh, God, no.
Awesome. Okay, I'll see you
in, like, ten minutes?
Great.
Soy, Henrietta,
something came up.
Take a rain check, pal?
Yeah, it's no problem.
All right, yeah, hey-ho.
Oh, you're strong.
What a jerk.
Henrietta, I...
Wait. Where
did Ted go?
I thought we were finally
going to get to meet him.
Yeah, something came up,
okay, Mom?
I told you
there was no Ted.
I heard that.
So there I was,
at one of the surest signs
of taking a relationship
to the next level:
an out-of-town wedding.
It was finally happening.
Champagne?
Ted, oh, my gosh,
I forgot to call you.
Well, whatever it is
you wanted to talk about,
we can talk about it now.
This is Jack.
He's the best man
at the wedding.
We just got back together.
You know, now that
I think about it,
a phone call
would have been nice.
You're Ted? Ouch.
But I hear you make
a mean chocolate cake.
Oh, isn't he great?
And he's in a band.
(squeals)
Thanks.
Come on, Lily. You have
to get Scooter off the hook.
Now, try again.
Teacup Pig, oh...
I don't want to be with you.
Right now.
Man up!
Teacup Pig...
I don't want to be with you.
Ever.
Finish him!
We will never be together
in any sort of sexual way
ever again.
Nice.
Sort of a weird thing
to say to a pig.
It felt really wrong.
Anyway, I just don't think
you and I are going to work.
(whispers):
Right now.
NARRATOR:
And that's when it hit me.
I was on the hook.
I also realized...
I missed this
so much, baby.
...Tiffany was
on this guy's hook.
It was a vicious cycle.
Henrietta was on my hook.
And years later, I found out
this poor bastard
was on Henrietta's hook.
You know what?
We're not going to work ever.
I'm done.
And it's really better
for the circulation
if you knead the arches
with your thumbs.
Now, I'm done.
Marshall, I can
do this by myself.
Okay, well, then prove it.
And, um...
Grab me a pudding.
Listen up, Scooter.
There is no way
you and I will ever be together.
Right now!
Marshall!
I'm sorry, but he's
adorable. Listen.
I don't want to be with you.
Right now.
Hang in there, Scoots!
I'm not going to live forever.
Last night I was with
this pharma girl who was
so hot, you should call a doctor
if you don't have an erection
for more than four hours.
Am I right, people?
Yeah, there's no people-
just the girl
you most recently dated.
(clicks tongue)
Hey, Barney.
I want you to meet
the newest pharma girl.
Oh.
Gladys Reynolds.
Nice to make
your acquaintance.
I represent statins and other
cholesterol-lowering drugs.
Come on, girl.
Let's go get our drink on.
It's over.
What's over?
Pharma girls are no longer
exclusively hot chicks.
It's the en.
You're being
a little dramatic.
Am I?
It starts out with a Gladys.
Next thing you know,
a few not-so-fabulous
gay guys enter the ranks.
And before
you know it,
pharma girls look like the crew
on a Southwest flight
from Albuquerque to Little Rock.
It's over!
So that night, I went
straight to Henrietta's-
all set to let her
off the hook.
This is Jack.
He's the best man
at the wedding.
I'm done.
Yes!
The answer is yes!
No.
Oh, it gets worse.
It's perfect!
Mom, Dad!
Ted proposed!
Oh, my God!
I knew this day would come!
(stammering)
Son!
Yeah, well, there's been a...
No. What did you do?
I seriously considered
just marrying her
out of sheer awkwardness.
But I did what I had to do.
I did what anyone keeping
someone on the hook should do.
I broke her heart.
Henrietta, I'm sorry
if this is blunt,
but I think
I owe you this.
I don't want to be with you.
Right now?
Ever.
But we're still
getting married, right?
It was brutal.
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy.
Honesty is tough,
but in the end,
it is the far kinder
alternative.
Yeah.
Hey, sweetie.
Hey, Mike.
I have to tell
you something.
Wait. Did you finish
my delicates?
Got one more load.
Ah, it can wait.
I...
Hey.
Hey, how's it going?
Still in mourning over the end
of the pharma girl era?
No. I realized
that their reign
had to end to make room for some
new hot girl profession.
Maybe it'll be intergalactic
communications officer
on a rocket ship
to some distant solar system
we can't possibly imagine.
Maybe it'll be... meter maids.
We just don't know.
But one thing is sure.
The future glows
like a giant sun
shooting amber rays of light
into our hearts and minds.
Wow, uh,
what changed your mind?
The realization that hope
springs eternal, Robin.
That and this little
bottle of purple pills
I found in my couch cushion.
Don't know what they are,
but they are amazing!
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net