Kids, as long as I'd known
your Uncle Barney,
he'd always had some
pretty strong opinions
on relationships
Your girlfriend?
She's your girl friend?!
She's a girl
and a friend?
Dont humanize
the enemy, Ted.
But nice to meet you.
Barney Stinson.
And yet,
in the fall of 2009,
he was the one
with the girlfriend.
Go ahead.
Open it.
Open it! Open it!
It's my porn collection!
Just kidding.
That would be weird.
It's your porn collection.
It's my porn collection!
I'm giving you my porn.
Now that things are
so great with Robin,
I don't need it anymore.
Wow, you are voluntarily...
giving up your porn?
You really are serious.
Yeah, well, that's obvious.
What does that mean?
Oh, nothing,
it's just, you know,
you got relationship gut.
What?! No, I do not
"got relationship gut."
That is ridiculous.
It's no big deal. I mean, once you're
dating someone,
it's natal to let
things go a little bit.
Trust me,
we've been there.
Yeah. Boy, did i
pudge you out for a while.
Well, we should get going.
Good-bye, my sweet,
beloved friends.
You have always
been there for me.
You'll be missed.
He's talking to the porn.
Oh.
Bye, Robin. See you, Robs.
Bye, guys.
God, look at these videos.
Space Orgy?
Horny Co-Ed Surprise Party 23?
You'd think after
the first 22 parties,
the co-eds wouldn't be
surprised anymore.
So, uh...
we can get rid
of these for you.
Yeah.
No. No-no-no-no-no-no.
It's not a problem.
I'll-I'll take care of them.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, no biggie. We can just
swing by the back alley
and drop the box
in the Dumpster.
I see six of the words you just
id on this video label.
Seriously, it's not a big deal.
I will take care of it.
No, 'cause I, I mean...
Leave them!
Okay.
You know, in a way
it sad, right?
I mean, Barney's
giving up his porn.
He's got relationship gut.
They eat at the same
diner every night.
It-it's, like, the end of Barney Stinson
as we know him.
Yeah, well, so what? They're happy.
Yeah, well, we gotta go.
Later. Bye.
Bye-bye.
So what'd you get?
I got Squat.
What are you...?
I thought I saw you take one.
Yeah, I did.
It's called Squat.
Hmm...
ArchiSexTure.
That is not how you spell
"Buckminster Fuller."
Kids, pornography is bad,
and so I was
getting rid of that
vile pornography right away...
I am getting rid of this vile
pornography right away.
...when something terrible
happened.
Oh, no.
ArchiSexTure...
Hello, Ted.
If you are watching this tape--
and I knew you'd pick this one--
then you are now
in possession of my porn.
This can only mean
one of two things:
either I'm dead, or m
in a committed relationship.
If I'm dead,
I want you to honor my memory
by taking my body
to the Hamptons
and recreating
Weekend at Bernie's.
I want to dance.
I want to have sex with a girl.
And I want to go fishing.
If, on the other hand, I'm
in a committed relationship,
then as your best friend,
I have only one request:
please, for the love of God,
get  out of it!
Sync by honeybunny. Corrected by Alex28
www.addic7ed.com
I might look happy,
but don't believe it.
Barney Stinson
is meant to be single.
So please, if you value
my best-friendship--
that's right, Marshall,
I'm his best friend,
how does that feel?--
then get me out of this.
And finally, since you were
expecting some porn...
No, no, no baby,
don't worry.
The flashing green
light means it's off.
Are we sure he was
finished talking?
Look, there's
reason we should
take this seriously, right?
Of course not.
This is an old tape.
Barney is happy with Robin.
But over the next couple weeks,
I started to notice things.
Barney and Robin stopped having
crazy adventures.
So what'd you guys
do last night?
I wanted to go
to a concert.
He wanted to go
to a party.
Obviously, we couldn't
do what just one of us wanted,
so we just stayed in,
watched a movie on
It was Legen--
wait for it--
ds of the Fall.
Legends of the Fall!
It was okay.
Barney stopped being himself.
Hey, Barney, I'm, uh, I'm
chatting up this girl
over there, and I could use a
little help landing the plane.
Sorry, Ted, I'm my own
wingman tonight.
And Robin got annoyed
at everything he said.
So, how are u two?
So great.
Oh... shut up.
Relationships are the best.
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up, shut up...
The sharing, the compromise,
The monogamy, can't beat it.
Catchphrase! Yes!
But the worse they got...
I'm full... sweetie.
...the more they kept saying
things were great.
Now, the truth is,
Barney and Robin
only kind of let themselves go
a little bit.
But I swear, after a few more weeks,
to us, they seemed like this.
I'll be there...
in a minute.
Hey.
They're killing each other.
They love each other.
Barney and Robin
love each other,
but they're not Barney
and Robin anymore.
They're the fat guy
and the old lady.
My favorite '70s detective show.
Look, it's so ear.
Barney's been overeating
because he hates being
tied down like this.
And Robin's stressing out
because she hates
what Barney's turned into.
No, they're a perfect match.
Well, maybe that's the problem.
Maybe they're too similar.
It must be tough having
two alpha dogs
in one relationship.
We have two alpha dogs in our relationship.
Sure we do, sweetie.
If they're not happy,
why don't they just break up?
Because they're too stubborn.
Neither one of them
wants to be the first
to admit that they want out.
They're playing
Relationship Chicken.
I think Barney ate
the relationship chicken.
Ted, it's just a rough patch.
It takes time getting used
to being with someone else.
And they're both...
What the nice word for selfish?
Independent.
Every relationship
goes through this.
It's true, um,
I have this astronaut friend--
totally loved his fiancée.
And then, the day before his
mission she caught him
with, like, four other chicks,
a couple of dudes.
Things got really tense.
Um, finally, she ended up
sneaking onto the space
shuttle...
Are you talking about Space Orgy?
Yes, I am.
Ted, it's just a rough patch.
Just let things
run their course.
She's right.
But...
Two-to-one, Ted.
Leave them alone
So I did leave them alone.
But that weekend...
Have you noticed how beef ribs
used to always be disgusting,
and then recently,
they found a way
to make them really
delicious instead?
Okay, Barney, I'm going to go
ahead and ask you this head-on
Are you happy with Robin?
Are you kidding?!
How could I not be happy
with Robin?
It's Robin!
So are you happy?
I can't believe you would even
ask me that.
I mean, yes,
we fight all the time,
but you know what they say
about relationships:
Every moment's a battle.
So are you happy?
Do you know what goes
hand in hand with fighting?
The makeup sex.
Which is different
when you're in a loving,
long-term relationship.
Heads we have sex,
tail we order a whole pizza
and just lay here moaning.
Oh, great.
Let the coin decide.
Which was pizza again?
Tails.
It was tails.
Sex-- am I right?
Thank God that's mostly over.
I'm still hungry.
You hungry?
We have to break them up.
You're right.
Barney and Robin
are miserable together,
but they're too stubborn
to admit it.
So we had to get them
to break up.
How do we do that?
We unleash...
the Kraken.
Kids, as you know,
earlier that year
I'd learned that Lily had
broken up not one,
not two, but seven
of my past relationships.
Forget it.
I'm retired.
I'm out of the game.
But nobody's better than you.
I'm telling you,
I swore off that rocket.
I've gone legit.
I'm a matchmaker now.
Set me up with someone.
Whoa, I'm just starting out.
Please. You've, you've
got to break them up.
This relationship
is killing them.
I know it is,
but I've learned my lesson.
No more interfering.
Let things run their course.
It's two-to-one.
Yes, but t one is me.
All right, we don't need her.
We can break them up on our own.
How?
Okay remember when
Robin and I were dating?
What was the one big thing that
really freaked her out?
No, no, no, no, no--Ted, you can't.
No! No-no-no!
What are you talking about?
This! This is
what I'm talking about.
What is this doing
in my champagne?
If we make Robin think
for even a second
that Barney is proposing,
she'll lose it
and they'll break up.
That's crazy.
Why don't we just,
uh, like, lead Barney
into temptation?
We'll find some hot woman
hit on him...
Okay, the ring thing.
Stakeout van.
What?
We should've gotten
a stakeout van.
We could've ordered pizza,
look through
big binoculars and said,
"This ain't what I signed up
for," stuff like that.
Shh, here
comes the waiter.
Please shut up.
What?
Oh, I thought
you said something, sorry.
Is that an engagement ring?
Are you...?
Oh, no. No.
That is not .
They must have delivered it
to the wrong table.
Can you imagine
us getting married?
Well, we are committed
to each other.
Most of your stuff is
already at my apartment.
It might make taxes easier.
It'd speed up your citizenship.
"Scherbatsky"
is so hard to spell.
My mom would be so happy.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, no reason not to.
We're getting married!
Not so loud, geez.
What did you do?
I am furious right now!
This is so wrong!
Lily, will you be
my maid of honor?
Oh, my God! I would love to!
Are you out of your mind?!
You knew they were playing
Relationship Chicken,
And what did you do?
You put an engagement ring
in front of them!
Okay, that's it.
I'm taking over.
Coming out of retirement
for one, last breakup.
Oh-ho! All right.
Oh, yes!
How are we going to do it?
These guys are in so deep,
just one fight
ain't going to do it.
We need
to reignite
the four biggest fights
they've ever been in
all at once.
Number one:
The Battle of the Dirty Dishes.
Number two:
The Ex-Girlfriend Conflict.
Hey.
Don't you know
that girl over there?
No, I don't think .
No, in fact,
I have definitely not--
Oh, hey, it's Meg.
Wow, I am certainly not comparing you two
in my mind right now.
Whoops! Hey, will you get that for me, please?
Really?
What's the problem? I'm not... Why do you keep--
You're embarrassing me in public.
Youre constantly putting me in these positions.
Oh, my God...
Number three:
The Star Wars Altercation.
Isn't it time you got
rid of your stupid doll?
It's not a doll.
It's a Storm Trooper.
Uh, he's wearing a diaper.
It's not a diaper, Robin,
it's protective armor.
Storm Trooper?
More like storm-pooper.
Stop it.
Oh!
Oh, it sounds like
your storm-pooper here
needs a changing. Okay, you know what?
I'm sick of it.
What? I didn't say anything. I'm sick of the jokes--
the joke about the magic,
the joke about the stormtrooper...
I can't... I can't joke?
And of course the biggie:
The Canadian/American War.
Thank God that song's over.
Who the hell was
that old lady singing?
Okay, you know that Neil Young
is my favorite musician.
Right. Now, was that the same
old lady who played
Archie Bunker's wife
in All in the Family,
or just sound-alike?
Neil Young is
a Canadian treasure.
Do not make fun of Neil Young.
Robin, I would
never make fun of
a defenseless old lady with
vocal cord paralysis... ever.
Oh, here we go. In public?
Really? In public?
Yeah, in public. I'll go there.
What's the problem? Everything
I say...
We're gonna have a fight in public?
I got it.
We e-mail them pictures
reminding them
of each of these fights.
You child.
Here's how it goes down.
They're at the diner...
LILY:
First, rekindling
the Canadian-American debate,
Ontario native Alan Thicke
stops by the table.
TED & MARSHALL:
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Alan Thicke?
Oh, right.
Robin knew him
back when she was a singer.
Yeah, and they still
keep in touch.
I already got his number
off her phone.
Seriously... amateurs.
LILY:
So Alan Thicke restarts
the Canada-U.S. fight.
Right at that moment,
Crazy Meg shows up.
Then, a stormtrooper happens
to walk by the window.
And just when they can't take
anything more,
a busboy walks by
with a tray full of what?
Dirty dishes.
Lily.
This is your masterpiece.
We're getting a stakeout van!
A station wagon?
Really? You rented
a station wagon?
Yeah, a van cost,
like, 25 bucks more.
A station wagon?
Greetings, Will Robinson!
Where's the birthday
boy or girl?
Hey, climb on in.
What the hell is this?
Oh, they didn't have
any stormtroopers,
so I had to get a different
robot; this'll still work.
Different robot?
Stormtroopers
aren't robots.
Of course
they're robots!
"Must kill Luke Skywalker."
Um, nobody says that
in Star Wars at all, ever.
That's a really lousy
robot voice, honey.
Someone order an
extra large sausage?
Hey, one of Barney's videos
starts off just like that.
Hey, guys, Barney's ordering...
five of something.
I don't know if
it's gonna fit in here.
Okay, now you're
just quoting the video.
Still ordering.
Waiter's taking out
a second pad.
Yeah, okay, well,
we need it in here.
We're on a stakeout.
Shouldn't you be in a van?
Thank you!
A van cost more.
Score me a slice, Will Robinson!
No, no-no-no!
You get a stain on that costume,
they're gonna charge us.
Dude, will you just chill
about money?
Yeah, let the stormtrooper
have a slice.
BOTH:
It's not a stormtrooper!
Hi, Lily
Sorry I'm late.
I was looking for a van.
Thank you!
$25!
So should I go
say hi to Robin?
Oh, not yet;
get in the car.
Okay, so wait,
wait, wait.
When they blew up
the Death Star,
knowing full well
there were thousands
of stormtroopers on it,
those were people?
It was called
the Death Star, baby.
They knew what
they were getting into.
Look, I don't want to play
the "I'm Alan Thicke" card,
but I really do have a dinner
to get to.
Someone has got to
take this sausage!
Okay, were you in that video?
Were you the guy
with the farmer tan?
Jonesin' for some 'za,
Will Robinson!
Come on, I'm Alan Thicke!
This ain't what I signed up for.
Hey! That's what...
Hey, you know what? Everyone, stop!
Alan Thicke, shut up! Marshall,
it's a station wagon.
Get over it!
Ted, stop talking about porn!
And for the love of God,
somebody get the stormtrooper
some pizza!
TED & MARSHALL:
It's not a stormtrooper!
Crap!
They see us!
Danger! Danger!
Are you sure they saw us?
Yes.
Hey!
Can I go talk to Barney now?
I'm so excited!
Do you really think
he's going to propose to me?
Oh, honey...
Forget it, Crazy Meg,
we've been made.
If we try anything now,
they're going to know it's us.
I, I think we should all just
go home...
No!
This is my masterpiece.
So what if they saw us?
It'll still work.
Stop it. We'll think
of something else.
Let me repeat:
"I am Alan Thicke."
You're Alan Thicke?!
No.
Alan Thicke, you're up.
Get on out there.
NARRATOR:
And so, Lily followed
through with her plan.
First, Alan Thicke.
Followed by Crazy Meg.
Then, the robot.
And finally, the dirty dishes.
But by the end of it...
LILY:
They're kissing?
They shouldn't be kissing!
Why isn't this working?
Because they're in love.
It really was
just a rough patch.
What the hell am I doing?
This whole thing was a mistake.
So, uh,
any of you dudes
want to get high?
I never thought I'd be
saying this tonight, but...
to Barney and Robin,
the happy couple.
That was the moment we learned
that relationships
take hard work,
but eventually,
everything will work out.
Oh, hey!
Where's Barney?
Uh, we broke up.
And that was the moment
we unlearned that other lesson
we had just learned
a few seconds earlier.
You see, earlier that night,
when Lily thought
Barney and Robin
had spotted her,
this is what they really saw.
Why do that fat guy
and old lady keep sta...?
Oh, my God. That's us!
Look at us.
Did  always look this awful?
Robin, I'm not happy.
I mean,
I wish I was.
Nothing would make me happier
than being happy, but...
I'm not.
What are we doing wrong?
We love each other.
I mean, if this don't work,
what will?
We're so similar.
We both like scotch.
We're both awesome.
You know, maybe that's it.
Maybe there's just
too much awesome here.
Exactly.
Two awesomes
cancel each other out,
and I'm tired of being
cancelled out.
Me, too.
Are we breaking up?
I think so.
Ah, crap.
Now comes the next part.
The part where you and can't
go back to being friends.
Well, maybe this isn't
a breakup.
Maybe this is two friends
getting back together.
ALAN THICKE: Robin!
Ooh!
Alan...
Oh, it's always so great
to see a fellow hoser.
Yes! Oh, is true.
MEG: Barney!
Good news!
I forgive you
for the whole
restraining order thing.
Uh, hi.
Whoa, is that a stormtrooper?
That's not a stormtr...
You want to get out of here?
Yeah.
See you guys.
Okay.
See you, Alan.
So you still on 73rd Street?
How do you know that?
Getting back together
as friends... I like that.
One more for the road?
And, I mean, who knows?
Maybe, when,
like, you turn 40,
if you haven't found anyone...
Oh, I already have
that deal with Ted.
Oh, right. Stupid.
Well, maybe when you turn 39,
if you haven't
found anyone...
It turns out
that they really did
just need to let things
run their course.
So, uh, how's Barney doing?
He's okay, I think.
It might be a while before
he fully recovers, but. Ooh!
Did you guys just feel a chill?
Yeah.
Daddy's home.
Well, Robin,
I'm glad we could catch up.
Oh, yeah, let's
do it again soon.
I love that you guys
are still friends
so long after you
did that music video.
Yeah.
The music?
Oh, the "Sandcastles"
video, yes!
Yes, we did that
together, too.
What do you mean "too"?
Oh, we had this
failed Canadian
TV variety show we did.
That was so embarrassing.
Imagine what would happen
if anybody ever got
their hands on that?
Oh, you.
Sync by honeybunny - Corrected By Alex28
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net