Never know
When you're about to meet
someone really important.
It's not like life
gives you a warning.
You just look up
and there they are.
Come on, we're going to
go get trashed on the roof.
No, not that dude.
Her.
I'm good, boomer.
My name's not boomer.
Oh, in my head,
it is. Gentlemen,
I'm a faculty member,
and you're underage,
So it's my duty to
confiscate this and this and-
Hard lemonade?
You know what, boomer?
You can keep that.
I swear,
Every week I get
asked by some frat guy
To a kegger, and I say,
"i'm a phd candidate writing
a dissertation entitled
'foreign direct investment
And intergenerational linkages
in consumption behavior.'"
(laughs)
And what does frat
guy say to that?
(in deep voice): "that's hot."
(laughs) actually,
that is kind of hot.
(laughs)
Ted, I have a confession. Hmm.
I recognize you.
Do you remember the first
day of classes last semester?
Econ 305?
Kids, you remember the
wrong classroom story.
I thought I was in architecture
101, but it was econ 305.
Of course, what
I didn't know was
That your mother was
somewhere in that class,
And she thought I
was a complete idiot.
I thought you were a
complete idiot. (sighs)
But a very cute idiot.
So, um, do you ever
date cute idiots?
Almost exclusively.
Transcript by addic7ed.com
She's a phd candidate,
She reads philosophy for fun,
She does the Sunday crossword
every week and finishes it.
Ooh. Barney: Wow,
Ted, I am so happy for you
- sorry,
Not for you,
happy I'm not you.
Long story short: I
have a date tonight.
Oh, yay. (hooting and
hollering from the street)
(chuckles) hmm?
Thanks, new york, I'll
try not to screw it up.
What's going on?
There's a huge line
outside maclaren's.
And why is it almost
entirely dudes?
Only two things could cause
that kind of commotion.
Boobs.
♪ she's my cherry pie... ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
Maclaren's has hired
a hot bartender.
♪ sweet cherry
pie, yeah. ♪
Look at all these guys.
(groans)
The sidewalk's going to
smell like pee-pee now.
Well, we'd better start
looking for a new bar.
What, are you- what,
are you- are you crazy?
It is a hot bartender.
Do you know how long I have
been waiting to land a...
My friends, I have been
with many women in my day.
Lawyers, teachers,
poets, doctors,
Professional equestrians,
amateur equestrians...
A butcher, a baker,
a candlestick maker-
Yes, we're to the
rhyming section now-
A math professor, a tax
assessor, a weight guesser...
A puppeteer,
A blackjack dealer,
A stay-at-home mom-
that's a job, too, guys-
A circuit court judge...
Get to the point!
I have never, ever
scored a hot bartender
Until tonight.
She's really not that hot.
Aw, is someone jealous
of all the attention?
Did somebody fancy herself
the hottest girl in the bar?
Gosh, no. Shut up!
All right, wish me luck.
All right, it's
never going to happen.
Barney, she's just going
To pretend to like you
The same way she hypnotized
all these geniuses.
Yeah, but guess who's not
going to fall under her spell?
I'm gonna be all, "drop
the act, baby doll.
Daddy needs a gin and tonic."
Then when she brings it,
I'm gonna just spit it
out and say, "try again."
Boom! Alpha dog is
right where he belongs:
On top, then after a few
minutes, on the bottom.
Why should I do all the work?
Hi, marshall. Guys,
what's happening?
New superhot bartender.
Oh, yeah? Mm-hmm.
(scoffing): Eh.
Ha, ha, see?
Marshall doesn't
think she's hot either.
Yes, he does.
Baby, you don't
have to pretend
Other women aren't
attractive just for my sake.
I know, and if that woman
were anywhere near as hot
As the woman I'm married
to, then I'd admit it,
But she's not.
Oh, baby, you're so sweet,
but compared to that woman,
I am a big bag of
three-day-old garbage.
Well, I call 'em
Like I see 'em, and...
I just think you're the most
beautiful woman in the world.
See, that's just annoying.
Oh, my god, you are so funny.
That'll be $6.75.
Here's a 50, keep the change.
Oh, thank you.
Amateurs.
Hey.
What do you want? Drop
the act, baby doll-
Wait, what? Are
you gonna order
A drink or are you just gonna
stand there looking stupid?
Um...
I don't know how
to make an um.
Is that equal parts vodka and
get-the-hell-out-of-my face?
Hey, bobby!
What's going on?
Later that night, I embarked
Upon a very
important first date.
How are you? Good. Come in.
It's funny, sometimes
you walk into a place
You've never been before,
but you get the feeling
You're exactly where
you're supposed to be.
And kids, that's the
first time I ever saw
Your mother's
little yellow bus.
You know the one.
It's right behind you.
Hey, this is cute.
Actually, it's my roommate's.
As, kids, standing in
your mother's apartment,
Never mind the fact that I
was on a date with her roommate
Cindy.
Sorry, I shouldn't be messing
With your roommate's stuff.
(chuckles) what's she like?
I didn't know it, but
I was about to hear
The very first description of
the woman I'd one day marry.
She's a whore.
I think she's a
dominatrix. What?
Okay, I'm sorry,
none of that is true.
I have a bit
Of a roommate complex. Why?
Guys are always falling
in love with her.
Hey, hey, look at me.
I promise you
I am not going to fall in
love with your roommate.
Oops.
Okay, now that you've had
a closer look, admit it:
That bartender is the
hottest woman in this bar.
(coughing): Second hottest.
I repeat...
Eh. (sighs)
Baby, how could you
not want to hit that?
I want to hit that.
If you don't want to hit that,
I'm sorry, but
you might be gay.
Hell, yeah, I'm gay.
Gay for you.
Whatever. Did you find out why
I'm the one guy in this entire
bar she seems to despise?
I did, um...
You're not going
to like the answer.
My last three boyfriends were
wall street guys- bastards-
So I vowed
Never again to date
A guy who wears suits.
Huh.
Okay, well, that's easy.
All I have to do is
stop wearing suits. Oh,
That's all, barney?
Come on, you're
never not in a suit.
True... But for those-
I mean, for that-
I mean, for her...
I will stop wearing-
Wait for it...
We know you're
going to say "suits."
...Suits.
(both gasp)
Meanwhile, cindy and I
Were having a lovely evening,
Except she wasn't kidding
about her roommate complex.
And another weird
thing about my roommate:
She does these bizarre paintings
of robots playing sports.
Yeah, that is weird.
I was lying.
That sounded awesome.
Your mother's robot
volleyball watercolor
Is hanging up in
the den as we speak.
Yeah,
And she has this crazy habit
Of making breakfast
food sing show tunes.
That's just bizarre.
Your mother's
rendition of "memories"
As performed by an english
muffin is, to this day,
The most hauntingly beautiful
thing I've ever heard.
Look, I'm sold.
I hate this girl.
I'm sorry.
Look, she's not that bad.
I just get a little jealous.
I don't know why.
You're awesome.
But not as awesome
as your mother.
And speaking of things
that are less awesome,
Your uncle barney had
officially suited down.
I am so sorry
I misjudged you.
If there is
One type of person
That I cannot stand,
It is a man in a suit.
(shudders)
That and a woman
who has no respect
For herself. (shudders)
Yeah.
Suits and insecure women
- I hate 'em.
Just hate 'em.
Hey. Hey. Hey, how was
Your date with cindy?
Well, last night was
great, today not so much.
What, why?
I found out the
school's policy
About students and professors
dating is really strict.
I could lose my scholarship.
Yeah, but I-it's not
like you're in my class.
I mean, we're not even
in the same department.
I'm sorry, but I
just can't risk it.
(sighs)
She's completely
overreacting, right?
Actually, ted,
she has a point.
Lily: Yeah, and
think about it.
If the rules are that strict,
You could be putting
your job in jeopardy.
I think, I think you got
to let this one go, buddy.
Let's try this again:
She's completely
overreacting, right?
Of course, they were right.
I had to let it go,
But as your uncle barney
was about to find out,
It's not so easy
to let things go.
(indistinct,
creepy whispering)
(eerie whispering): Suit up.
Narrator: Now, none
of us had ever seen
Barney go this long
without suiting up,
And kids, it wasn't pretty.
So sorry I'm late.
I got stuck at work.
You know how today I
had that presentation
On offshore dividend
tax implications?
Sure, I was totally
paying attention
When you talked about that.
Right, so I fire
up the powerpoint...
Um, barney?
Barney. Aah.
(panting)
(sighs)
(eerie whispering): Suit up.
♪ ♪
Marshall: Hey, barney, we're
going to order some food.
Okay, be out in a sec.
Okay.
(ripping)
No.
Out of the way!
Stay with me.
It's not your time.
Narrator: If anyone could
fix something like this,
It was barney's
personal tailor,
Tv's tim gunn.
I'm sorry, barney.
I couldn't make it work.
(sobbing)
So young.
There's nothing
else you could do?
No, but there is another suit
That can use the
buttons from your suit.
That can...
Like an organ donor?
Your suit's death could
mean another suit's life.
But I...
Do it.
You're doing the right thing.
(sobbing and muttering)
Please don't cry on this.
It's silk. I'm sorry.
I know. I know.
We cremated the remains.
His buttons saved the life
Of a sick little jacket
on the upper east side.
Well, at least now you
can finally drop this quest
For the so-called
hot bartender.
No.
My suit gave its life
For this cause,
And I will not
rest until those...
I mean, that...
I mean, she... Is mine.
He's absolutely right.
Who, the guy kissing a jar full of dead suit ashes
- that guy?
What if cindy is the woman
I'm supposed to marry,
And I'm just giving up?
So long, elegant, yet
welcoming home in westchester
With a sensible
mortgage I can handle
Without dipping
into my savings.
Bye-bye, two kids I raised
with a stern, yet loving hand,
Finding the perfect
balance between
Father and friend.
Adios, triplet schnauzers,
frank, lloyd and wright.
Ted! Ted! Ted!
The point is,
I'm not giving up, either!
Ooh. Ooh.
I don't know why
I just did that.
Barney, I'm so sorry
about your friend.
Tell me about him.
(laughs) he was italian.
Classy, elegant.
And boy, did he have
a way with the ladies.
They just couldn't say no.
How old was he? Seven.
I miss him so much!
You shouldn't
be alone tonight.
I'm gonna end my shift early.
Thank you, old friend.
(voice breaking): You're
going out with a bang.
Lily: Come on, marshall.
Just admit that
she's hotter than me.
I won't be hurt.
Can't do it.
You're hotter.
Oh, she's a goddess!
Her skin glows.
Her legs go for miles.
And that ass?
I would wear that
thing for a hat.
Last night in
bed, I'll admit it,
She popped into my
head a couple of times.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you try...?
Like, you think
she's hotter than me?
I never said that.
Marshall: Oh, my god!
You do.
It's apples and oranges.
She's younger than you.
I'm just saying, like,
Me in my prime versus
her in her prime.
Well...
Oh, my god!
You guys, her hotness
isn't even real!
It's circumstantial hotness.
Watch.
♪ she's my cherry pie ♪
♪ cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
♪ taste so good, make
a grown man cry... ♪
I
- I suppose you think she's hotter than me, too.
♪ wow! ♪
What the hell are
you doing?! What?
You're not allowed back here.
Oh, no. Uh, I... Carl, look.
No. I-I don't
want to go back.
Please, please,
don't make me go back.
You got to go. Don't. I...
You got to go. I just...
No, carl. I was... I
was somebody back there!
Everybody loved me.
(knocking)
Hey. Hi.
Can we talk?
My roommate's just about
to get out of the shower.
Let's talk in my room.
Okay.
(water running)
(sighs)
Look, cindy, I know
The university rulebook
says we can't date.
But it also says,
"don't teach drunk,"
And I do that all the time.
The point is,
I like you.
I do.
You're sweet, you're funny.
You're writing a dissertation
Entitled,
Foreign direct investment
And intergenerational linkages
and consumption behavior.
I mean, that is hot.
I know this sounds
crazy, but...
I feel like our paths are
supposed to cross somehow.
And I don't want to
miss out on knowing you.
I don't want to miss out
on knowing you, either.
Look, I got to tell you,
I mean, just from
looking around your room,
I can tell we have
a ton in common.
Really?
The unicorns?
Who will cut our
hair when we're gone?
I have never met anyone
else who has this album.
That's my roommate's.
I borrowed it.
Oh.
Well, well, what about this?
World's end by t.C. Boyle?
That was a birthday
gift... From my roommate.
Haven't checked it out yet.
Oh. Oh, you should.
It's-it's a good read.
Well, what about this?
This is ridiculous.
You play bass?
Seriously, ask my friends.
I always say,
my ideal woman...
Does not play bass, because
this is clearly your roommate's.
She's in a band.
(sotto voce):
Damn, that's cool.
This is unbelievable.
You just picked out the
only three things in here
That are my roommate's.
So, does your roommate's band
ever play shows, or...? Get out.
Narrator: Kids, as
you probably guessed,
That wasn't the night
I met your mother.
Although I think I
glimpsed her foot.
But I did get a
little bit closer
To meeting the
woman of my dreams.
And your mom-
Well, she got her
yellow umbrella back.
It was just so
special, you know?
I feel like we should give
him a moment of silence.
Followed by, like, 20
minutes of grunting.
I'm gonna make you
feel all better.
(laughs)
Let me just go freshen up.
All right.
Oh, wait. No, no,
that's not the bathroom!
That...
Are these yours?
I'm suit-sitting for someone.
Barney, you lied to me.
(sighs)
You have to choose right now.
Me... Or the suits.
(music intro begins)
♪ I know what you're thinkin',
"what's barney been drinkin'?" ♪
♪ that girl was
smokin' hot! ♪
♪ yes, I coulda nailed her,
but no, it's not a failure ♪
♪ 'cause there's one
thing she is not ♪
♪ to score a ten
would be just fine ♪
♪ but I'd rather be
dressed to the nines ♪
♪ it's a truth
you can't refute ♪
♪ nothin' suits
me like a suit! ♪
♪ picture a world ♪
♪ where all the boys and girls
are impeccably well-dressed! ♪
♪ that delivery guy
in a jacket and tie ♪
♪ that puppy in
a double breast! ♪
♪ that eighties dude
with muttonchops ♪
♪ that baby with
a lollipop! ♪
♪ that lady cop
who's kinda cute ♪
♪ nothing suits
them like a suit! ♪
♪ suits! ♪ ♪ a
wingman I can wear! ♪
♪ suits! ♪ ♪
they're, oh, so debonair ♪
♪ suits! ♪
♪ the perfect way to snare
a girl with daddy issues ♪
♪ suits! ♪ ♪ in
navy blue or black! ♪
♪ check out this
perfect rack ♪
♪ I want to give
them a squeeze ♪
Oh, really!
♪ then answer
these questions ♪
♪ if you please ♪
♪ what would you do
if you had to choose ♪
♪ between your suits
and a pot of gold? ♪
♪ suits ♪
♪ what would you say if
you gave your suits away ♪
♪ and in return you'd
never grow old? ♪
♪ suits ♪
♪ what would you pick:
One million chicks ♪
♪ or a single
three-piece suit?
It's moot.
♪ what if world peace
were within your reach? ♪
(stammering): I'm gonna
stop you right there.
It's suits.
Come on, lily, get your
head out of your ass.
Two, three, four!
♪ girls will go and
girls will come ♪
♪ but there's only
one absolute! ♪
♪ every bro on the
go needs to know ♪
♪ that there's no
accepted substitute! ♪
♪ I'm sorry, suits,
let's make amends ♪
♪ my Sunday best are
my best friends! ♪
♪ send casual Friday
down the laundry chute ♪
♪ 'cause nothing
suits the undisputed ♪
♪ oft-saluted
suitor of repute ♪
♪ like... ♪
♪ a... ♪
Wait for it.
♪ suit... ♪
♪ nothing suits him ♪
♪ like... A...
♪ ♪ suit... ♪
♪ suit! Up! Suit! Up! ♪
♪ suit up! Suit up! ♪
♪ suit...! ♪
Then again, she is pretty hot.
I choose you, baby.
First thing tomorrow, I'm
getting rid of these suits.
Really?
Yeah.
Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
(whispers): You guys are fine.
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net