Kids, the secret to dating
is very simple.
Be confident, be comfortable
in your skin,
be assured of who you are.
Uncle Barney was really good
at that last one,
even though a lot of the time
who he was was someone else.
Do you see that guy
over there in the scuba suit?
You thinking of going
and talking to him?
Good. He's seriously the biggest jerk
on the face of the Earth.
- How do you know him?
- He's one of my best friends.
So what's with the scuba suit?
It's a long story. See, he just
went through a breakup...
There's two basic philosophies of how
to handle yourself after a breakup.
Some people throw themselves into...
My career. That's my number one
focus right now.
From now on, no more dating.
It's all about work.
While others throw
themselves into...
Every woman in New York City.
That's right, Barney Stinson
is back on the market.
Mothers, lock up your daughters.
Daughters, lock up your MILSWANCAs.
- MILSWANCAs?
- Wait, I can get this.
"Mothers I'd Like To Sleep With
And Never Call Again".
Correct!
Circle gets the square.
Don't you think you're kinda
rushing back into this?
Since I started dating Robin,
there's a certain
thing I haven't used as much
as I would like.
It's... kinda big,
surprisingly heavy,
kind of leathery, and it's black.
This, my friends...
is The Playbook.
Synchro: Mickeyte, MiniBen314
Traduction: Dark_Chii,
Litéo, Lino72 & MiniBen314
Relecture: MiniBen314
How I Met Your Mother
5x08 - The Playbook
par la "Have You Met Team"
pour www.forom.com
The Playbook contains
every scam, con, hustle,
hoodwink, gambit, flimflam,
stratagem and bamboozle
I've ever used,
or ever hope to use...
to pick up chicks
and give them the business.
You wrote another book?
We got a... Stephen King over here.
It's all in here.
Everything from basic moves like
The Don't Drink That.
Don't drink that. I saw some guy
slip something in there.
What? Who?
That guy.
Thank you.
To more advanced maneuvers
like The Mrs. Stinsfire.
Now Kappas,
after our disciplinary hearing
for lewd behavior last semester,
we have been assigned
a new housemom.
I'd like you to meet Mrs. Stinsfire.
Hello, girls!
I can't picture a way
that wouldn't work.
What's The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn?
I'm glad you asked.
The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn
will be my grand return to the stage.
Or you know, the bed.
Actually, my bed
is kind of on a stage.
I put a platform underneath,
and got some lights going.
It's a real production.
Barney exits!
So, how about you?
You getting back out there?
- Where is your playbook?
- My playbook? Bro...
two-volume set, right here.
- It's a great read actually.
- I'm reading it right now.
Anyway, I told you already,
I'm taking a break from all that.
- It's totally gonna happen.
- So gonna happen.
- What's gonna happen?
- You're gonna fall in love.
So soon.
Not likelly I'm focusing on my career.
I'm done with dating.
We playing The Pyramid?
"Things people say right before
they meet the love of their life."
Kelly Harris, girl I went
to law school with, said...
Law school'so hard,
I just want to focus on my studies.
Six months later?
Married!
- That's all well and good...
- Travis Frenchroy,
backup bartender tells me...
I'm so over the whole dating game.
I just want to focus
on my Star Trek fan fiction.
Six months later...
Married!
May I respond?
- That's all well and good for them...
- Matthew Blitz,
accountant at my office says,
I'm gonna die single and alone.
I might as well just focus
on this year's taxes.
Six months later? Civil union and
planning to get married pending
the passage of legislation currently on
the floor of the New York State Senate!
Protest all you want,
but it's gonna happen.
- It's a law of nature.
- Lawyered. Of nature.
Believe me, I'd love to have
no interest in a relationship.
There's no way I'd be single right now
if I wanted to be single.
- Okay, now you're ready.
- Ready for what?
Three years ago, this girl Shelly
started teaching at my school.
The moment I saw her, I was like,
"This is the girl for Ted."
Why am I just hearing about her now?
You know,
I usually hate being set up
but this Ted just sounds so great.
He is. He's so sweet
and thoughtful and intelligent.
One more chicken
finger and the crown is yours!
I don't see him anywhere.
He must be out doing charity work.
So, different bar?
- Yeah she was cute.
- Still is. And now you're ready.
Now you can fit like, three times
as many chicken fingers in your mouth.
- You know it.
- Okay, I will set it up, but,
promise me you won't do
anything stupid.
I promise I won't do
And I kept that promise.
But only because...
she never showed up.
I know. I'm sorry, I feel terrible.
- You should feel terrible!
- I do feel terrible!
- You should! You should!
- I do, I do!
I don't. Look, I was really
looking forward to meeting Ted,
but I got to the bar
an hour early and I met this
amazing guy.
Like, seriously amazing.
And you met him at MacLaren's?
- Right at the bar.
- What's his name?
I shouldn't say.
What the heck.
It's Lorenzo Von Matterhorn!
You... son of the bitch.
So, he hooked up with Shelly?
You must've been pissed.
Damn straight.
I've had Shelly set aside
for Ted for three years.
Dude, Ted was not missing out.
She's brainy and annoying,
kind of boring in the sack.
I guess she would've been
perfect for Ted.
Had I known
that she was there to meet Ted,
of course I wouldn't
have done it, but...
given the circumstances,
I think Ted'll be proud of me.
I pulled off
The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
What's The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn?
My question exactly.
- What's The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn?
- Glad you asked.
To perform
The Lorenzo Von Matterhorn,
here's what you'll need,
basic knowledge of Web site design
and a very unique fake name.
So, think of your fake name
right now.
Have you g it? Good.
Now, select your target.
Preferably a girl
with a real nice...
phone.
Yeah, it's me.
Do I know you?
I'm Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
Are you, like, famous or something?
You really don't know
who I am, do you?
What a refreshing change of pace.
Nice to meet you...
Once again,
I'm Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
Spelled like it sounds two "T"s.
Then, as soon as you're gone,
she gets out her phone
and does an Internet search
for Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
And that's when she discovers.
A series of fake Web sites,
all devoted to the incredible life
of Lorenzo Von Matterhorn.
There's the fake business article about
Lorenzo, the reclusive billionaire.
The fake Explorers Club newsletter
describing his balloon trek to
the North Pole, a feat of pure
daring and imagination.
The fake medical journal
featuring the heartbreaking story
of doctors telling him penis reduction
surgery isn't an option.
And by the time you get back...
I hate to be forward but,
can I buy you a cup of coffee?
Please.
What does coffee go
for these days, $50?
And... it is on.
That's awful.
You realize you broke her heart?
She's inconsolable.
Why would she be inconsolable?
Lorenzo's balloon won't disappear
over the Arctic for another week.
The only way she would be upset
is if someone told her it was all
a bunch of lies.
- It was all just a bunch of lies?
- It was all just a bunch of lies.
- The balloon expedition?
- Lies!
The man-made island
shaped like his face
- off the coast of Dubai?
- Lies!
Finishing third
in the laser tag competition?
Li... Actually, that one's true.
I went to that.
- You went to the Vatican?
- Lies!
Well, I hope
you're happy with yourself.
- What?
- You broke that girl's heart.
- Me?
- You!
She'll probably never trust
a guy again.
You ruined her for Ted.
Not to mention
Julio Von Matterhorn,
Lorenzo's twin brother.
Can you believe that? He blames me
And by the way, Ted,
I bet she'd still go out with you.
Let me think. Do I want to go out
with a girl Barney hooked up with?
Help me out with the harmonies.
Sure.
Hell no...
- You must be a little bothered by this.
- It's his life.
If these girls are dumb enough to fall
for this crap, they have it coming.
Agreed. Have you seen the one
there labeled The SNASA?
You're an astronaut?
I'm actually in a top secret
government space program
called Secret NASA
or... SNASA.
SNASA?
- Do you go to the Moon and stuff?
- Not the Moon you're familiar with,
though I have been to the Smoon.
The Smoon.
If you fall for that one,
my heart breaks for you,
but I'm sorry, you're a smoron.
So, what happens next?
Come on, Barney, you just...
You just got out on
an honest to God relationship.
You're a real boy now.
You can't go back
to these cheap tricks.
Cheap tricks?!
Not one of these is a cheap trick.
Except for The Cheap Trick.
I'm the bass player for Cheap Trick.
And even that one involves
expensive hair extensions.
Now, if you don't mind, I am off
to prepare for tonight's main event.
I will be performing
The He's Not Coming.
Glad you asked.
To perform The He's Not Coming,
here's what you'll need,
the observation deck
of the Empire State Building.
Are you up there? Good.
For generations, this has been
the spot New Yorkers have chosen
for their romantic reunions
with long-estranged lovers,
so all you have to do is walk up
to every girl you see and say:
He's not coming.
- What are you talking about?
- Never mind.
He's not coming.
She's not coming?
Sorry.
Until sooner or later...
He's not coming.
He's not?
But we agreed.
We always said we'd meet here.
On this night.
I'm such a fool.
I'm gonna go get the paper.
- More like, go get a husband.
- Totally.
You guys need to stop at, seriously.
The last thing I am looking for
right now is a relationship.
When you pick up that newspaper, be sure
to check the wedding announcements.
For yours.
It's like this. Do you have any idea
how many times in my life
I've gone to the freezer looking
for frozen waffles and not found them?
- Thousands?
- Millions.
But when I go
to the freezer loing for
a Popsicle or the remote control
because Lily and I are having a fight
and she's hidden it there,
you know what I fi?
Frozen waffles.
That's how it works.
You go out there looking
for a paper,
you're coming back with
frozen waffles. And, in this case,
frozen waffles is a guy.
Also, could you pick up
some frozen waffles?
In that case, frozen waffles...
are frozen waffles.
Guys, code red! Emergency.
Lockdown. Nobody's leaving.
- What happened?
- I tried The He's Not Coming,
and it worked. Gangbusters.
You should have seen this girl.
I'm leaving.
So, we get up to my place,
and I go intmy room to set up
the camera... to light the candles...
and when I come out,
she's gone,
and so is The Playok!
I think we all know
who is responsible for this.
Yeah, we do.
Al-Qaeda.
No, you idiot.
It was me.
You... son of a bitch!
You stole The Playbook?
So, the girl on the
Empire State Building?
A friend of mine, an actress.
An actress.
Of course.
That explains her impeccable
diction and her sluttiness.
I've got half a mind
to take that playbook and
put it up on the Internet
for the whole world to see.
- You wouldn't.
- I won't, as long as you agree
to no more scams, no more cons,
no more hustles,
no more hoodwinks, no more gambits,
no more stratagems
and no more bamboozles.
I notice you left out flimflams.
- No more flimflams!
- Damn it.
I'm sorry to interrupt
but look at this.
I got left at the altar.
Oh, my God, that's horrible.
I wonder if that would work.
That's not even
the worst one in here.
Have you guys seen the
My Penis Grants Wishes?
Really?
A genie comes out of it?
Only if you rub it hard enough.
- So, then, what happened?
- It says here he breaks into song
and then the furniture comes
to life and dances with him.
It's not very well-thought-out.
It's no Mrs. Stinsfire.
- No, what happened in real life?
- Well, a few hours later...
You know, I heard it was gonna rain.
If anyone's interested,
I will be at MacLaren's Pub
performing a play out of
The Playbook entitled The Scuba Diver.
That is all.
That's it. I'm putting
The Playbook up on the Internet.
Baby, can you put The Playbook
up on the Internet?
Of course, baby,
but here's the weird thing.
I have literally been through
this book cover to cover.
There is no play in here
called The Scuba Diver.
So, now you guys want to know
what The Scuba Diver is.
Well, it was
on the last page of The Playbook,
but I ripped it out just in case.
Don't worry, though.
You're about to see it in action.
See the blond over there by the bar?
Tizzarget acquizzired.
- Barney, don't do this. You're so...
- Give it a rest, pest.
If anyone should be mad, it should be
Robin. She loves The Playbook.
I don't love The Playbook.
What are you talk...?
The Playbook, it's gold.
You got to admit
it's pretty spectacular.
We just broke up.
I mean, yes,
the costumes are cute, but...
we just broke up.
Well...
I didn't know you felt that way.
I guess I've been so wrapped up
in my own stuff that...
Crap, she's looking over here.
Quick, everyone, scatter.
That's it.
You see at guy over there
in the scuba suit?
And that brings us to rig now.
But... wait. So, why is he
wearing scuba gear?
We don't know. And it's killing us,
Claire. It's killing us!
Let's go ask him.
So, what's The Scuba Diver?
And this is Claire, by the way.
Hello, Claire. My name
is Lieutenant Frank Lyman.
I train bomb sniffing
dolphins for the Balt...
You know what?
I can't do this.
I am so sorry.
I guess this breakup's
been tougher on me than I thought.
I think this playbook was just a way
to take my mind off of things.
It's okay.
It's been tough on me, too.
I mean, look at me.
I've sworn off relationships.
- She's so about to get married.
- I got to work on my toast.
I got to make sure my tux fits.
I will bang your heads together
like coconuts.
I'm so glad you're stopping this.
And, frankly,
the real Barney is way cooler
than any of the fake Barneys
- in this playbook.
- Is that right?
Claire, you've prably heard a lot
about the real Barney tonight.
Want to grab a cup of coffee?
Before you turn him down,
I think you should know that
under this neoprene suit
with what appears to be
- a tube sock stuffed in the crotch...
- Can of Pringles but go on.
... is an amazing guy. He's fun
and one of my best friends.
And he landed this hottie.
He's a good guy.
- Come on, Claire, go out with him.
- It's just a cup of coffee, right?
- Can't hurt.
- All right, all right.
Let's t some coffee.
And by the end of the night...
I'm prd of that guy. To be that
vulnerable takes a lot of Pringles.
I got a text from Barney.
"Look under the table."
- It's a page from The Playbook.
- What does it say?
It's The Scuba Diver.
Step one, tell a meddlesome
female friend about The Playbook.
Step two, run play on one of her
coworkers, making her so angry
she's steals the Playbook.
Step three, put on the scuba suit and
tell her you're gonna do one more
scam called The Scuba Diver
on the hot girl standing by the bar.
Your friend, let's call her Lily,
goes tell the girl
everything about The Playbook.
Here's where it gets tricky. When Lily
and the girl ask at The Scuba Diver is,
take off your mask, get them some
schmear about your deep-seated
insecurities which don't really
exist cause you're awesome.
Feeling bad for you, Lily talks you up
to the girl, who then agrees
to go get coffee with you. And it...
is...
on.
You... son of a bitch!
I'll give you a call.
For those of you keeping score,
"The Ted Mosby" works.
Here we go. You say
you don't want a relationship.
Well, the love of your life is about
to walk through the door,
and it's...
that guy.
I'm not falling in love
with that guy.
Right, cause it's going to be...
that guy.
I don't know. The blue blazer's just,
like, not doing it for me, so...
You're right, cause here
he comes. It's that guy!
You should at least give her a chance.
You know, make out with her a little,
see if there's sothing there.
- I'm going to work.
- Yeah, you are.
I'm actually going to work.
And the ironic part was...
Are you Robin?
I'm Don, your new cohost.
That was the day she met Don.
Damn it, Marshall.
www.tvsubtitles.net