Kids, as long as I'd known
your Uncle Barney,
he'd always had some pretty
strong opinions on relationships.
Your girlfriend?
She's your girl friend?!
She's a girl and a friend?
Do not humanize the enemy.
But nice to meet you.
And yet, in the fall of 2009,
he was the one with the girlfriend.
Go ahead. Open it.
It's my porn collection!
Just kidding.
That would be weird.
- It's your porn collection.
- It's my porn collection!
I'm giving you my porn.
Now that things are so great
with Robin, I don't need it anymore.
You are voluntarily...
giving up your porn?
You really are serious.
- That's obvious.
- What does that mean?
Nothing, it's just you know,
you got relationship gut.
What?!
I do not "got relationship gut".
That is ridiculous.
It's no big deal. I mean,
once you're dating someone,
it's natural to let things go
a little bit. Trust me,
we've been there.
Boy, did a pudge out for a while.
We should get going.
Good-bye, my sweet, beloved friends.
You have always been there for me.
You'll be missed.
He's talking to the porn.
- Bye, Robin. See you.
- Bye, guys.
God, look at these videos.
Space Orgy?
Horny Co-Ed Surprise Party 23?
You'd think after
the first 22 parties,
the co-eds wouldn't be
surprised anymore.
We can get rid of these for you.
It's not a problem.
I'll take care of them.
Are you sure? I mean, no biggie.
We can just swing by the back alley
and drop the box in the Dumpster.
I see six of the words you just
said on this video label.
Seriously, it's not a big deal.
I will take care of it.
- Cause I mean...
- Leave them!
You know, in a way it sad, right?
Barney's giving up his porn.
He's got relationship gut.
They eat at the same diner
every night.
It's, like, the end of Barney Stinson
as we know him.
- So what? They're happy.
- We gotta go. Later.
- So what'd you get?
- I got Squat.
What are you...?
I thought I saw you take one.
I did. It's called Squat.
ArchiSexTure.
That is no how you spell
"Buckminster Fuller."
Kids, pornography is bad,
and so I was getting rid of that
vile pornography right away...
I am getting rid of this vile
pornography right away.
When something terrible happened.
ArchiSexTure...
If you are watching this tape,
and I knew you'd pick this one...
then you are now
in possession of my porn.
This can only mean
one of two things,
either I'm dead, or
I'm in a committed relationship.
If I'm dead,
I want you to honor my memory
by taking my body to the Hamptons
and recreating Weekend at Bernie's.
I want to dance.
I want to have sex with a girl.
And I want to go fishing.
If, on the other hand,
I'm in a committed relationship,
then as your best friend,
I have only one request.
Please, for the love of God,
get me out of it!
Synchro: Mickeyte
Traduction: Dark_Chii,
Eomyn & MiniBen314
Relecture: MiniBen314
How I Met Your Mother
5x07 - The Rough Patch
par la "Have You Met Team"
pour www.forom.com
I might look happy,
but don't believe it.
Barney Stinson
is meant to be single.
So please,
if you value my best-friendship...
that's right Marshall,
I'm his bestriend,
how does that feel?
Then get me out of this.
And finally, since you were
expecting some porn...
No, baby, don't worry.
The flashing green
light means it's off.
Are we sure he was finished talking?
Look, there's no reason we should
take this seriously, right?
Of course not. This is an old tape.
Barney is happy with Robin.
But over the next couple weeks,
I started to notice things.
Barney and Robin stopped
having crazy adventures.
So what'd you guys do last night?
I wanted to go to a concert.
He wanted to go to a party.
Obviously, we couldn't do
what just one of us wanted, so,
we just stayed in,
watched a movie on cable.
It was Legen... wait for it...
ds of the Fall.
Legends of the Fall!
It was okay.
Barney stopped being himself.
I'm chatting up this girl over there
and I could use a little help
landing the plane.
Sorry, I'm my own wingman tonight.
And Robin got annoyed
at everything he said.
So, how are you two?
- So great. Relationships are the best.
- Shut up.
- The sharing, the compromise,
- Shut up...
the monogamy, can't beat it.
Catchphrase!
But the worse they got...
I'm full...
The more they kept saying
things were great.
Now, the truth is, Barney and Robin only
kind of let themselves go a little bit.
But I sware after a few more weeks,
to us, they seemed like this.
I'll be there...
in a minute.
- They're killing each other.
- They love each other.
Barney and Robin love each other, but
they're not Barney and Robin anymore.
- They're the fat guy and the old lady.
- That's my favorite 70s detective show.
Look, it's so clear.
Barney's been overeating because
he hates being tied down like this.
And Robin's stressing out because
she hates what Barney's turned into.
They're a perfect match.
Maybe that's the problem.
Maybe they're too similar.
It must be tough having two
alpha dogs in one relationship.
We two are alpha dog
in our realtionship.
Sure we do.
If they're not happy,
why don't they just break up?
Because they're too stubborn. Neither
one of them wants to be the first
to admit that they want out. They're
playing Relationship Chicken.
I think Barney ate
the relationship chicken.
It's just a rough patch.
It takes time getting used to being
with someone else. And they're both...
- What the nice word for selfish?
- Independant.
Independant. Every relationship
goes through this.
It's true...
I have this astronaut friend,
totally loved his fiancée.
And then, the day before his
mission she caught him
like, four other chicks,
a couple of dudes.
Things got really tense.
Finally she ended up sneaking
onto the space shuttle...
- Are you talking about Space Orgy?
- Yes, I am.
It's just a rough patch.
Just let things run their course.
- She's right.
- Two-to-one, Ted. Leave them alone
So I did leave them alone.
But that weekend...
Have you noticed how beef ribs
used to always be disgusting,
and then recently, they found a way
to make them really delicious instead?
I'm going to go ahead
and ask you this head-on.
- Are you happy with Robin?
- Are you kidding?!
How could I not be happy with Robin?
- It's Robin!
- So are you happy?
I can't believe you would even ask me
that. I mean yes, we fight all the time,
but you know what they say
about lationships,
"Every moment's a battle".
So you're happy?
And you know what goes
hand in handith fighting?
The makeup sex.
Which is...
different
when you're in a loving,
long-term relationship.
Heads we have sex,
tails we order a whole pizza
and just lay here moaning.
Great. Let the coin decide.
- Which was pizza again?
- Tails.
It was tails.
Sex...
Am I right?
Thank God that's mostly over.
I'm still hungry.
You hungry?
We have to break them up.
You're right. Barney and Robin
are miserable together
but they're too
stubborn to admit it.
- We have to get them to break up.
- How do we do that?
We unleash...
the Kraken.
Kids, as you know, earlier that year
I'd learned that Lily
had broken up not one,
not two,
but seven of my past relationships.
Forget it. I'm retired.
- I'm out of the game.
- But nobody's better than you.
I'm telling you,
I swore off that racket.
I've gone legit.
I'm a matchmaker now.
- Set me up with someone.
- I'm just starting out.
Please. You've got to break them up.
- This relationship is killing them.
- I know it is, but
I've learned my lesson.
No more interfering.
- Let things run their course.
- It's two-to-one.
Yes, but the one is me.
We don't need her.
We can break them up on our own.
How?
Remember when Robin and I
were dating? What was the one
big thing that really
freaked her out?
You cannot do this to me.
- What are you talking about?
- This! This is what I'm talking about.
What is this doing in my champagne?
If we make Robin think for even
a second that Barney is proposing,
- she'll lose it and they'll break up.
- That's crazy. Why don't we just,
like, lead Barney into temptation?
We'll find some hot woman hit on him.
Okay, the ring thing.
- Stakeout van.
- What?
We should've gotten a stakeout van.
We could've ordered pizza,
look through big binoculars
and said,
"This ain't that I signed up for",
stuff like that.
Here comes the waiter.
- Please shut up.
- What?
I thought you said something, sorry.
Is that an engagement ring?
Are you...?
That is not. They must have
delered it to the wrong table.
Can you imagine us getting married?
We are committed to each other.
Most of your stuff is
already at my apartment.
- It might make taxes easier.
- It'd speed up your citizenship.
- "Scherbatsky" is so hard to spell.
- My mom would be so happy.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Yeah, no reason not to.
- We're getting married!
- Not so loud, geez.
What did you do?
I am furious right now!
- This is so wrong!
- Will you be my maid of honor?
Oh, my God! I would love to!
Are you out of your mind?!
You knew they were playing Relationship
Chicken, and what did you do?
You put an engagement ring
in front of them!
Okay, that's it.
I'm taking over.
Coming out of retirement
for one, last breakup.
- How are we going to do it?
- These guys are in so deep,
just one fight ain't going to do it.
We need to reignite
the four biggest fights
they've ever been in all at once.
Number one,
The Battle of the Dirty Dishes.
Number two,
The Ex-Girlfriend Conflict.
Don't you know that girl over there?
No, I don't think so.
No, in fact, I have definitely not...
It's Meg.
I am certainly not comparing
you two in my mind right now.
- Will you get that for me? Please?
- Really?
Number three,
The Star Wars Altercation.
Isn't it time you got rid
of your stupid doll?
It's not a doll.
It's a stormtrooper.
He's wearing a diaper.
It's not a diaper,
it's protective armor.
Stormtrooper?
More like storm-pooper.
Stop it.
It sounds like your storm-pooper
here needs a changing.
- You know what? I'm sick of it.
- I didn't say anything.
Of the jokes about the magic,
the stormtrooper...
And of course the biggie,
The Canadian/American War.
Thank God that song's over.
Who the hell was
that old lady singing?
Okay, you know that Neil Young
is my favorite musician.
Was that the same old lady
who played
Archie Bunker's wife in All
in the Family, or just sound-alike?
Neil Young is a Canadian treasure.
Do not make fun of Neil Young.
I would never make fun of a defenseless
old lady with vocal cord paralysis...
I got it.
I got it. We e-mail them pictures
reminding them
of each of these fights.
You child.
Here's how it goes down.
They're at the diner...
First, rekindling
the Canadian-American debate,
Ontario native Alan Thicke
stops by the table.
- Alan Thicke?
- Right.
Robin knew him back
when she was a singer.
And they still keep in touch.
I already got his number off her phone.
Seriously... amateurs.
So Alan Thicke restarts
the Canada/US fight.
Right at that moment,
Crazy Meg shows up.
Then, a stormtrooper happens
to walk by the window.
And just when they can't take
anything more,
a busboy walks by
with a tray full of what?
Dirty dishes.
This is your masterpiece.
We're getting a stakeout van!
A station wagon?
Really? You rented a station wagon?
- A van cost, like, 25 bucks more.
- A station wagon?
Greetings, Will Robinson!
Where's the birthday boy or girl?
Climb on in.
- What the hell is this?
- They didn't have any stormtroopers,
so I had to get a different robot.
This'll still work.
Different robot?
Stormtroopers aren't robots.
Of course they're robots!
"Must kill Luke Skywalker."
- Nobody says that in Star Wars at all.
- That's a really lousy robot voice.
Someone order an
extra large sausage?
One of Barney's videos
starts off just like that.
Barney's ordering...
five of something.
I don't know if
it's gonna fit in here.
Now you're just quoting the video.
Still ordering. Waiter's taking out
a second pad.
We need it in here.
We're on a stakeout.
Shouldn't you be in a van?
- A van cost more.
- Thank you!
Score me a slice, Will Robinson!
You get a stain on that costume,
they're gonna charge us.
Will you just chill about money.
- Let the stormtrooper have a slice.
- It's not a stormtrooper!
Sorry I'm late.
I was looking for a van.
- Thank you!
- $25!
- So should I go say hi to Robin?
- Not yet, get in the car.
So wait...
When they blew up the Death Star,
knowing full well there were thousands
of stormtroopers on it,
those were people?
It was called the Death Star.
They knew what they were getting into.
I don't want to play the
"I'm Alan Thicke" card,
but I really do have
a dinner to get to, so...
Someone has got
to take this sausage!
Were you in that video?
Were you the guy with the farmer tan?
Jonesin' for some'za, Will Robinson!
- Come on, I'm Alan Thicke!
- This ain't what I signed out for.
You know what? Everyone, stop!
Alan Thicke, shut up!
Marshall, it's a station wagon.
Get over it!
Ted, stop talking about porn!
And for the love of God, somebody get
the stormtrooper some pizza!
- It's not a stormtrooper!
- Crap!
They see us!
Are you sure they saw us?
Can I go talk to Barney now?
I'm so excited!
Do you really think
he's going to propose to me?
Forget it, Crazy Meg,
we've been made.
If we try anything now,
they're gonna know it's us.
- I think we should all just go home...
- This is my masterpiece.
So what if they saw us?
It'll still work.
Stop it. We'll think
of something else.
Let me repeat: "I am Alan Thicke."
You're Alan Thicke?!
Alan Thicke, you're up.
Get on out there.
And so, Lily followed through
with her plan.
First, Alan Thicke.
Followed by Crazy Meg.
Then, the robot.
And finally,
the dirty dishes.
But by the end of it...
They're kissing?
They shouldn't be kissing!
Why isn't this working?
Because they're in love.
It really was just a rough patch.
What the hell am I doing?
This whole thing was a mistake.
So... any of you dudes
want to get high?
I never thought I'd be
saying this tonight, but...
to Barney and Robin,
the happy couple.
That was the moment we learned
that relationships take hard work,
but eventually,
everything will work out.
- Where's Barney?
- We broke up.
And that was the moment we unlearned
that other lesson we had just
learned a few seconds earlier.
You see, earlier that night,
when Lily thought
Barney and Robin had spotted her,
this is what they really saw.
Why do that fat guy
and old lady keep sta...?
That's us!
Look at us.
Did we always look this awful?
Robin, I'm not happy.
I mean, I wish I was.
Nothing would make me happier
than being happy, but...
I'm not.
What are we doing wrong?
We love each other.
If this don't work, what will?
We're so similar.
We both like scotch.
We're both awesome.
You know, maybe that's it. Maybe
there's just too much awesome here.
Exactly.
Two awesomes cancel
each other out, and...
I'm tired of being cancelled out.
Me, too.
Are we breaking up?
I think so.
Crap.
Now comes the next part.
The part where you and can't
go back to being friends.
Maybe this isn't a breakup.
Maybe this is...
two friends...
getting back together.
It's always so great
to see a fellow hoser.
Good news! I forgive you for
the whole restraining order thing.
- Is that a stormtrooper?
- That's not a stormtr...
You want to get out of here?
See you guys.
See you Alan.
So you still on 73rd Street?
How do you know that?
Getting back together as friends...
I like that.
One more for the road?
And, I mean, who knows?
Maybe, when, like, you turn 40,
if you haven't found anyone...
- I already have that deal with Ted.
- Right. Stupid.
Well, maybe when you turn 39,
if you haven't found anyone...
It turns out that
they really did just need
to let things run their course.
So, how's Barney doing?
He's okay, I think.
It might be a while before
he fully recovers, but...
Did you guys just feel a chill?
Daddy's home.
- I'm glad we could catch up.
- Let's do it again soon.
I love that you guys
are still friends
so long after you
did that music video.
The music?
The "Sandcastles" video!
We did that together, too.
- What do you mean "too"?
- We had this
failed Canadian
TV variety show we did.
That was so embarrassing.
Imagine what would happen if
anybody ever got their hands on that?
You.
www.tvsubtitles.net