This is the life.
We got the three B's.
Beach, booze
and bodacious babes.
I don't know.
I'm starting to think
we should call the police.
Oh, would you relax?
We've got it made.
One whole week
at his bodacious beach house,
no strings attached.
Well, there is one
string attached.
Hi, Barney.
Bodacious.
"Weekend at Barney's!"
What is it? What's wrong?
The plays, Robin, the plays.
The ingenious techniques I used
as a bachelor
to pick up busty dullards.
They just keep coming to me;
I can't turn them off.
Okay, Barney, let me
ease your mind, okay?
All right, here we go.
Remember when you set
your Playbook on fire?
That was the moment I realized
you were someone I could marry.
And I'd burn it again
if I could.
You're right.
I'm done with all these plays.
Besides, there's no way
I'll ever come up
with anything that tops
"Weekend at Barney's."
"Weekend at Barney's Two!"
Damn it, Barney!
♪ How I Met Your Mother 8x18 ♪
Weekend at Barney's
Original Air Date on February 25, 2013
So, there's this big
gallery opening tonight.
Oh, we'd love to, but
we've got this, um...
Genesis reunion,
Madison Square Garden,
front row.
It's gonna be legend...
I wasn't inviting you guys.
Oh, thank God.
There is no concert.
As the captain's
new art buyer,
I have to go schmooze
this up-and-coming artist,
Strickland Stevens,
so we get first dibs
on all his new stuff.
And I'll be helping
Lily seal the deal
by impressing
the intelligentsia
with some art-related
hilarity.
I've prepared some jokes.
Why couldn't the art
dealer pay his rent?
I don't know. Why?
This is gonna be rough.
Because he ran
out of Monet.
You're gonna get that
on the walk home.
How about this one?
You know what, we'd...
we'd love to hear it,
but we've got that,
um... that...
Steely Dan, Carnegie Hall,
backstage pass. Let's go.
We don't want to miss
whatever their big song was.
Yeah.
Your wedding response card,
as promised.
Why didn't you just mail
it like everybody else?
Oh, see, that's sad, Robin.
You should be touched
that I hand-delivered it.
Has social media so eroded
our interpersonal relationships
that we no longer wish
to experience the...
You wanted to
keep the stamp?
They're 46 cents now.
It's getting out of hand.
"Your invitation
is joyfully accepted
by Mr. Ted Mosby and Jeanette""
Kids, as you'll recall,
Jeanette was
the last girl I dated
before I met your mother.
My friends only had
one tiny problem with her.
She was nuts.
So you're bringing
a plus one?
If you count the
voices in her head,
it's plus five.
Guys, I'm bringing her,
and you're gonna love
having her there.
Oh, and, um, by the way,
just so this doesn't turn
into an argument later,
the dress she's gonna wear
isn't technically white;
it's eggshell.
The shoes are white, though.
And the gloves.
And the veil.
Well, see you guys.
No, no, no.
Mosby! Get...
Oh, my God, what happened?
Oh, I trashed your apartment.
See, I got bored,
so I started going
through all your e-mails.
Sure.
And I found one from a woman
with the subject line,
"big penis orgasms,"
so naturally,
I smashed your plates,
knifed your mattress,
peed in your drawers,
the whole nine, but then,
while I was upper-decking
your toilet,
I actually read the e-mail.
Turns out it was spam.
Classic Jeanette, huh?
Oh, my God.
You are certifiably insane...
...about me.
Come here, you knucklehead.
I can't stay mad at you.
Ted, Ted,
I'm breaking up with you.
You're just
so intense,
and it's all moving
way too fast.
Here's your key back.
I never gave you a key.
And here's
your grandmother's ring.
She was buried wearing this.
And just like that,
it was over.
I texted Barney and Robin.
I'm sure they're over the moon
that Jeanette's not coming
to the wedding.
Oh, no, Ted, no.
They're not gonna be
happy about you being sad.
They broke up!
Ted, respectfully,
are you sure that this was
the right girl for you?
Of course not.
She was crazy.
Absolutely a nightmare.
It's totally not worth
the trouble.
I mean, no matter how...
no matter how great the sex was.
Uh-oh.
Stay with us, buddy.
No matter how hot and passionate
and surprising,
possibly illegal...
I don't like this.
Me, neither.
I'm gonna win her back.
Barney and Robin are gonna be
so happy I'm happy.
I know.
Did you just unhook my bra?
Shh. There, there.
That night was
the big gallery show.
Hey. I'm so sorry.
I decided to grab a snack
from the bodega.
Why?
They'll have food
at the gallery.
Oh, come on,
these places never have food.
It's fine.
I got some Skittles.
That was the last bag
of Skittles
your Uncle Marshall
would ever buy.
Meanwhile, I headed over
to Jeanette's place
to win her back.
What the hell?
I can't let you do this, Ted.
I want Jeanette back.
Well, then accept my apology.
For what?
This.
Ow, ow, ow! Damn it!
You're strong.
That's just from Pilates?
Twice a week.
Look, I don't want you
getting back with Jeanette.
Ted, what is my one rule?
You can tell how old a girl is
by her elbows?
My other one rule.
Flaxseed relieves upset stomach?
Always have a fake pair
of concert tickets
in your pocket in case Lily
invites you to something stupid?
My other one rule.
Lebanese girls sprint to third
base and then stay there?
My other one rule.
New is always better.
New is always better!
Exactly, Ted.
You want to invite a date
to our wedding,
it is not gonna be Jeanette.
It is gonna be someone new.
And I am gonna help you
find her
with a little help from...
The Playbook.
The Playbook?
Didn't you burn that?
Oh, I didn't burn the real one.
That was
the ceremonial playbook
for parades,
mall openings,
inaugurations, stuff like that.
That's a pretty big secret
to keep from Robin.
Which is exactly
why I'm trusting you,
my best bro,
to never let her know
that the Playbook still exists.
Pinky swear?
Fine.
Wow.
See, I told you.
Thank God I snuck in
this bag of goodness.
There's Strickland Stevens.
Wow.
Even his scarf
is up-and-coming.
Are you gonna be okay
by yourself for a few minutes?
Yeah, of course.
Why wouldn't I be?
Well, you're sitting
on an $80,000 sculpture.
For 80 grand,
you'd think it
would be more comfortable.
Lil, I'll be fine.
Do you know
who you're talking to?
In high school,
I was voted most outgoing
freshman, sophomore
and senior year.
What happened junior year?
Egdud Ferhaki,
that outgoing son of a bitch.
He beat you for most outgoing?
Huh? Oh, no, we tied.
Look, the point is, I can make
friends anywhere, even here.
Thanks, baby.
You got it.
Hey, excuse me.
Listen.
Do you think that you
would enjoy a show
featuring Donatello, Raphael,
Michelangelo and Leonardo?
Sound like
you're a fan
of the Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles.
Gotcha. Skin it.
He will get that
on the drive home.
He didn't.
Fireworks?
Yeah.
Everything in there is a
prop we'll need for tonight.
Everything.
All right, here's how
this is going down.
You'll be wearing this
earpiece and microphone.
I'll be staked out here,
telling you exactly what to say,
so just stay focused
and you'll be fine.
Which play
are we gonna run first?
How about
the "Weekend at Barney's"?
Oh, Ted, your first day
at the salon,
and you want
to do a cut and color?
No.
Tonight we're gonna
start off with...
Ice Man to Neruda.
Bogey at 10:00,
and she is packing
two fully-operational
sweater stretchers.
That's bravo, Oscar, Oscar,
bravo, Sierra.
Possible delta cups.
Copy that. Engaging target.
Over.
Excuse me,
I have a delivery for Lisa.
Excuse me, I have
a delivery for Lisa.
Are you Lisa?
Uh, no.
But you must be.
I was told to...
...deliver this package
to a girl named Lisa,
and that I'd recognize her
because she'd be...
The most beautiful girl
in this bar.
So, here's your delivery,
Lisa.
Uh, I am definitely
not Lisa,
but I would be happy
to help you find her.
Great, and then maybe later...
I could give you
a different package-- my penis.
That is a terrible line!
You said it wrong.
I did not say it wrong.
My penis.
No.
Still not right.
My penis, my penis, my penis!
Hello.
This sucks.
I can't get near Strickland.
At least Marshall's having
a good time.
Man, he always knows
just the right thing to say.
For a gay guy,
Andy Warhol sure liked cans.
This sucks.
Maybe I've lost my charm.
No, Marshall,
if Lily's gonna make it
in this fancy art world,
you're gonna have to make it,
too, so suck it up,
stop sitting on the art,
and bust out the "A" material.
You two keep chugging
like that,
you're gonna have to
Vincent van go
to the bathroom, am I right?
It's pronounced van Gogh.
Oh, "blogh" me.
I still don't get why someone
would leave the hospital
without changing
into their clothes first. Over.
Ted, this is my thing.
So just... okay?
Over.
Okay? Over.
Are you all right?
What? Oh.
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
Tomorrow, I'm...
donating a kidney
to my best friend.
My best friend Barney.
Not Marshall.
Barney.
Marshall's so lame.
Anyway, uh...
just wanted to grab
one last drink, in case...
you know, I don't make it.
You are so brave.
Hey, listen.
Before I give my best friend
this organ, how about...
Nope.
Nope, I'm not saying that.
I did hear you,
but I'm not saying that.
Because I'm not.
Are you okay?
One second. I know you put
a lot of work into this.
I understand that.
Why can't I just
talk to her?
Maybe we'll hit it off...
Fine.
Copy that.
How about I give you
a different organ?
My penis.
You said it wrong.
I did not say it wrong!
Thank you all so much
for coming.
If you'll
indulge me,
I would like to share a story
about my dearly departed
grandmother.
Oh, God.
News flash, Johnny Ascot:
Lots of people
have dead grandmas.
No, Marshall.
Don't be bitter.
You're here for Lily.
Just look at her,
so professional.
She hasn't sat
on a single piece of art.
You're gonna ride this thing
out with dignity for Lily.
Not one more thing
that might embarrass her.
I will simply stand here.
Perfectly invisible.
And so I dedicate this show
to my grandmother's memory.
Now...
please join me in honoring her
with 60 seconds
of absolute silence.
Okay, Neruda, this play is
extremely complicated.
Let me guess.
Does it involve me
saying "my penis"
in a Scottish accent?
Now you're gettin' it, laddie!
Hey!
Robin. What are you doing here?
I was curious as to whether
you found Ted a date
to our wedding
who was a little less,
you know, Antichrist-y.
Is that the Playbook?
No, Robin, that is a couch.
Oh, you mean
the Playbook on the couch?
I can explain.
Don't bother.
I can ex...
Uh, Ted? Uh...
I got to step away from
mission control for a sec.
Don't do anything stupid
while I'm gone.
Robin...
Robin, wait.
Um... shoot.
I haven't figured out
what I'm gonna say yet.
Keep going.
Robin, wait.
Look, I'm sorry
that I still have the Playbook.
It's just, it's filled
with a lifetime of great ideas.
Am I supposed to just
leave all that behind?
Yes.
But...
"Weekend at Barney's"!
Okay, what is that?
Explain the
"Weekend at Barney's" to me.
What's to explain?
I play a dead guy,
and Ted and Marshall
carry me around.
Okay. And based on that,
girls want to sleep with you.
Big time.
But you're dead.
Yeah. Except not really,
obviously.
But the girl thinks you're dead.
No, she thinks I'm alive.
Which you are.
Exactly.
Except you're dead.
Except you're alive.
Exactly.
Okay, so instead of...
of being an alive person
pretending to be a dead person
pretending to be
an alive person,
why not just be an alive person?
Okay, let's start
from the beginning.
The movie is called
Weekend at Bernie's.
My name is Barney.
I'm so sorry,
sweetie.
I don't know
if you heard,
but I dropped
some Skittles.
Do you know what,
I'm just gonna
go home before I
make things worse.
You're not
going anywhere.
We're a team.
You stuck by me
after my nip slip
at your law school graduation.
And after my nip slip
at the GNB Christmas party.
at the Honeywell and Coots
Family Fun Day.
I don't know why you
keep wearing that top.
All right,
I'll stay put,
but I'm keeping
my mouth shut.
No more jokes,
no more candy,
no more Teenage
Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Hey, are you guys
talking Ninja Turtles?
I'm a huge TMNT fan.
I grew up on those comic books.
Me, too!
I was obsessed.
Did you know that
the original comic debuted
in 1984 at a convention
in New Hampshire?
Uh, yes.
Did you know that Eastman and
Laird always had their doubts
about their characters
being commercialized?
Yes!
Did you know that the painting
on the back wall
is inspired by Master Splinter?
Oh, the one of the
rat doing karate.
I see it now.
Hey, I'm Strickland.
Hey. Marshall.
And this is my wife, Lily,
who, as a matter of fact,
happens to represent one of
the biggest art collectors
in New York City.
I love your work.
It's great to see you
getting some recognition.
Thank you.
It's been a long haul.
The first painting
I ever sold,
I used the money
to get my car fixed.
You might say...
I used it to make my van go.
That's...
Um, a little something
called rigor mortis?
Oh, come on.
Are you really this
mad about a book?
You really think that this
is just about a book, Barney?
You lied to me.
If we're gonna
be in a marriage
and trust each other,
you can't lie to me ever.
Really?
Well, that's just great.
Because, in case you haven't
noticed these last eight years,
lying is what I do best.
I'm a magician, Robin.
Misdirection and deceit
are my stock in trade.
You don't want me
to lie to you?
Lies are the reason
that we're together.
Everything single
thing I did
to get you to say yes
to me on that rooftop--
Patrice, the false
engagement, everything--
it was all utter malarkey.
But...
underneath all
of those lies
is one true thing.
One true thing
that can support the weight
of all the lies
in the world, and...
and that's the fact
that I love you.
And you know
that when I say that...
I am not lying.
Wha...
Did you just unhook
my bra again?
Jeanette,
this is great.
We're back together.
You're coming to Barney
and Robin's wedding.
I found two wine glasses
you didn't smash.
Call me crazy,
but I've got a feeling,
from here on out, it's gonna be
nothing but blue skies and...
What...
the hell...
is this?!
Uh-oh.
Check out this
text from Ted.
Oh, my...
What the hell
happened here?
Jeanette and I had
a little spat.
Would anyone like some wine?
It's a nice Côtes du Rhne.
Still needs to breathe a bit.
You know what?
I got a decanter upstairs, so...
We should just drink it now.
And for
the grand finale,
I found your fireworks.
Let's see what they do
to your precious Playbook!
No!
Jeanette, please,
that's Barney's
life's work!
It's fine, Ted.
Blow it up, Jeanette.
♪ Put a candle in the window
♪ 'Cause I feel
I've got to move ♪
♪ Though I'm going, going
♪ I'll be coming home soon
♪ Long as I can see
the light... ♪
Okay.
No more dating.
I'm ready to settle down.
And, kids...
for the first time in my life,
I really meant it.
Oh!
Oh...
The boots...
www.tvsubtitles.net