Kids, the summer of 2012
was the Summer of Love.
Barney and Quinn,
me and Victoria,
Robin and Nick,
Lily, Marshall and Marvin.
Everyone was happy as can be.
Which means there are
absolutely no good stories.
Let's skip ahead...
...to October 2012,
the official kick-off
of what came to be known as
the Autumn of Breakups.
It all started when Barney
got a little friendly advice
from a coworker.
Get a prenup,
or I'll neuter you
before she ever
has a chance!
First of all,
if you have an onion bagel,
you don't need
scallion cream cheese.
Secondly, Quinn
is a great girl.
I trust her.
Oh, Darlene was
a great girl.
I trusted her.
And then she took everything!
My house, my car...
my dog Tugboat.
I even lost out
with the kids.
Full custody!
I got full custody
of those kids!
Your kids are horrible.
The worst.
Barney, I watched as Darlene cut
everything good out of my life
like a deranged surgeon
hacking out organs,
and that's not a metaphor.
She got one of my kidneys.
That's her ringtone.
I have nothing left
to give you, Darlene!
* How I Met Your Mother 8x02 *
The Pre-Nup
Original Air Date on October 1, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
You won't believe
what Barney did today.
what Quinn did today.
Hey, you ready for lunch?
Hey, there she is.
The future
Mrs. Barney Stinson.
You better enjoy signing
your name "Quinn Garvey"
while you still can, right?
Like, I don't know...
here, here, here,
initial here...
What is this?
Oh, this is our prenup.
Black or blue?
Totally up to you.
Um, can I read it first?
Can you believe that?
He wants me to sign a prenup!
She wants to read it first!
Just go ahead and sign.
It's all pretty standard.
"In the event of divorce,
"Mr. Stinson is granted
weekly visitation rights
to Ann, Sarah and Molly."
You named our future kids?
That's actually pretty sweet.
Those are Mr. Stinson's names
for your lady parts.
It's important for the girls
to maintain a relationship
with their daddy.
You named her lady parts?
Everyone does that.
So... Lily?
Snap, Crackle, Pop.
Solid.
Wait.
Is this prenup
in any way legit?
I mean, so far,
it sounds a lot like
that bar napkin document you
make one-night stands sign,
promising not to get clingy.
The Pre-Shtup, patent pending.
God, I come up with
a lot of good stuff!
Anyway, I realize
these aren't just terms
for divorce, so I ask...
Are these rules for how I have
to behave in our marriage?
Rules?
Suggestions.
Rich people and celebrities
put stuff like this
in their prenups all the time.
And those are
the marriages that last.
I have to pay $2,000
every time I gain a pound?
Not every time.
Just if it shows up
at the weekly weigh-in.
See, you can't do that.
"Miss Garvey must invent 12 new
sexual positions per year,
"at least ten of which
involve her doing all
or most of the work."
You definitely can't do that.
Hm-mm.
"Miss Garvey's breasts must be
enhanced every five years
or 50,000 honka-honkas,
whichever comes first."
That's actually not bad.
I'll allow it.
That's repulsive.
And, sidebar:
why do men think
women like to be
honka-honka'd?
What woman wants her breasts
squeezed like a seal horn?
Um... totally.
Lily like-a-like-a
the honka-honka.
"All hair below the neck
must be removed weekly."
Hey, you're gonna be thanking me
for that hair loss
during the weigh-in.
"Miss Garvey's parents
may stay at our place
as long as they like."
Well, at least that one's nice.
"Provided they
each arrive in an urn."
"Wives two through eight will
make a weekly chore wheel."
I'm sorry, I borrowed
a few sections
from a prenup I did
for a Saudi Arabian sultan.
I'll cross out
the extra wives stuff.
Unless...
Cross it out.
My God! What the hell
does Barney think
marriage is going
to be like, anyway?
Just a healthy,
modern-day marriage,
based on mutual respect
between two equals.
Ready for your wake-up
lap dance, Master?
Aren't you forgetting something?
Oh, my God, it's 9:00 a.m.
Legally mandated morning
pillow fight time!
Best husband ever.
Best husband ever. Aw.
Best husband e...
Sorry, sorry, we crossed
out the wives
two through eight stuff. Unless...
Nope.
Okay.
Don't worry. I crossed it out.
I didn't really cross it out.
I can hear you.
I'll cross it out.
I didn't really cross it out.
Hey, hey...
Hey, guys, what's up?
Oh, Quinn's pissed because
Barney wants her
to sign a crazy prenup.
But is it really crazy?
Yes. Well, I'm new to this
but guessing yes.
Okay, look.
Did I go...
a speck of sand,
a fairy eyelash,
a unicorn whisper
too far?
Perhaps.
But can you tell me
there's nothing
in any of your relationships
you'd want to change?
No behavior you'd
want to outlaw?
No terms you'd
want to renegotiate?
Look me in the eye
and tell me I'm crazy.
You're crazy.
But a funny thing
happened that night.
Look, I'm not saying
he's right, but
Barney does have
a little bit of a point.
But on this one, he may have
a point. I mean, look...
the idea of renegotiating
the terms of the relationship,
that's valid.
No.
There isn't anything
about you
that I'd want to change.
Well, okay,
maybe a couple of things.
Like what?
And just like that...
one of these four couples
would break up
the very next day.
Okay, it wasn't Lily
and Marshall.
One of these three couples
would break up
the very next day.
What happened?
So last night
Nick was all like,
"Barney has a point
"about renegotiating the terms
of the blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah."
Yeah, and Marshall
was all like, "Uh, I want
to blah, of the blah,
uh, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah."
If I shut my eyes
it's like they're here.
They're just using
Barney's prenup
as a way to complain about us.
I'm just saying, you've
forbidden certain things
that I might like to revisit.
Marshall, you're not going
on a Sasquatch hunt
in Oregon
with a bunch of loonies.
Loonies?
Those brave, bearded men and
women are crypto-zoologists,
and they deserve the respect
that title commands.
But that's not what
I was thinking of.
You're too precious
with the baby.
Okay,
when we first came home
with Marvin,
there was a bad moment.
Welcome home, buddy.
Was it really that high?
I don't know. I was hormonal.
And suddenly, this primal,
protective mother voice
came out of me.
Actually, it was two voices.
I seriously think one
was coming from my vagina.
Never do that again!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is the big deal?
My brothers and my dad
used to roughhouse with me
all the time.
Welcome home,
Marshall.
Hi. Boys...
go long.
Stop!
Not in the house.
That's how lamps break.
Now go pass
that baby around outside.
Oh, fumble!
And I turned out
perfectly fine.
Marshall, this morning
you thought a ghost
made your toast.
I didn't put
the bread in.
You didn't put the bread in.
You know what?
I will play with my son
however I see fit.
And you know what else?
You can honka-honka
yourself tonight.
Barney's prenup
ruined my night, too.
Okay, uh, what behavior
of mine don't you like?
I'm talking about the TV thing.
Okay, the TV thing
is an argument
from, like,
three weeks ago.
Mmm.
Uh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Didn't realize it
takes 42 inches
to keep you satisfied.
The TV happened
to be on.
I happened to glance at it.
Does that make me so weird?
No.
Not at all.
Thank you.
I may be a little weird.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
I get...
turned on
watching myself
do the news during sex.
Yeah, that's a little weird.
Look, seeing myself
on TV makes me feel
confident and sexy.
And that is nothing to be
ashamed of, right, sisters?
Never speak of this.
Ever.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
There's more.
Wait.
So when you're doing the news
live at 7:00,
you wink to future you
watching the rebroadcast
at 11:00?
Maybe.
Never speak of this.
Ever!
You won't believe
what Ted did last night.
You said you were
happy to help him out.
Well, now
I'm changing my mind.
Sorry to interrupt, roomie,
but I am trying
to make sausage.
Where do you keep
your pig intestines?
What's your ex-fiancé
doing at Ted's?
Klaus came to me
a few weeks ago.
Since we broke up,
he lost his job,
he got evicted.
He's miserable.
I'm so sorry.
If I could just take
a quick whore's bath
in your kitchen sink,
then I will skedaddle.
Oh, Klaus, I wish that
there was something
I could do to help.
There is,
little lady.
I've got a guest room.
You'll stay here
till you're back on your feet.
Are you sure?
This is your apartment.
Shh.
Think of this as our apartment.
Oh...
Hero Ted.
He loves that move.
Yeah, for about five minutes,
then he gets hero's remorse.
Danke schon, roomie.
I will go get my things.
Das is super-duper-duper.
My ferrets will be so happy.
They have been living
in an airport locker for weeks.
Here comes papa,
children.
I'll admit,
there have been a
few awkward moments.
You are going to love this.
This is the popular
German situational-comedy,
Strange Compatriots.
Here we come.
Ooh. Here's the thing
about this show, okay?
One of them is very neat
und the other one
is very, very neat.
Oh, Fritz,
kommen sie hier.
Ah, Fritz...
It's time to give Klaus
"das boot."
Klaus?
Wait, can-can you hear us
through the wall?
Yes, I can hear you.
I hear everything.
That's it.
Klaus, get in here!
For God's sake.
I want you out
of my apartment.
You, those ferrets
and all five newborns.
Six and counting.
Mama is still going.
It is like a clown car.
Suddenly, it wasn't
our apartment anymore.
I had no say
in the matter.
These guys are unbelievable.
You know what,
I am gonna go home
and watch the news
all by myself.
Wait.
I have an idea.
You know what?
I'm on board
with the whole prenup thing.
That's great.
It's here to protect you,
too, sweetie...
from becoming unappealing to me.
Actually, I made my own prenup
with a little help.
Ladies?
Go ahead and sign.
It's all pretty standard.
This might not be the
best time to ask...
I'm sort of getting
back in the game.
The redhead with the baby,
what's her situation?
"In the event of divorce,
Miss Garvey shall get
full custody
of Mr. Stinson's suits"?
Why?
What would you do with them?
Nothing. I'd just sit around
and watch them go out of style.
That is just sick.
Keep reading.
"Mr. Stinson
is allowed to attend
any function
at the Playboy Mansion."
Well, at least that's nice.
"Provided he arrives in an urn."
Gentlemen, just in time.
What are you bitches doing here?
Lily.
Oh, he's napping.
It's the only time
I get to go blue.
Barney texted us that you
guys were ganging up on him.
So we're just here to ensure
he doesn't sign anything
he'll regret.
I'm sorry,
I don't think anyone here
other than me is a lawyer.
A well-paid,
successful lawyer.
I-I'm a lawyer.
Actually, we worked together
for years.
Back off, stretch,
I saw her first.
Hang on a second.
"A half million dollar fine
"any time Mr. Stinson can't
'rise to the occasion,'
cue sad slide whistle sounds"?
Hey, what's this
about a shock collar?
Ah, yes, we'll explain.
Miss Garvey has
many attractive friends
who will come to visit.
May I offer you
goat cheese puff
pastries I made, mistress?
As long as you can
do it quietly.
Wait, I'm confused.
If it's not around my neck,
then where's the shock collar?
Oh, God.
It's more
of a shock ring, really.
Her idea.
Little missy
is packing a brain, too.
Okay, you know what?
Since we're all pitching in,
may I suggest a provision?
In the event
that you have a son,
Mr. Stinson is free
to play with his child
however he sees fit.
How about forbidding
your future husband
from spiking his child
into his crib?
How about a clause protecting
you from having to engage
in a three-way with her
and whatever's on basic cable?
Oh, yeah?
How about forbidding...
I got nothing.
How about a provision barring
any nudist German ex-fiancés
from slapping his strudel up
and down your sofa?
How about pretending
to be a hero,
but then caving the moment
a ferret bite breaks the skin?
The skin of my eyelid.
That's how they kiss.
Are you serious?
Enough! Enough!
You all have someone
who loves you,
and you're screwing it up,
and over what?
Who has the most power?
That's not love.
Love is trusting
someone enough
to tell them
what's really bothering you.
So that's what we're gonna do.
You, start.
When you got scared
about Marvin,
it felt like
you were saying that
I'm not as good a parent as you.
You're an amazing mom,
and I want to live up to that.
Well, I probably have
trust issues
because my dad
wasn't there for me.
But I know that you'll always
be there to catch Marvin.
You, next.
Having Klaus back in our lives
made me scared we're never
gonna escape the past.
I only wanted to help Klaus
because I feel guilty
about how happy I am with you.
Next.
I find you so sexy,
it just hurt that you don't
feel the same about me.
I get turned on watching myself
do the news during sex.
Oh.
Well, that's cool.
Look at that,
no legal documents needed.
Just honesty and vulnerability.
That's love.
You see, I once loved someone,
only I didn't say it enough.
Now I wish I could
say it every day.
Hell,
I don't care if it's crazy,
I-I'm doing it.
Hello, Darlene?
Put Tugboat on the line.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, it's the man.
And for a moment,
all felt right with the world.
But that very night,
the Autumn of Breakups
would claim its first victims.
...wish you a very safe
and pleasant evening.
Good night.
Gute Nacht.
And you too, my babies.
Oh, danke for the sweet
eye kisses.
Ow.
After you, sir.
Ladies first.
I insist.
I'm not throwing mine out first.
You've slept
with half the women in New York.
I'm the one who needs a prenup.
You duped me out of
thousands of dollars.
I'm the one who needs a prenup.
I just thought
of some more stuff to add.
I'm not half finished.
Let's dive in.
It should be simpler than this,
shouldn't it?
Yeah.
Maybe it should be.
Barney, do you trust me?
No.
Do you trust me?
If we really need something
this complicated
to get married...
Yeah.
* I was anxious to be found *
* You can always go home *
* To the safety of your cloud. *
I'm sorry, buddy.
Hey, there's always
wives two through eight.
They sounded pretty hot
in your fantasy.
All but wife seven.
She was just there
'cause her dad was rich.
Actually, I'm okay.
I found out I'll never trust
someone enough to get married,
and that's fine.
My single life is,
and always will be,
legen... wait for it...
...dary!
My wedding
is gonna be legendary.
So, prenup?
Not this time.
Oh, hey you.
Ready for lunch?
Totally.
Mmm.
Thanks.
See, Tugboat?
That's love.
Yeah.
Okay, you see, Ludwig has
started to polish the doorknobs,
but Wilhelm has
already completed this chore.
Yeah.
Ahh...
You know,
it's big comedy,
but you also really care
about these characters.
Wilhelm!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net