different, not different?
married--
it's the same. mostly.
except i think i might
be getting carpal tunnel.
my hand keeps
cramping up.
i thought the whole point
of getting married was
that you didn't have
to do that anymore.
no, it's from writing
all the thank you notes.
mostly.
yeah.
you're writing
constantly.
there's forms we
have to sign,
our death folders,
thank you notes.
whoa, whoa.
what are death folders?
it's this thing they
recommend you do
in case one spouse
dies unexpectedly.
it's all
the information
your spouse might need
all in one convenient
location.
lily:
yeah.
account info,
important addresses,
a letter to the
other person.
all that stuff.
i'll get the next round.
thanks.
i am such a jerk.
yeah.
wait, why?
i didn't know that i was
supposed to write a letter.
all lily's gonna find
in that folder are a bunch
of bank statements
and a funny list of things to do
with my ashes.
marshall brownies.
number six.
yeah.
oh, god, i am a bad husband.
no, uh, no, i'll just write,
i'll write lily a letter
tonight, everything'll be fine.
that's right.
unless...
you die between
now and then.
ooh.
but...
come on, that's never
gonna happen.
yes!
if there's one thing
we can state
with absolute certainty
it's that marshall eriksen
is not going to die
before writing
that letter.
barney:
no way at all.
in fact, i dare god
to smite down this
perfectly healthy...
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
i get it.
okay, you guys know
i'm a little superstitious,
and you guys are trying
to freak me out.
well, guess what?
it didn't work.
so, there.
you guys are jerks!
captioning sponsored by
20th century fox television
cbs
and volkswagen.
when you get into a volkswagen,
it gets into you.
ted:
kids, after robin
and i broke up,
she needed some time away.
away from her normal home,
her normal life,
and it turns out,
her normal self.
i was just so uptight
in new york, you know?
i mean down here everybody
shares everything.
it's like we're all one big
shimmering ball
of positive energy.
i wonder if anyone's ever
thought that before.
here.
eat.
if we run out of fish,
i will catch more
with my hands.
(drums playing)
a drum circle!
they're different
every time.
let's go watch!
and here i am
at the drum circle.
whoa, are you topless?
ted, check this out.
seen 'em.
wow, it seems
like a great trip.
oh, it was.
i feel like
the robin who left
is not the same robin
who came back, you know.
wow, there's a lot
of nude people in here.
you haven't changed,
scherbatsky.
you're a sophisticated,
scotch-swilling,
cigar-smoking,
red-meat-eating,
gun-toting new yorker.
just shoes
and a shirt.
that's a look.
what you are not is
a massage-giving,
windsurfing,
bongo-playing,
teetotaling, vegan,
peacenik, hippy
like you soon to be
ex-boyfriend, gael.
back me up here, ted.
i'm just happy
robin's happy.
thank you.
lily:
man,
this is like a
"where's waldo"
of exposed genitalia.
except that it's really
easy to find waldo.
i'm evolved...
and i'm enjoying
living my life
a little bit closer
to the way gael
and i did
in argentina.
please.
vacation romances have
an expiration date.
gael's got a "best if
banged by" sticker on him.
once your romance
starts to stink,
you'll dump his ass
down the drain
like sour milk
and go back to being
"unevolved robin,"
the one we actually like.
back me up here, ted.
i'm just happy
robin's happy.
i'm telling you,
within three days...
ooh, here he comes.
switched to big words.
within a triad
of solar periods,
you'll recognize your dearth
of compatibility
with your paramour
and conclude your association.
my journey
was transformative.
and i reassert
my commitment
to both
the aforementioned paramour
and the philosophies
he espouses.
what are we
talking of?
baseball?
this is all gonna return to
masticate you in the gluteals.
support my hypothesis, ted.
i'm just jubilant my former
paramour's jubilant.
to write the letter
he hoped lily would never have
to read.
"my dearest,
sweetest, lily pad.
"let this letter
be a small beacon,
"a tiny firefly
to help light your way
"through the years ahead.
"my love for you persists
"higher than
the himalayas.
deeper than
a scottish loch."
(sobbing)
"if i died under suspicious
circumstances,
"then beware.
"trust no one.
not even ted."
"especially not ted."
"know that i'll always
be there in your heart
"whenever you need me,
"and that my love for you
will never die.
"love...
(sobbing)
your marshmallow."
(inhales sharply)
"m.
"atm pin code:
5-4-5-9.
"teacher's pension
account:
"a-3-9-3-2.
"cancel vogue.
l."
my windsurfing board...
it had floated away.
and the shark...
he was getting closer.
they say to escape
you punch a shark
in the nose.
but i said,
"brother shark,
we are both children
from the same
earth mother."
(sighs)
and that's all i remember
until the hospital.
that guy.
yeah.
look at how easy
he has it.
you and me, we have
to bend over backwards
to get a woman to, well,
bend over backwards.
but that guy...
every woman in the bar
is hanging
on his every slightly
mispronounced word.
and why?
he's better
looking than us.
no.
because he's from
out of town.
mmm.
with and accent
and an innocent smile,
you don't even
have to try.
yeah.
plus automatic out,
you're leaving in
a couple of days.
god, i wish we
were tourists.
yeah.
actually...
you know where i've been
meaning to visit?
(camera shutter clicking)
okay, okay, we're
from a small town
in the south
of france.
our plane leaves
sunday morning.
(with southern accent):
uh, hey, uh, howdy, ladies.
hate to bother you.
we seem to be
a little bit lost.
would you happen to know
which street
the statue
of liberty's on?
actually,
it's on its own island.
oh!
oh, it's right...
ah.
thank you very...
uh, my name is, uh,
ignatius peabody nobel.
from east westerton,
missouri.
and this is
my friend, ted.
hi, um, i'm colleen.
hi, colleen.
this is lindsay.
hi, lindsay.
so, hey,
you-you-you ladies,
been awful nice to us.
what do you say...
ah, never mind.
no...
no, what is it?
well...
it's just we're leaving
sunday morning.
it sure would be nice to
have some real new yorkers
show us around.
yeah.
well, we're busy
tonight, but...
maybe tomorrow
afternoon?
after lunch?
well, hotdog!
should we...
you want to just
meet here
in front of mac...
maclaren's pub?
it's kind of a
lame bar, but sure.
really? it doesn't
seem that lame to me.
it's pretty lame.
i think it's cool.
we'll see you
tomorrow.
barney:
all right.
i'm just saying it seems like
a kind of bar
a lot of cool people
would ng out at.
okay, all right.
so, gael, huh?
mmm.
still going strong?
yeah, it's great.
amazing, fantastic, awesome.
ooh, that's one too many.
what's going on?
well, now that i'm home,
i'm finding myself
getting annoyed
at things that i loved
on vacation.
here, taste.
experience your food.
oh.
so good.
here, taste.
experience your food.
ooh, sofa,
ooh, sofa.
sofa, sofa, oh.
(grunts)
ooh.
we're alone now.
i must have you.
(laughs)
(moans)
ooh.
i must have you.
laptop, laptop, laptop!
(sighs)
and you know
what else?
i'm still finding sand
everywhere.
i mean, we haven't been
to the beach since argentina.
where is all coming from?
well, maybe you're just
going back
to the person you were
before the trip.
but i don't want to.
i was so happy down there.
no, you know what?
i'm done complaining.
i'm evolving.
just gonna
go with the flow.
wow.
gael, you're peeing
while i'm in the shower.
okay.
okay, old robin would have been
like, dude, ocupado.
but now, you know what,
i'm cool with it.
pee it up.
in fact,
when you're done, why don't you
come in here and join me?
don't mind if i do, love.
(screams)
gael, there's some weird du...
hello.
hey!
good news!
i made some new traveling
friends today,
and they'll be staying with us,
how do you say...
indefinitely!
all:
g'day!
bp
ooh, here.
will you sign
this thank you note?
wow.
both sides.
you wrote on
both sides of a thank you note
to my third cousin
for a blender that you haven't
even taken out of the box.
wow, that's...
it's a really nice blender.
well, if you love
that blender so much,
why don't you just marry it.
i can't.
i married you.
that's how we go the blender.
what's wrong?
nothing.
nothing's wrong.
what could be wrong?
except that when you die
i'm gonna find out
that your parting words
to comfort me for all eternity
were "cancel vogue."
how can you
open my letter?
that was not a letter.
it was barely even
a text message.
next time you
write something
that short, at least have
the courtesy to make it rhyme.
marshall, wait.
this was our first fight
as a married couple.
oh, baby.
oh...
oh.
kids, there are a thousand
amazing places you can find
only in new york city.
instead of any of those,
colleen and lindsay
took us here.
colleen:
this is our favorite restaurant
in the city.
yes, i'm sure
this is the best
of their 57 "spudtacular"
east coast locations.
i'm going to run
to the restroom.
i'm gonna go, too.
(growls)
(ted groans, barney laughs)
this is the easiest date ever.
you know
what i'm gonna try next?
a knock, knock joke.
easiest?
somehow we have managed
to find the two lamest
new yorkers of all time.
ted, ted, ted.
dude,
i am looking at you.
what?
right.
stay with me.
we are on the cusp of moving
from out-of-towners
to in-their-pantsers.
ay-o.
all right,
ignatius,
one more hour.
nice.
nice. hey, nice.
hey...
hey, our friends
invited us to a party.
you guys want
to come along?
knock, knock.
who's there?
yes, we do.
(all laughing)
(cheering on television)
quick announcement.
i am
so glad that you're here,
fellow travelers.
a couple rules--
not even rules.
let's call them guidelines
for harmonious living.
guideline
for harmonious living
number one--
the kitchen sink is for dishes,
the toilet is for pee-pee.
g.f.h.l.
number two--
marijuana is illegal
in the united states,
even when baked
into a blueberry muffin
that someone might mistakenly
eat for breakfast
right before they leave for
their job as a tv newscaster.
"this just in:
look at my hand,
how weird is my hand?"
is not an appropriate thing
to say on the air.
and number three, i...
(all cheering)
and number three is please keep
the noise to a minimum.
i have to take a nap.
i'm still pretty baked.
(gasps)
everything's so bright,
even at night.
no wonder
the city never sleeps.
(barney and women laughing)
hey, if we're
going north,
why did we cross over the fdr?
we should have taken the hudson.
(scoffing):
now he knows
all the streets.
someone's been watching
too many steinfeld reruns.
(women laughing)
(laughs sarcastically)
where are we even going anyway?
148th and
brook avenue.
a hundred-- in the south bronx
at this time of night?
we're going to get killed.
ted, i think
these local new yorkers
know more about the city
than we do, so relax.
we're in very capable hands.
(siren wails)
there were three of them,
at least two guns--
they took all
oumoney.
well, i only had
traveler's checks.
hey, babe.
i've been thinking
about our fight.
yes?
i'm really, really...
surprised that you haven't
apologized to me yet.
wow, you really want
to open this up again.
oh, i forgot,
you open everything up,
even if you're not supposed to
until i'm dead.
you know that this
is important to me.
why won't you just
write the letter?
because i can't bear the
thought of not being with you,
not even for long enough
to write you a stupid letter.
really?
yes, really.
plus, i know
as soon as i write it,
you're just going to open
it up and read it again.
lily, i won't,
i promise.
okay.
i'll write you a letter
for my death folder.
do you mind, um,
maybe slipping
in a little bit of
dirty stuff, too?
i tell you what.
how about i make it
all dirty stuff
and slip in
a little clean stuff?
you're the best.
and maybe a
couple polaroids?
come on,
let's get out of here.
this night's a disaster.
what?!
this night couldn't
have gone any better.
we just survived
a mugging.
you know what
that means.
"thank god we're alive" sex.
"thank god we're
alive" sex.
it's even better
than "i can't believe you
just proposed to me" sex,
which i've only had,
like, four or five times.
ted, please, we
are so close.
all right, i'm in.
i've never worked this hard
for anything in my life.
whew!
wow, i think
we all need
to go back to our place
and recover.
yeah.
i just want
to celebrate
the fact that
we survived.
you know?
mm-hmm.
me, too.
so where do
you live?
what, west village?
close.
west orange.
west orange,
new jersey?
yeah.
you guys live in new jersey,
not new york?
theodore.
yep.
new jersey?
teddy.
yeah, but don't worry,
it's pretty much new york.
ted:
oh.
no.
oh, no.
new jersey is not
"pretty much new york."
you are not
"pretty much new yorkers."
and how would
you know?
because i live here.
that's right,
i live here.
yes, we're full of crap.
yes, we pretended
to be from out of town
so we could sleep with you
and leave in the morning.
but you know what's
even worse than that?
saying you're a new yorker
when you're not.
because this is the
greatest city in the world
and you have to earn the right
to call yourself a new yorker.
so why don't
you girls crawl
into the open sewer pipe
you call the holland tunnel
and flush yourselves back
to "pretty much new york"?
because i
will do a lot
to get laid,
but i am not going
to new jersey!
(huffs)
(in accent):
you're not from missouri?
well, i will be
a monkey's unc...
ew.
right.
can we get
a ride?
hey, um, sir,
can we get
a ride, too?
newark, born and raised.
(drumming)
(sighs)
can you please keep it down?
what happened to you, man?
you said you wouldn't
change, but look at you.
no more tan,
no more beaded braids,
no more lush,
untamed forest
of leg and armpit hair.
you're back
at work.
what gives?
well, i have
to have a job.
"i have to have a job."
god, that's so american.
i'm canadian.
you know that.
what about the important things
like making your own jewelry
and lying
on the beach
and thinking about peace?
god, don't
you care
about thinking about peace?
wow.
i just realized something.
that you've
lost your way.
no,
that you really suck.
you're boring and me
and you're getting sand
everywhere.
seriously, where is
all the sand coming from?
you're not the real me.
all you are is me on vacation
trying to get away
from a break-up.
don't you remember argentina?
don't you want
to go back?
what are you doing?
shh...
let this happen.
(robin gasps, drumming)
all right, everyone out.
i said everyone out!
(frustrated growl)
(drumming stops,
panicked shouting)
all right, we're leaving,
we're leaving, okay.
michael moore was so right
about americans.
i'm canadian!
robin,
you okay?
no, i'm not.
listen, gael,
i need to talk to you
about something.
after they broke up,
robin went back to being robin.
(sighs)
welcome home, scherbatsky.
oh, good to be back.
although it's weird.
vacation robin popped into
my dream again last night.
listening.
this time we went all the way.
tell you
one thing.
->1
wñw?
okay, i'm done..
but i really don't want you
reading this unless...
you know, something happens.
can you swear to me
you won't open it?
totally. what does it say?
marshall, i'm serious.
okay.
i promise i won't, i won't
open that until you're dead.
(quietly):
okay.
and through 22 wonderful years
of marriage,
marshall kept his promise
until november 1 of last year
when, sadly...
"busted! i knew
you'd read this.
you suck, marshall,
you totally suck."
that's it?
i suck?
lily.
yes, you suck.
you said you wouldn't read it
and you did.
well, you didn't keep
your promise either.
i don't see any dirty pictures
in here.
oh, fine,
i'll take the dirty pictures.
i don't want 'em now.
what is that supposed to mean?
what?!
nothing.
you're beautiful.
i would love
the photos.
have i told you how
beautiful you look?
www.tvsubtitles.net