Now kids, when aunt Robin
was a teenager,
she was, well,
a Canadian pop star.
But by 2008, she was
an entirely different person...
Coming up next:
Is your baby trying to kill you?
...which made the events of that week
all the more surprising.
So, I go in this morning and,
brr, it's freezing!
So I walk over there, and
I don't know why I'm still talking,
because clearly, we're all
asking the same question,
What in God's creation
is going on with Robin's breasts?
I know! Right?
Isn't it amazing?
I spent half an hour
making this happen.
There's tape in there,
cotton balls,
half of a Nerf football,
but it works, right?
Totally.
What's the occasion?
And old friend from Canada is in town
and I'm meeting him for a drink.
Somebody you went
to Degrassi with?
No. Actually,
he was my first boyfriend.
Simon. I thought he was
the coolest guy ever.
He smelled like Drakkar.
He could ollie on a skateboard.
And he had the most amazing collection
of Hard Rock Café T-shirts.
We spent the whole summer
madly in love.
Tell me more.
Like, did he have a car?
So he's the guy who...
How shall I say this
like a gentleman?
Robin, did he take
your maple leaf?
No, it wasn't like that.
Sounds to me like he gave you
your first "O, Canada!" face.
This went on
for a really long time.
Some of them jokes
were elegant and well-crafted...
Wait, wait. Did he break up with you
and tell you he's just not that Inuit?
...others were crude,
and ill-formed...
Um, something about fur trapping.
...and others were obvious,
but needed to be said...
Did you ride his Zamboni?
Wait, wait, wait.
Did he...?
I think I'm out.
Yeah, I'm also "oot."
Okay, now I'm really out.
Well, I'm sorry, guys.
It was all very tame.
We only dated for
a week and a half.
I thought you said
you were together all summer.
Yeah. Summer in Canada is
pretty much the last week of July.
Anyway, one night, his band
just finish playing this gig...
Oh, my God! Simon.
That was such a good show.
You guys totally rocked out.
Yeah. I know.
I figure we're about four or five gigs
away from really exploding.
We're gonna be big, babe.
I mean,
like Crash-Test-Dummies big.
- So, that everything?
- Yeah.
Listen, babe...
It's over.
What?
I'm getting back together
with Louise Marsh.
Louise Marsh?!
That's a whore's name
if I ever heard one.
Yeah, why would he want to get back
together with Louise Marsh?
Well, the thing is...
her folks just put in a pool.
Totally... I get it.
Pools are great.
Swimming's awesome.
We have a sprinkler.
Run right through it.
Well, I should go.
Babe, wait.
Yeah, Simon?
You forgot to load
the drum set.
Tell me you did not
load the drum set.
I did.
And now he's coming here?
Robin,
why do you want
to see this guy?
Oh! I know why.
You're gonna win,
aren't you?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Yes, you do. Whenever you haven't
seen someone for a long time,
no matter how much you want
to deny it, there's always
a clear winner
and a clear loser.
Well, since you brought it up,
let's add up the points.
You're starting out
with two big ones right there.
Thank you. Okay.
So, Simon still lives
with his mom.
Point Robin.
He never became
a rock star.
Point Robin.
He now works at a water slide
park outside of Ottawa.
- Point Simon.
- Wait.
- Do they have a wave pool?
- No.
Ah. Point Robin.
That's five-zip.
There's no coming back from that.
Yeah, he's going down. I mean,
unless somehow, he got hotter.
There he is.
And sure enough,
there was a clear winner,
and a clear loser.
It just wasn't clear
to everybody.
Hey, babe.
Oh, my God.
How I Met Your Mother 3x16
- Sandcastles In The Sand -
Okay, what the hell
just happened?
Oh, come on,
it wasn't so bad, was it?
- Hey, Simon.
- Wow, look at you.
You got old.
Yeah. You look great.
You got hotter,
like that's possible.
Look, I know it didn't go
as planned, but,
I can't help it.
I mean...
he's still got it.
Whoa! Four bucks for a brew?
What a rip.
Good think I'm packing.
So he's not a snob.
He's from a different part
of Canada, you know?
The maple leaf flag
on the back of the pickup truck?
He's Red Province.
He's from the Deep North.
The thing is, we gave you
so many opportunities.
So, Simon, Robin's a bit of a local
celebrity here in New York.
She's the lead anchor
at Metro News One.
- Tell him, Robin.
- No. It's stupid.
It's not cool,
like Simon's shirt.
I'm sorry, Simon. Here we are
nattering on about our big celebrity.
What do you do for a living?
Oh, I work at the Splish Splash
Ottawa Water Slide Park.
A water slide park. That sure is
different than what Robin does.
Yeah, it is...
because I save lives.
If I'm not sitting in that stool
at the top of the slide, going...
Go...
people die.
What, you think
it's so easy?
You try it.
- Go.
- You didn't put your hand up
kid just died.
- No, I didn't know...
- Another kid just went,
he died too.
Oh, well, sure.
I mean, if I was actually...
Another kid just went,
now you've got a pile-up and Robin's
got something to report on the news.
This just in: My friend, Ted,
just killed a bunch of kids today.
Well, that's cool.
You got to pay the bills somehow
since your whole music thing
didn't really pan out, did it?
Well, it hasn't panned out yet,
but the band's still going.
About four or five gigs away
from really exploding.
The Foreskins are still playing?
The Foreskins?
How'd you guys come up
with that name?
Well, there's four of us,
and we play without shirts.
Babe, seriously.
I know. I'm sorry.
But you guys just don't understand.
The fact that he kept
the band going...
that's impressive.
I mean, I gave up
my musical dream.
Which brings us to the most important
piece of information from tonight.
So, Simon,
how did you guys meet?
Oh, I was in her video.
Starred in it is more like it.
Once you win Mr. Teen Winnipeg,
everybody wants a piece
of the moneymaker.
I'm sorry. I've seen "Let's Go to
the Mall" about a thousand times,
- and you, sir, are not in it.
- No, I was in the other one.
There's another video?!
Robin, seriously,
just make this easier on yourself
and give us the tape.
All right.
You give me no choice.
From this moment on,
I will spend every waking minute
searching down this tape.
I will not sleep.
I will not eat.
My life will be a living hell of search
engines and overseas phone calls,
chasing down something
that possibly can't be found.
Okay.
It's just... It was so hard to watch,
Robin. You're usually so cool.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm sitting next to Simon,
and suddenly I'm 16 again.
Oh, it's actually a common thing. When
you're around someone from your past,
you kind of revert back to
who you were when you knew them.
There's not really
a name for it, though.
It's called "revertigo."
Yeah, I don't know
about "revertigo."
You know who gets
really bad revertigo?
Lily when she around
her high school friend, Michelle.
Michelle? She sounds hot.
You don't know
about Lily and Michelle?
No. What about Lily and Michelle?
Oh, my friend,
you are in for a treat.
- Hey, Lil?
- What?
You know, I was just thinking, we haven't
seen your friend Michelle in a while.
Oh, yeah. I'll give her a call,
see if she wants to hang out.
What...
Do they make out?
Better.
- Comparable.
Whatever.
It's over. I lost.
I guess you, uh,
you don't get second chance.
- I got a second chance.
- What happened?
He came by my place tonight...
Simon.
What are you doing here?
I just feel like there's some
unfinished business between you and me.
Seeing you now...
has made me realize
that breaking up with you
is the biggest mistake
I made in my entire life.
Oh, I like where this is going.
I know this is crazy,
and I'm only in town
for a couple of days, but,
do you want to go on a date?
He asked you out?!
Oh, step into my web, Simon.
The coup de grace.
Finish him!
I'd love to!
Wait. You're going on
a date with Simon?
That Simon? The one we met?
Robin, this guy doesn't
deserve a second chance.
Not after the way he treated you.
That was ten years ago.
People evolve.
I mean, are you the same person
that you were in high school?
- Oh, hell, no!
- I think you're gonna enjoy this.
That my girl Michelle?
- Bitch, you know it!
- How she livin'?
She living only way she know
how to. Large!
Oh, girl, you gots to get
your drink on up in here.
I'm hoping my fat ass can
hustle me up a vodka-Gatorade.
For reals.
I want her around all the time.
I'd even consider not trying to sleep
with her if that's what it takes.
Guys, I've decided
to seduce Michelle.
Guys, that was great.
Let's take five.
Hey, babe, did you like it after my bass
solo when I flicked my pick at you?
That rocked.
Uh, 'cause I'm gonna need
that pick back.
Oh, uh, sure. Um...
- It's cool. You'll find it later.
- Oh, cool.
I wish I didn't have to go
to work in the morning.
But, babe, you got to go to work.
You got to play our demo
on your show.
Oh, well, you know, it's not
a show. It's the news.
Right. So you can be, like,
"Hey, did you hear there's some news?
There's a rad band you guys
should check out." And then play it.
Or just, like, the first three songs.
And now it's time
for "Puppy Corner,"
some little angels
looking for a new home,
courtesy of
the Midtown Animal Shelter.
# Murder climb aboard
the Murder Train #
Hey, a lot of puppies
got adopted.
Of course, a lot of
the people calling in
thought we were going
to kill them.
Robin, your revertigo is really
starting to affect your work.
What's revertigo?
It's a stupid, made-up word
with no meaning.
No. It's a phenomenon where, when
you're around people from your past,
you start behaving like them.
Oh. One example of that
springs to mind.
I think we all know what it is.
You do?
Yeah. Ted.
Me?
Whenever Ted's friend Punchy
comes into town,
it's like, all of a sudden,
Ted's in high school again.
Okay, okay. First of all, his name is
Adam Punciarello, and I don't do that.
Ooh. That must be Adam.
- 'Sup, Punchy?
- 'Sup, Shmosby?!
- You want to go?
- I'm already there!
- Come on!
- This is it!
Dude, seriously,
I'm sorry about your dad.
Yeah, it was a real shock.
I can't believe you, of all people,
are saying this.
Why?
No reason.
Robin, the point is,
what are you doing?
I mean, this guy?
Okay, you want the truth?
I like Simon.
I do. We have fun together.
We know you do, honey,
but we're worried about you.
You're worried?
Okay, hold on.
Is there any version
of this conversation
where you guys don't sound
like my parents?
I don't know.
Is there any version where
you don't sound like a 16-year-old?
That's exactly what
my mom would say.
No. If I was your mom, I would say,
"We forbid you from seeing this boy."
No, I'm sorry,
but it's for your own good.
This is my life!
You guys just don't get it!
You've never felt the way that I feel!
No, no. We were once young
and in love, too.
Yeah, like, a billion years ago.
You've been drinking,
haven't you?
Yeah, we all have.
You bought the last round.
You're not going
to that show tonight!
Oh, yes, I am,
and you know what else?
Tonight, after the show,
Simon and I are going all the way!
Young lady, get back here!
Thanks for your help.
- Hey, so, today at work...
- Not now, Ted!
Hey, Simon. Great show.
- You guys still rock.
- Yeah.
They totally dug
my bass solo.
Man!
Why can't I always
feel this alive?!
God, I just love
seeing you so happy.
Yeah. About that.
Listen, babe.
It's over.
What?
I'm getting back together
with Louise Marsh.
What?
You're kidding me.
You're breaking up with me?
Again?
F-For the same ex-girlfriend?
In the same van?
What is it?
Her-Her parents got a pool?
Is that still the reason?
Well...
her folks did just
put in a Jacuz.
I'm sorry, Robin.
I'm fine, really.
Oh, Robin, I'm gonna tell you
for real. Simon's a dawg.
- You feel me, Chelle?
- Mm-hmm, for reals.
- He a scrub.
- Mm. True dat.
I'm get me my champagne
and grape soda on.
So, how's Columbia?
Great!
I'm almost done
with my dissertation.
I'm getting a PhD
in behavioral psychology.
Can I make an observation?
I know.
Whenever I'm around Lily,
she just brings out that side of me.
There's a psychological term
for the phenomenon.
- Revertigo?
- No.
Actually, it's associative regression.
You see,
the neural pathways that...
Oh, no, you did not just
put on my jam!
Oh. Put your hands up, girl!
One by one,
we all had to go home.
Soon, it was just Robin.
All right.
I can't find your video.
I've wasted three days tr...
What's the matter?
Simon dumped me
in his van after the show.
Yeah, Robin, that was, like,
ten years ago.
No, tonight.
Really?
Oh, come here.
Come here.
It's just...
when I was young,
I was so...
vulnerable and-and open
to things, you know?
And...
I guess I just...
I wanted to feel
that way again.
I wanted to be 16 again.
Robin,
that is the stupidest thing I've
ever heard come out of your mouth.
You want to be 16 again?
I have watched your first
Robin Sparkles video 1,000 times,
and it's not because
I'm proud of you as a friend.
It's because you were totally,
totally lame back then.
But now, come on. Pa-cow!
You're the most awesome person
I have ever known.
Well, second most awesome.
Right. Of course,
the-the first being you.
No.
No. The first is this guy who
lives in a place called the mirror.
What up.
I'm saying
that you are way more awesome
than Simon ever will be.
Barney, do you want
to come back to my place?
Your place?
- Are you sure you want to do this?
- Yeah. I am.
Let's just not tell anyone
about this, okay?
Of course.
So, should I just put it in?
Yeah, why not?
# Met you at the mall... #
This was my big artistic follow-up
to "Let's Go to the Mall."
It kind of tanked.
# My friends said I was a fool #
- # You're a fool.
- Shut up! #
- Is that Tiffany?
- Mm-hmm.
# 'Cause you were older and
got kicked out of school #
# You are so rad. #
# Together we were
gonna travel the globe #
# From Alberta to Ontario #
It's everything I want it to be
and more.
- Oh, I'm so glad.
- Hmm.
# a sandcastles in the sand #
# Sandcastles in the sand #
# Thought I could fly
when you held my hand #
- # Thought I could fly
- But now... #
# Eternity returns
to black and white... #
- Is that Alan Thicke?
- Yeah.
# It was the greatest
week and a half... #
# Of my life
We used to go to the beach #
You know, if you reedit it, there's
a tampon commercial in here somewhere.
# On our favorite bench #
# We'd sit and talk and
you taught me to french #
# You're good at... #
Do you see how lame
you were back then?
- Yeah, you're right. I was lame.
- Totally lame.
# ...so unfair... #
# You don't understand
about love. #
And, of course, the robot makes an
appearance in the sad love ballad.
He was my sidekick.
He had to be.
And so they watched it again.
# Its crazy, #
# no one gets me #
# Let's go all the way #
#I love you. Let's do it. #
# I miss you. #
And again.
# Sandcastles may be cute
I'm on the pill now. #
# But now... #
And again.
# all they do
is remind me of you... #
They watched it over and over
that night until finally,
they stopped watching.
www.tvsubtitles.net