But by 2008, we'd all had enough.
Well, most of us.
Who wants to kiss
The Barney Stone?
- Look, it's the Riddler.
- That's not the Riddler.
That's Gumby.
Hey, Gumby, can we tie you
in a knot later?
Hey, NBA player sidelined
by a knee injury?
All right, laugh all you want,
but this is my lucky
St. Patty's Day suit.
I have dry-cleaned many
a stain off of this baby.
You know why it's lucky?
'Cause it's green,
the color of go, as in let's.
Uh, Barney, we, uh...
we talked this over, and, uh,
we're not doing
St. Patty's Day this year.
Come on. Let's...
Are you s...
Wow. Okay.
I think I got to lie down.
Can we shoot pool on you?
No! No!
Unacceptable!
That's so not Raven!
What are you gonna do instead?
We just got the keys to
our new apartment,
so we're gonna go over there and
hang up that painting,
have board game night.
You're welcome to join us
if you want.
Board game night?!
Board game night.
Come on!
Let's drink green beer.
Let's do green Jell-O shots!
Where's your St. Patty's Day spirit?!
We're drinking green tea.
With caffeine.
Sorry, Peter.
We're grown-ups now.
We can't fly off to Neverland
with you anymore.
All right, fine.
You know what?
I'll celebrate St. Patty's Day
by myself.
I don't need you people.
You make me physically ill.
He did look a little green.
Hello?
Hey, happy St. Patty's Day!
How are you?
Yeah, I haven't talked to you forever.
- Who is it?
- It's Ted's butt.
Ah, damn it!
My phone keeps pocket-dialing!
That's, like, the eighth time today.
In fairness, I did call Ted's butt at,
like, 2:00 this afternoon.
It took long enough to call you back.
Barney, where are you?
In a cab, heading downtown with our
hot and sexy dates for the evening.
Yes, it happens that fast!
We're going to that club Low Point,
and you're coming with us.
Barney, for the last time...
All right, I didn't want to tell you
this in front of Marshall
and Lily because they're old
and married,
and it's too late for them anyway,
but Ted,
the world is going to come
to an end tonight.
Yes. Think about it.
End of the world, Nostradamus.
Notre Dame.
Fighting Irish.
Irish.
St. Patrick's Day.
This is it, bro.
Bro-pocalypse Now.
Bromageddon.
Ted, you are young, you're single.
You'll have so much more fun with me.
Do you really want to spend
your last night on
Earth playing board games
with Marshall and Lily?
My hands smell weird.
Smell this.
Yeah, they do.
That's new.
I'll be there in five minutes.
Yes! All right!
He's in! Ted's a great guy.
Y...
You're gonna love him.
So on March 17, 2008,
I went to a big St. Patrick's Day party.
And it's a good thing I did,
because, funny story:
your mother was there.
How I Met Your Mother 3x12
- No Tomorrow -
Hi. Have you met Ted?
Hi. I'm Mary.
Hi. Happy St. Patty's Day.
I haven't met Ted, either.
- I'm Stephanie.
- Hi.
Dude, back off.
I called dibs on Stephanie.
Okay. Mary's hot.
Well, then I want Mary.
Fine.
Oh, I see.
Reverse psychology.
Then I'm sticking with Stephanie,
Dr. Freud.
Okay.
- Which one do you want more?
- Either one.
- I want them both.
- You're an idiot,
and it may be a moot point.
I mean, it doesn't look like
we're getting in.
Look at this.
You know why there's a line?
It's because I ditched
Marshall and Lily,
and now the universe is
punishing us for it,
that's why.
Yeah.
What's it gonna cost us to get in, $20?
$40?
Dude, come on, you're making
the wee folk look bad.
Just give him your pot o' gold.
Is it just you two?
Don't worry.
We're not gonna blow your ratio.
We happen to have
two very hot girls with us.
Mine's the hotter one.
Look, if it was just you two,
you could go in right now.
We got nothing
but girls in there.
People are gonna start
thinking it's a lesbian bar.
Would you excuse us for just a minute?
Ted, I'm gonna be honest.
I was full of it with that
whole Nostradamus thing.
No.
But I am starting to think
there is some serious
planetary crap going on here tonight.
Never in the history of
New York City nightclubs
has there been a shortage of dudes,
not even during
the Great Dude Shortage of 1883.
We got to ditch these girls.
But you dragged them all
the way down here.
I don't see no ring
on this finger.
All right, hold on.
Uh, excuse me?
Are the girls in there
hotter than our dates?
I don't know if they're hotter,
but they're drunker.
Rock 'n' roll.
Welcome to your dream home,
my lady.
All right, all right.
You can put me down.
Robin thinks we're weird.
No, it's fine.
It was only weird on the subway.
Oh. I'm gonna check
the other rooms to see
if the previous owners
left us any free stuff.
I'm gonna hang our
first piece of art.
Oh, look, there's already a nail.
Hey, Lil, free nail!
Score!
How's that?
Perfect.
Oh, now this is ridiculous.
Is it the nail?
Marshall?
Is the wall slippery or something?
Marshall.
Is there a wind?
Is there some sort of draft in here?
- Marshall!
- What?
Your apartment's crooked.
What do you mean?
It was the kind of thing
you didn't notice until you noticed it.
But once you did notice it,
you couldn't not notice it.
Lily and Marshall's
new apartment was crooked.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no. Oh, no.
Yes.
Are you telling me that we just spent our
entire life savings and then some on...
on a crooked apartment?
Oh, my God!
No, she's gonna flip.
Just calm down.
It's gonna be fine.
Look what I found in the kids' room!
Free skateboard.
Score!
Free Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Double score!
I'm gonna check the kitchen!
Okay.
How could she not notice this?
It's like the last 20 minutes
of Titanic in here.
We have to keep this quiet.
If Lily finds out her new dream
house is crooked, it's gonna...
it's gonna break her heart.
Free salad strainer!
I love this place.
Just for tonight, okay?
Okay.
But it's gonna be an uphill battle.
I am just saying we have to
think of the right angle.
I have a third one,
but I'm not gonna say it.
Okay, Barney, I think we've stumbled
into some kind of ethical,
philosophical wormhole.
- Green suit.
- Yeah.
I ditched Marshall and Lily,
and was rewarded with
two beautiful girls.
Suit's made of green.
We bailed on those
two beautiful girls,
and now we're being rewarded
with a sea of beautiful girls.
38 long.
It's like the laws of the universe
are working in reverse.
- Can you put it on my tab?
- Yeah. What's the last name?
Garrido.
All right, I'm gonna try something,
and if this works...
Uh, hey.
Hey, what can I get you guys?
A bottle of Dom Perignon,
and can you put it on my tab?
Sure. What's the name?
- Garrido.
- Dude!
Oh, uh, yeah, you're right.
Uh, make it two bottles.
Two.
Now we wait,
see if something good happens...
Oh! Hello!
St. Patrick's Day tradition.
If you're not wearing green,
you got to get pinched.
Well, I guess I got what I deserved.
I'm not wearing green, either.
This is, um, deep teal.
- The lighting makes it...
- Uh, I'm Ted.
Ashlee with two "e"s.
Please. "C"s at most.
You know, you guys should
come join me and my friends.
We have a bottle of tequila and
shockingly deep belly buttons.
Okay, it's official:
do bad things, good things happen.
Ted, listen.
Are you hearing that?
That's the universe.
The universe is talking to us.
We don't have to build
a baseball field, do we?
No. The universe is telling us that
we have a free pass tonight.
The universe is saying that
we don't have to live in fear of the...
- Are you still there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
...of the repercussions of our actions.
There is no waiting for tomorrow,
because do you know why, Ted?
There is no tomorrow.
No tomorrow, huh?
By the way, Mr. Garrido,
second bottle of champagne gets you
a complimentary ounce of caviar.
Enjoy.
- No tomorrow!
No tomorrow!
Hey, I wonder what
the grown-ups are doing right now.
I win again.
Why do I keep winning?
Maybe your hippo is just
hungrier hungrier than ours.
That's it.
That's what it is.
It's not gravity,
that's for sure.
I'll tell you that.
What was that?
What's going on here?
Okay, Lily...
while you were in
the other room, Robin and I,
we discovered something
about the apartment.
It's not a big deal.
It's not like a disaster.
It's just...
It's something that we're going
to have to learn to live with.
Robin and I saw a ghost.
What?
Oh, he's kidding, right?
No, we really saw a ghost.
What did it look like?
Uh, a sheet with two holes in it.
He was a Confederate general
who was wounded at
the Battle of Antietam,
and he died at the army hospital
which once stood on this very spot.
And now he wanders these halls,
vowing revenge against the
Union cannonade hat once felled him.
But he seems nice.
He's a good-good guy.
Marshall, you see ghosts everywhere.
You see ghosts at Stars Bucks.
That Kenny G holiday CD
just flew off the shelf.
Last time that happened.
But, Robin, you're a skeptic,
so if you say you saw a ghost...
It passed right through me,
and suddenly I felt cold,
so very cold.
You know, Ashlee, I'm sorry.
You're probably just gonna want
to get up and walk away,
but I just have to test out
this theory I've been working on.
Tonight, I am not looking
for a relationship.
I really just want to hook up with you,
leave before breakfast,
and never see you again.
I'm in.
Unbelievable.
Hot damn, that's a deep navel.
No tomorrow, Ted.
Yeah, no tomorrow, Barney.
No tomorrow, huh?
I like that idea.
Because if there is a tomorrow,
I'm gonna be in a lot of trouble.
Oh, yeah? Why is that?
I'm married.
Tell me you're messing with me, guys.
You didn't actually see a ghost.
It's not a big deal, baby.
He seemed friendly.
You said he's a Confederate general.
They're the bad guys.
And he's probably racist.
No, he seemed polite.
He had courtly Southern manners.
We're gonna raise our kids here.
I don't want some Confederate general
ghost teaching them his racism.
He loves people of
all colors and creeds.
He was fighting
for states' rights, that's all.
Robin said he was wearing a sheet.
What do you think that means?
The apartment is crooked.
What?
Robin and I didn't see a ghost.
The floor is crooked, isn't it?
Yeah.
We spent our entire life's
savings on this floor.
The next 30 mortgage-paying years
of our lives will be spent
on this floor, and it's crooked.
Thanks a lot, Robin.
How is "racist ghost"
better than "crooked"?
Seriously, somebody tell me
how that's better.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay.
Um, dude, so, I'm having second
thoughts about that theory.
I'm telling you, if you want to know how
old a woman is, check her elbows.
Not that theory.
You have to be more specific, Ted,
'cause I have so many theories.
The whole do bad,
good things happen...
- Ashlee is married.
- So?
What do you mean, so?
Open your brain tank, brah,
'cause here comes some
premium 91 octane knowledge.
There's three rules of cheating:
It's not cheating if you're not
the one who's married,
it's not cheating if her name has
two adjacent vowels,
and it's not cheating if she's from
a different area code.
You're fine on all three counts.
How do you know she's from
a different area code?
She's 516.
She might dress like she's 718,
act like she's 212,
but trust me, she's 516.
Oh, and her husband...
letting her out alone
on Saint Patty's Day?
If that dude's not 973, I'm 307.
Wyoming.
We're gonna have to nail down
all our furniture.
We won't be able to get
a pinball machine.
I mean, unless we put some books under
two of the legs or something.
But then what if we want
to read those books?
This is a nightmare.
We can't raise our kids here.
They'll grow up slanted.
If we have a daughter,
we'll have to call her Eileen.
I don't think we can live here,
Marshall.
I don't know what we're gonna do.
Marshall?
Open the door.
If I make it through the door,
that's five points.
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Five points.
Ten bucks says I can do it backwards.
So Lily and Marshall decided to make
the best of a bad situation.
And that's also how the sport of
Apartment Roller Luge was invented.
Very careful baby!
Oh yeah!
So she's married?
It's not like she has kids.
How do you know?
Wrists.
It's like you don't even listen to me.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Where'd you go?
Well, I just, um...
- Was it something I said?
- No, no, no, it's just, well...
you're married and-and we've been
drinking, and I was worried we might...
Oh, this is a very bad idea.
- We have a problem.
- Hey, hey. Hey.
Hey.
Is this your husband?
I've never seen this man in my life.
Oh, okay.
Uh, what's our problem?
Rick. Rick Garrido.
According to the bartender,
I'm the guy
that's been buying you
champagne all night.
Okay, there's-there's
a very simple explana...
Next thing I know the police show up,
they arrest the other guy,
and I'm drinking for free
the rest of the night.
It was awesome.
Awesome, huh?
Yeah.
You don't see anything wrong
with that story?
Well, I lost my new phone back
at the club somewhere.
What the hell is wrong
with you, dude?
You know me, I lose things.
You kissed a married woman, Ted.
You committed credit card fraud.
You... you kissed a married woman.
Do you know how offensive that is to me?
You're turning into Barney.
We don't need another Barney.
Look...
it's Saint Patty's Day.
It wasn't as bad as it sounds.
- "It wasn't as bad as it sounds"?
- No.
Huh? Okay...
I want you to hear exactly
how it sounds, Ted.
First skipped message:
I don't see no ring on this finger.
And then last night started
coming back to me:
The real version.
Are the girls in there
hotter than our dates ?
I don't know if they're hotter,
but they're drunker.
Rock 'n' roll.
- How many messages did I...
- Seventeen...
Kids, it's sometimes possible to think
you're doing just fine in life...
Next message:
Can you put it on my tab?
Sure, what's the last name?
Garrido.
...and then someone opens
your eyes a little bit,
and you realize...
Next message:
I really want to hook up with you,
leave before breakfast,
and then never see you again.
...your whole world is off balance...
Next message :
...out of whack...
Okay, look, brah,
there is a very simple explana...
...crooked.
That was hard to listen to.
No one likes how they sound
on an answering machine.
Thanks for doing that.
You yelled at me.
You got very firm with me.
Very confident.
It was cool.
Thanks.
- You're very sexy when you yell, Marshall.
- Shut up.
Veins, crazy muscles in your neck.
You look like
a Kentucky Derby-winning steed.
You're ruining a nice moment.
At one point, I swear,
I thought we were gonna kiss.
Ted, seriously.
I'm married.
Oh... a slanted floor.
Architecturally speaking,
fixing that's going to be...
Very, very, very expensive.
And it's gonna take some time, too, so
it looks like you're stuck with us for
a little while longer, if that's okay.
Are you kidding?
I love it.
I don't know what's gonna happen
to me without you guys around.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get my stupid phone.
So that was Saint Patrick's Day, 2008.
I found out years later
that your mom was at that party.
I just didn't meet her.
And it's a good thing I didn't,
'cause if I had met her,
I don't think she would have liked me.
Heck, I don't think I liked me.
But that's okay.
Tomorrow had arrived.
# Leave me alone, and there'll be #
# No one to get hurt #
# Nobody move and there'll be
Nothin' to disturb #
# The sum of it all is that you
Don't know where to turn #
# Despite all your promises you
Don't keep what you learn #
You see, I didn't know it yet,
but my luck was about to change.
# Beautiful beat get me
out of this mess #
I'm awesome!
www.tvsubtitles.net