Back when we were dating
Robin and I have this running joke.
We were the only two people in
the world who found it funny.
No way.
March does not have 31 days.
Yes, it does.
Everyone knows that.
It's like general knowledge.
- General Knowledge.
And we did it all the time.
Isn't it sad?
I mean in 2007,
some countries actually still
condone corporal punishment.
- Corporal Punishment.
Because once you start,
it's surprisingly hard to stop.
Oh, man, I got a kernel
stuck in my teeth.
- Colonel Stuck-In-My-Teeth.
- Please stop!
- I hate you!
But now, we were broken up,
so when Marshall said...
But after the first year,
I get a major pay raise.
We just let it slide.
You see, on the surface, Robin and I
looked like we were doing great.
But the truth is,
trying to be friends with your ex
is a lot harder than it looks.
You can't be as candid
as you used to be.
So then this hot intern
leans over my desk,
I can totally see
she has a pierced...
Brosnan. Pierce Brosnan is my
favorite of all the Bonds.
But most importantly, you can
never, ever be alone together.
- I gotta go.
- I'm gonna go pay.
Peeing.
- I'm gonna help Marshall pay.
- I'm gonna help Lily pee.
How I Met Your Mother 3x09
- Slapsgiving -
All right, we have a turkey.
Yeah, we do.
Isn't this exciting? Our first
Thanksgiving together as a group.
Yeah, this is gonna be
the best Slapsgiving ever.
What?
I said this is going to be
the best Thanksgiving ever.
Yeah, this is going to be great.
Just the five of us, right?
Oh, uh, that reminds me,
I invited Bob.
Bob?
You've been on, like,
three dates with that guy.
We haven't even met him.
Well, he didn't have
anywhere else to go,
and I didn't know what to say.
- Is it really that big a deal?
- Yes.
This is our first Thanksgiving.
30 years from now, we're
going to look at the photos and say,
"Oh, there's the four people
I love most in the world.
And Bob."
I'm sorry, sometimes I forget
how seriously
you guys take
American Thanksgiving.
Real Thanksgiving happened
over a month ago.
I'm sorry.
Did you just say Canadian
Thanksgiving was and I'm quoting,
"the real Thanksgiving"?
What do Canadians even
have to celebrate about?
Canadian Thanksgiving celebrates
explorer Martin Frobisher's valiant yet
ultimately unsuccessful attempt
to find the Northwest Passage.
Why are you guys even a country?
Oh, hey, by the way, if anyone wants
to come over early Thursday,
we can watch the
Slapsgiving Day Parade.
Well, there,
you said it again.
- Said what?
- Slapsgiving.
Oh, I guess I did.
You know why? I've invented
a new holiday: Slapsgiving.
It's the one day we set aside
each year to gather together
and give slaps.
I should explain.
Kids, you remember
the slap bet.
A year earlier, Marshall
made a bet with Barney
and won the right
to slap him five times.
He had already used the first.
And the second.
But Marshall had something
special in store for the third.
Slapcountdown.com.
No, no.
The countdown ends at 3:00 p.m.,
the day after Thanksgiving.
I counted it out.
How many days
are in October?
Uh, thirty.
Dude, I thought
we cleared this up last year.
I like Halloween very much.
Is nice.
- Is also tomorrow.
- Damn it!
Wait, you're gonna slap me
on Thanksgiving?
Slapsgiving.
That's not allowed.
Lily, you're the Slap Bet
Commissioner, is that allowed?
The hostess in me who's using
her wedding china for the first time
wants to say hell, no,
but yeah,
I'm going to allow it.
Well, you know what?
If you're trying to freak me out
about spending Thanksgiving...
Slapsgiving.
At your place,
then you failed.
- Truth is, I'm not scared.
- Really?
Right. 'Cause you blew it.
The worst part about getting slapped is
not knowing when it's going to happen.
But now I know exactly when
I'm gonna get slapped.
So, you took
all the suspense out.
You showed your hand.
And Thursday at 3:01 p.m.,
your face is going
to show my hand.
Oh, there's Bob! By the way, heads up,
he's a little bit older than us.
- How old is he?
- He's forty-one.
Hey, Bob! Over here!
Okay, kids, the truth is,
Bob probably looked like this.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hi.
But when your ex
is dating someone new,
your mind tends to
accentuate their flaws.
This is how I saw Bob.
Hey, dudes, what's crackin'?
- Hey, man, how are you?
- Good to meet you.
Sorry I'm late. I just got off
the phone with my parents.
- Parents?
- They were totally on my case:
"What are you gonna do with your life?
You're forty-one."
And I'm like, "Chillax,
snowboarding is a legit career.
You ought to be stoked
I found my bliss."
And speaking of bliss,
sugar me, baby.
Let's go get a drink.
Wow! Unbelievable.
Robin is dating
Orville Redenbacher.
What are you talking about?
He's forty-one. He looks great.
Yeah, dude he's in pretty good shape.
He could kick your ass.
How are you guys not seeing this?
He's 150; Robin's 27.
Barney, come on,
what do you got?
Nothing but respect
for that man.
Oh, by the way, we're all baking
pies at Robin's tomorrow.
Marshall can't be trusted in the
apartment with pies overnight.
For the millionth time,
sleep-eating is a very serious
and delicious medical condition.
Hey, uh, what time are you guys
going to Robin's?
- 7:30.
- Perfect. Just to be safe,
I'll get there like 8:00, 8:30.
9:30 pm
- Hey.
- Hey. Sorry I'm late.
- Where are Marshall and Lily?
- Uh, they just called.
They're both super swamped
preparing for tomorrow.
- Is Bob coming?
- No, he went to see Green Day.
So it's...
- Just the two of us.
- ...just the two of us.
Making pies.
Pies. They're things that
friends make together.
- Yeah, they do.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Great.
- Yeah.
Great. Well, this is great.
It'll give us a chance to catch up.
Yeah.
- I'm going to make a phone call.
- I'll put it in the oven.
Hey, it's me. Listen, you have
to come over here and make pies.
Yeah, I'll be there, absolutely.
Oh, awesome, you're a lifesaver.
It's still kind of weird being alone
with Robin, but if you were here...
Hey, say no more.
I mean, when I pulled you out
of that burning wreckage,
I wasn't doing it to have
a battleship named after me.
But if you insist, yes,
I'll be there for the christening.
You're hitting on someone
right now, aren't you?
No, I'm not going to wear the medal
of honor. That would just be tacky.
So you're not coming
to make pies.
No, no.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Sorry.
After a very long night, it was
finally the big holiday.
Sorry, the two big holidays.
Oh, Marshall, are you working
on the cranberry sauce?
In a minute, baby.
I've only got so many hands.
You see what I got going on here?
They're turkeys, but they're also hands,
because later,
we're going to eat turkey...
and then I'm going to slap
you in your face.
Please, you took out
all the suspense.
In a horror movie, the killer does not
grab a bullhorn and announce,
"Attention unsupervised teens
here at the lake house:
"At precisely 3:00 a.m., I'm gonna
jump out of that closet right there
"and hack you all up
with a machete.
P.S. Fire is my one weakness."
- Hey, Ted.
- Hey, Happy Thanksgiving.
You, too.
- Is Lily in the kitchen? Great.
- Yep.
- Marshall?
- Lily?
- Yeah?
- Uh-huh?
- Something really weird happened last night.
What do you mean
something weird happened last night?
You may not realize this,
but since we broke up,
Robin and I have never really
been alone together.
So we're in the kitchen,
starting on the pies, and we realize,
we don't have a damn thing
to say to each other.
I mean, you can't talk about
how close you used to be.
You can't talk about how close
you're not now.
You just feel like everything you say
is gonna make things worse.
Exactly. And you know why?
Because you don't want to hurt
someone you really care about,
especially around the holidays.
I mean, what decent human being
would want to cause
any kind of emotional
or physical pain...
You're still getting slapped.
I wanted to leave,
but I couldn't stick her with making
all the pies by herself.
She was exhausted.
I yawned like a million times
trying to get him to leave.
Yeah, some people
just can't take a hint.
By the way,
I'm really swamped in here.
I kept looking at the clock
and sighing... totally clueless.
I'm not sure I have time to mash those
potatoes, you're standing right next to.
Then Ted does the thing that he always
does when there's an awkward silence.
Yep. Masher's right there,
next to the pot.
He panics and says the first
thing that pops into his head.
Hey, did you know that
the first pies
in recorded history
came from ancient Egypt?
Remember last year's Thanksgiving,
when we had sex seven times?
- Ooh.
- Terrible.
What?!
I thought it would break the ice.
I'd already broken the ice
with my cool pie fact.
Then he makes it
ten times more awkward.
How do you respond
to something like that?
Did you know that the Egyptian
pyramids can be seen from space?
Probably?
- Ooh, the oven's pre-heated!
- Okay, um...
the pecan pie is gonna take
the longest.
Why don't we put
that one in first?
Pecan pie?
Why are we making that?
Um, it's my favorite.
- You're allergic.
- I know.
I just like smelling it.
It's like eating with your nose.
So we're making a pie for Bob.
Well...
yeah.
She's got you making pies
for this guy?
That is a real slap
in the face.
You know, you could have
just told me it was for Bob.
Yeah, I-I just thought
it might upset you.
Upset me?
Wait a second.
Do you think that...
...do you think
that I'm jealous of Bob?
I don't know. Is it so ridiculous
to think that you might be?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because he's
a thousand years old.
No, Ted, what are
you doing?
Right?
The only reason
I'm jealous of Bob
is that we can only talk about the first
Thanksgiving, but he was actually there.
Come on.
The only reason
I'm jealous of Bob
is because I heard Noah
gave him shotgun in the ark.
The only reason
I'm jealous of Bob
is that I'm just an architect,
but he discovered fire.
How do you top that?
He's 41! Why are you bashing
on him so hard?
I'm not.
I'm just joking around.
- That's what friends do.
- It's mean.
Well, how come we're all allowed to bust
on Barney when he dates some skanktron,
but when you sleep
with the Crypt Keeper's dad,
I'm not allowed to say a word?
First of all, Bob and I are not
sleeping together.
We're just dating.
Secondly, have I said
one word about
the parade of dubious conquests
you've been marching past me
the last few months?
One of whom got you
a butterfly tattoo?
And if you and I
are such good friends...
why is baking a pie for Bob
so weird?
Yeah, if you and I are
such good friends,
why couldn't you just tell me
that's what we were doing?
Okay, maybe we should talk about
this later. I-I should get going.
Well, what are we doing?
It's Thanksgiving.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
This is stupid.
I'm sorry, too.
Of course we're friends.
I'm glad we're friends.
Me, too.
You guys slept together last night?
That is a terrible idea!
Horrible idea.
Relapse five!
That's where we high-five,
then it's awkward for a little bit...
and then we
high-five again!
What the hell were you doing?
Let's review:
You and Ted broke up
six months ago,
- you're dating another man...
- You are correct, sir.
...who's coming to my
Thanksgiving today...
That is a truth-fact.
- ...an event Ted is also attending.
- Ka-blammo.
Why are you trying to destroy
American Thanksgiving?!
Lily, it's not
as bad as it sounds.
Bob and I aren't that serious,
and what happened last night
with Ted was a fluke.
Well, did you guys
at least talk about it?
- There's office material I'd...
- I hear something burning...
Clearly, we need to ignore this.
Clearly, we need to talk about this.
- You know? To save the friendship.
- Hi.
- We need to talk.
- Stuffed mushroom?
We need to talk
about last night.
Did you know that some
mushrooms are carnivorous?
Probably... Not?
Ted, can we please
just deal with this?
- Look, I'm not mad. I just think...
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why would you be mad, you started it?
What?!
- You're crazy!
- We called a truce,
we hugged, and when I tried to pull
away, you kept your hand on my neck.
Only because your hand
was still around my waist.
Oh, come on!
You leaned into it.
- I... leaned into it?
- Yeah.
You're like the crappy kid
in Little League
who knows he's not going
to make contact, so he just...
"Oops, I got hit by the pitch.
Better take my base."
Oh, that was you
in Little League, wasn't it?
My on-base percentage
was off the charts!
- I will have to...
- What have you always to...
Oh, no!
The slap-petizers.
You know what?
That's it!
This is Thanksgiving.
Solve this right now.
And if you have sex again,
neither of you gets dessert!
Oh, what the hell kind
of Thanksgiving is this anyway?
Um, most Thanksgivings.
Don't stress, baby. I'll try
to find us something relaxing.
Thanks, baby.
Ooh, some classical music, maybe.
Oh, my!
Look at that.
That means we're in the final
hour of the countdown.
I'm not scared.
Then why is your
right cheek twitching?
Maybe it's because Future Me
slaps Future You so hard,
it reverberates back to the present,
shattering the time-slap continuum.
Please don't slap me.
I'm sorry, what?
Oh, God!
Don't slap me again!
I don't want to get slapped again,
and the first two times hurt
so bad, I don't like it!
I don't like it one bit!
I thought I ruined it by putting
a clock on it, Barney?
Well, you didn't ruin it;
you made it so much worse!
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
I've lost ten pounds;
my suits are wearing me.
You know what?
I'm outta here.
- Well, no, no, no. You can't leave.
- Why can't I?!
Nowhere in the rules does
it say that I have to sit
through sort of mental torture!
You are allowed to slap
my face, sir,
but you are not allowed
to slap my mind! Good day!
- But it's Slapsgiving.
- It's not!
It's Thanksgiving!
Our first one as a married couple,
as grownups...
and you're not even trying
to be a part of it! None of you are!
So...
as Slap Bet Commissioner,
I'm issuing a ruling.
Thanksgiving is a day of peace.
There will be no slaps today!
- What?!
- Yes!
In your face! Not my face...
your face!
- What's up, dudes?
- Hey, Bob.
- Baby, please...
- No!
The Slap Bet
Commissioner's word is final,
so get in the kitchen
and mash some potatoes, now.
And for the rest
of the day,
we are going to enjoy
a civilized, grownup holiday.
Not too grownup.
I made Jell-O shots.
We's gonna get silly, bitches.
Look at us!
We can't be alone
together, can we?
Apparently not.
What does that mean?
We're supposed to be friends.
We aren't friends, are we?
Not really.
We avoid each other.
We smile politely.
We're two people
who pretend to be friends
because it would be
inconvenient not to.
Well, maybe we should stop
pretending.
Maybe we should.
So...
Oh, what do we do now?
I suppose... we eat dinner.
And then that's it.
Okay.
Happy Thanksgiving.
So we sat down to our first
Thanksgiving together as a group...
and, apparently, our last.
Marshall, you're not eating.
Did something spoil your slap-petite?
No, I just thought...
before we eat, maybe the chef
would like to say a few words.
Nope. This sucks.
Eat up and leave.
Well, then,
I'd like to say something.
If that's cool?
Today, Lily did something great.
Not only did she gather us all here
together and cook a delicious meal,
but she also started
a new tradition.
We're gonna do this again next year,
and the year after that
maybe for the rest of our lives.
I think that's pretty amazing
if you think about it.
And it's all thanks
to you, Lily.
I love you.
So, to the first of many
Thanksgivings together.
This is rad!
A nice, small,
simple Thanksgiving.
I'm the youngest of ten
in my family,
so our Thanksgiving is
a mess.
All the yelling
and the screaming...
And then a funny thing
happened...
It's really a major buzz-kill.
- Major Buzz-kill.
- Oh, no...
- I thought we were done with that?
I guess we're not.
Guess we're not.
You see kids, friendship
is an involuntary reflex...
it just happens,
you can't help it.
That first Thanksgiving turned
out to be a wonderful dinner
with the four people
I love most in the world...
and Bob.
And it did become a tradition.
That's why every year, we go to Aunt Lily
and Uncle Marshall's for Thanksgiving.
Hey, check it out!
We're in the last 20 seconds
of Marshall's countdown to nothing.
Barney, put it away.
How does it feel, Marshall,
to sit there, impotently...
your large, flaccid hand,
just dangling in the wind?
The slap will occur in ten...
Ooh, classy touch, dude.
Too bad!
- Barney, put it away.
- I will in... five...
- ... four...
- You can slap him.
- What?! Wait, you...
- ...two... one.
That's three!
Thanks, baby, you're the best.
And as a special, added bonus, I've
composed a song just for this occasion.
Ted, lights!
# What is this feelin' #
# That's put you in your place? #
# A hot, red burnin' on the side #
# of your face #
# You feel the blood rush
to your cheek #
# Tears start to fill your eyes #
# And your lips are tremblin'
but you can't speak, #
# you're tryin' #
# Oh, you're tryin' not to cry! #
# - Ya just got sla-apped
- Oh, oh! #
# - Across the face, my friend
- Oh, oh, oh #
# You just got slapped #
# - Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
- Yes, that really just happened #
# Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh! #
# Everybody saw it #
# And everybody laughed and clapped #
# It was awesome #
# Wait, you just got... #
# Slapped. #
Happy Slapsgiving, everybody.
Well, guys, have fun.
Wow, this gonna be
a major clean up.
- Major clean-up.
Oh men, we're gonna to be doing this
all the time now, are we?
That's the general idea.
- General idea.
www.tvsubtitles.net