Now kids,
the spring of 2008 was complicated time in you old man's life.
The last time I had seen Barney
was shortly after I found out he has spent night with Robbin.
Are you saying you don't wanna be bros anymore?
I'm saying I don't wanna be friends anymore.
It's Barney.
Dude, seriously you need to stop calling me.
Ted I'm sorry, I haven't returned your calls.
Yeah I never called you,
you called me fifteen times and my parents twice.
I'm sorry, I gotta let you go.
It's just too many good wingmen out there.
Ted, are you crying?
No, I am not.
Sh....let it out, let it out.
Goodbye Barney.
-So are you two back together?  -No.
I miss Barney.
I haven't "high five" with anyone like a week.
I think I might be starting to lose my fist bone careless.
Let me asking you something Ted.
Why are you so much madder at Barney than me.
Yeah, She had just as much sex with barney
as barney had with her.
You know what? I'm not sure that's true.
I think I actually prefered if you are mad at me.
This is too wierd.
I'm not mad at anybody. I've forgiven you.
And I've outgrown Barney as a friend. That's simple.
I will tell you why he is not mad.
Because he is so happy with stella.
She was right.
Stella and I had been dating for two months.
And things were going really well.
She had mat my friends in past for flying colors.
There was just one little problem.
You guys haven't had sex yet?!
When marshall and I were two months.
We were doing it 24/7.
I know. I was in the top bunk.
Also sat next to you at football games.
So what you guys waiting for?
I... She wants to make sure we are serious first,
that's why she hasn't introduced me to her daughter either.
She wants to take things slow.
Wait, So you haven't had sex since like Thanks Giving.
Do you know how many big federal holidays
have come and gone since then.
Oh, baby, Do you remember Martin Luther King Day
Yeah, I do. We ode that dude big time.
Look, I'm crazy about this girl, if waiting is what it takes,
I'm fine with that.
And totally unrelated note.
Does anybody have gamma icer
or a piece of bark that you are not chewing.
Hey Barney, new sky mall came in.
So Worldaround blog's fear is
you are looking for a new wingman.
I wanna let you know, I am available.
Just say the word, or don't even say the word.
Just do something with your eyebrow.
Was that it?
No offence Randy,
but there is long list of candidates for this slot.
The slot is vice president of awosome.
And you are like assistant under secretary of only ok.
Assistant under secretary of only ok
Thank you, I will not let you down.
So uncle Barney began to search for a new wingman.
-Pitt, Barney Stinson. -Hey
I haven't been calling you, It has been a while.
Yeah yeah, so listen,
you should meet me in mclaren tonight.
You never gonna believe this. I'm at the hospital.
Just had a baby daughter.
So What do you think? 9:30 or 10 o'clock.
Starry Porten, Barney stinson.
What up, chef.
I need a new bro, what do you say?
Dude, I'd love to, But now I'm bro with Duck Stan.
Oh, I understand.
Duck Stan is a good bro.
I'm happy for you. Best of luck.
Crazy Willie. Barney Stinson.
What up B dog, long time no bro,
so are we gonna tire it up tonight or what?
Yes Finally.
Here is what on the rocket tocket.
My wife is gonna put cheese out at seven.
9pm we watch 27 dresses.
Everybody is home by 11:00. Booya.
-Hello  -Hanging up on you once wasn't enough.
So I lanced this thing  on this guy's back,
and I'll be honest with you, I didn't even know what it was,
and then it exploded like a volcano.
Pus everywhere.
Let's have sex.
Right now.I'll lock the door.
Oh, there's no lock on that door.
We can do it against the door.It'll be hot!
It'll be like a three-way: you, me, and the door.
Yeah, but then it's just gonna be weird
between me and the door tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
We're waiting. It's cool.
You've been so patient, Ted.
The truth is...
I'm kind of nervous.
I have a confession to make.
I was afraid of this.
You're 14.
No, um...
It's kind of embarrassing,but it's been a while
since I was intimate with anyone.
Wow, it's funny that you say that.
Me, too.
Really?
How long's it been for you?
It's been a while.
Tell me.
Me, too!
It's been five months  for you, too?
Five years?!
Wow.
Stella hasn't had  sex since 2003.
Let's put this in context.
The last time Stella had sex,the movie, Seabiscuit,
had just galloped into theaters... and our hearts.
Five years?
God, if I even went one year,
I would be out on the street selling it for a nickel.
The last time Stella had sex,
the world was just learning about SARS.
Well, Ted, what else did she say?
Did she give you any kind of explanation?
Look, after Lucy was born,I dated a little,
but it was hard to find a guy  I could trust enough.
Sooner or later, every one of them
gave me a reason not to.
But nobody in five years?
Look, Ted, guys regret the girls they didn't sleep with.
Girls regret the guys  they do sleep with.
And for the past  five years,
I've had no regrets.
Ted, you're staring at my boobs.
In my defense,   they were staring at me.
So what does this mean for you?
Is she ever gonna want to get intimate?
Actually...
But the truth is,I really do
want to do this with you.
I don't think  I'd regret it at all.
Your pillow talk's a little rusty.
You know what I mean, Ted. I'm ready.
That's great.
Like, "right now" ready?
So her sister's driving up   to baby-sit Lucy,
and we're getting a hotel room  in the city Saturday night.
The last time  Stella had sex,
The Da Vinci Code  had just come out.
Well, that doesn't seem  like that long ago.
Not the movie, the book.
Wow.
It's a lot of pressure,   isn't it?
You know what? It's not.
This woman needs it bad.
Anything you do is going to be fireworks.
I remember my longest drought...
It was that summer I lived   in San Francisco.
I hadn't had been with Marshall   in two months and 19 days.
Oh, San Francisco.
I don't know, Lily,after five years,
her expectations  have gotta be pretty high.
Notable deaths  in 2003...
Oh, my God...   Nell Carter.
Did you guys know  that Nell Carter had died?
I'm really gonna have to bring my A-game to satisfy this woman.
Yeah, it'll be pretty hard  now that she's dead.
Not Nell Carter-- Stella.
Dude, relax.
It's all about expectations management.
Do you know why I hated Jerry Maguire so much?
Because you're dead inside?
No, because you built it up for, like, two weeks,
saying it was the greatest movie ever.
With Stella, do the opposite:  lower expectations.
Right, right, and then no matter what happens,
she'll be happy
Hey, buddy.
I'm married, Barney.I cannot be your new wingman.
No.
Hey, Randy.
Could you come in here for a minute?
Good news.
I'm calling you up to the majors.
Starting tomorrow night,
how would you like  to be my new wingman?
Uh...
Just need to check my calendar. Be right back.
Tomorrow works.
I have a surprise appetizer for us today.
Check it out.
Potato skins.
Fancy.
Yeah, right?
God, it's been forever since I had potato skins.
I remember them as being
pretty much the most delicious things ever.
Huh.
That's surprising.
What?
This potato skin.
It's good
but not nearly as good as I'd built it up to be in my head.
Even though this potato skin performed admirably,
and is a totally respectable size...
I couldn't enjoy it
because of my own unrealistic expectations.
Hmm, Ted, I see  what you're doing.
You're trying to lower
my expectations for tonight.
-Is this a length thing?  -No.
-Quick on the draw?  -No.
-Unexpected number of testicles?  -No!
It's just that this is a big deal for you.
I mean, it's like your virginity: the sequel.
Virginity 2: Electric Boogaloo?
Exactly, and I don't want to mess it up.
I don't want you to ever wonder if I was worth it.
Ted, of course it's gonna be worth it.
Stop worrying.
It's you and me.
It already has everything it needs.
"Unexpected number of testicles?"
It happens. I knew a guy in med school...
We used to joke that he was one ball away from getting walked.
Hey.
What up, Bro-seph Lieberman?
No, uh-uh.
Randy, we never use  the word "bro" in the name
of a failed Democratic vice presidential candidate.
Good-bye, "Geraldine Ferrar-bro."
You know what?
I'm excited  about this, Randy.
You will be my next masterpiece.
It's like with Ted.
When I first met him,
he was an even bigger loser than you.
What a loser.
But tonight, I am going  to make you
the greatest wingman  in the history of wingmen.
Oh, it's gonna be easier than you think, bro.
Yeah, I've been reading  your blog for years.
You are like a god to me.
That's why tonight is going to be legendary...
wait for it...
dary.
Okay, Randy, let's do this.
Okay.
You ready?
Yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What? What's  the matter?
Nothing.
Let's do this.
No, no, no, no, no, please, please, please.
Just wait. Just wait. Just wait. Just wait!
Randy, what are  you doing?
Dripping with game,that's what I'm doing.
Okay, let's go. No. Let's...
Yes. No!
Randy, listen to me: you can do this, okay?
Oh, I don't know. Are those girls really that hot?
Yeah, they're hot. Let's do this.
Okay!
Hey, ladies.
Have you met...
-Hey. -Hey!
So, here's the plan.
Take a horse-drawn carriage through the park,
and it just so happens
-the Philharmonic is playing  an open-air... -Ted.
Five years.
-Straight to the hotel? -Straight to the hotel.
I'll get my bag.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
So, uh, looking forward to tonight?
Yeah. Definitely.
It's been such a long time since I've had a night out.
Yeah, we heard.
I would explode if it had been that long
since I had a "night out."
This one wakes me up at 4 am sometimes
just to have a little "night out."
Um, what are you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Pizza.
What are you talking about?
Hey, guys.
Ted, you told them,  didn't you?
Told them what?
You told them
that I haven't had  sex in five years.
You haven't had sex in five years?!
That is a shocking revelation
that we're just finding out right now!
Stella, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have told them.
But they're my best friends. I tell them everything.
I-I didn't even think about it.
Ted, that was so personal.
Plus, now your friends  think I'm a freak.
No, they don't.
Look, I realize it's weird, okay?
Not many people go five years without having sex.
13 years?!
I peaked really young.
That's why it was difficult  for me to tell you.
But I did tell you because I thought that I could trust you.
You can trust me.
Obviously, I can't.
You know, there's always a reason not to sleep with a guy,
and you just gave me yours.
Wait, did I give you a reason,
or were you looking for one?
Why would be looking for one?
Because things are getting  serious between us,
and that scares you.
Good night, Ted.
Okay, Randy, now,
tell me, without looking at your hand,
are the three beginner techniques
for picking up a woman at a bar?
Isolate her from her friends;
repeat her name in conversation;
subtly put her down.
Excellent.
Now...
let's put those to use.
I'm right  behind you.
Hi, I'm Randy.
What's your name?
Haley.
Haley, that's a pretty name, Haley.
Haley...
come here, Haley.
Um... okay.
Haley, you are a fat ugly whore.
I'm sorry, Barney.
Eh, so you got a drink thrown in your face.
Happens to me all the time.
Pretty soon you'll be  able to anticipate it,
and when you do?  Free drink.
We got two live ones.
New plan: this time follow my lead.
Evening, ladies.
Oh, I like your broach.
What is that?
Oh, it's a koala bear.
I think they're adorable.
No way!
My friend randy here is the leading expert
On koala bears in australia!
He's in town working with the bronx zoo.
You are?
That is so Cool!
Okay, what is your favorite thing about koala bears?
Their...
Meat is delicious.
I'm sorry, barney.
Ah, it's okay.
New plan: We need to get you comfortable
Just saying words to women.
Now, there's no reason to be nervous,
Because my friend, robin, has agreed to help out.
Because you threatened to put a video of us on the internet,
Which I'm still not convinced you have.
Right, which is why you came all the way
From brooklyn at midnight.
Now randy,
Let's keep it Simple.
Just start by introducing Yourself.
Hi.
My name's randy.
Hi, randy.
How are you?
I'm good. how are you?
-Good, thank you. -great.
You're doing really, really well.
Now ask her what she's doing later.
What are you doing later?
Yeah, your nose is bleeding like a faucet.
Oh, god.
This happens every time I get an erection.
I am so sorry.
Okay.
Okay, new plan.
We wrap his face in gauze  so he can't bleed or talk.
You are the woman...
Barney, why are you so desperate to have this happen?
I'm a wingman.
That's what wingmen do.
Is it possible
That you're trying to fill the void of losing ted
By rushing into a new wingman relationship?
What are you saying?
I'm saying that randy is your rebound bro.
No.
That's crazy.
What randy and I have is real.
No, it's not, barney.
And even if you got randy laid tonight,
Would it feel anywhere near as meaningful
As when you got ted laid?
He was just so happy the next morning, you know?
I know.
All right.
It hasn't clotted,
But I think it's pretty much draining backwards now.
Randy.
I've been thinking,
Is isn't working out.
Yeah, I figured.
I knew I couldn't fly this close to the sun
Without getting burned.
This is the story of my life.
I always let people down.
You, my dad, the chief.
The chief?
Yeah, I was a cop for like three months.
But I got kicked off the force
Because I screwed up so much I was an insurance liability.
You were a new york city police officer
And you didn't tell me?
Did you ever shoot anybody?
Only all the time.
But not himself.
And not in the foot.
-Actually...   -ah, bah, bah,   bah, bah.
But nothing.
I don't think there's anything hotter than a cop.
Are you okay?
Your nose is bleeding.
Uh, old injury.
The bullet's still lodged in his sinus.
Oh, my god!
You know what?
I live right around the corner.
Can I take you to my place
And fix you up?
That would be very nice.
Have a great time, you two.
Oh, my god, thank you.   I can't thank you enough.
I am the greatest wingman of all time.
Ted doesn't know what he's missing.
You had to mention ted,  didn't you?
Okay, I really overreacted last night.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I have some trust issues,
But believe me, I have earned them.
You said that I was looking for a reason
For this whole thing to fall apart.
Well, you're onto me, ted.
That's actually something that I do a lot.
But I'm not going to do that with you.
Ted... I'm in.
This is awkward.
I have a girl here.
So...
Come on.
There is something that I'm ready to do with you.
Ted, this Lucy.
-Hi, lucy.  -lucy, this is ted.
Stella and I thought our relationship
Was going to take a big step that weekend.
turned out. it even took a bigger one
She's sound asleep.  oh.
She is so great.
I think so.
So, uh, I was thinking,
My sister is in town until tomorrow.
And, uh, there's a motel just down the turnpike.
-Wow, that was amazing!  -oh, yeah.
What are you doing?
I gonna call Marshall and Lily tell them about this
www.tvsubtitles.net