Kids, this is the story of the
cab ride that changed my life.
I know it sounds crazy,
but for all I know my life
would be very different
if I had taken, say...
that cab.
Or that cab.
God knows what would have happened
if I had gotten into that cab.
I took this cab.
And it changed my whole life.
But first,
we need to back up a little.
Is there any beer in the fridge?
It's 10:00 in the morning.
Grab me one?
So... something bad
just happened.
Stella and I were out
having breakfast.
So, my sister broke up
with her boyfriend.
Well, I can finally say it.
I hated that guy!
Everything out of his mouth is,
"I'm a vegan.
"Fish feel pain.
I'm never constipated."
The guy's an idiot.
Actually, she's marrying him.
I just wanted your honest opinion.
He's actually a really nice guy.
I think there's a wisdom to...
Anyway they pick a date so, uh,
you want to come with me,
so that we can laugh our asses off
as we watch him walk barefoot
down the aisle in a hemp tuxedo?
- Yeah, sure. When is it?
- First weekend in November.
Is that the something bad?
That she invited you to a wedding?
Six months from now.
As in...
we'll be together
six months from now.
Do you guys remember Barney's whole thing
about making plans in a relationship?
Fourth row.
Ted, no. You're violating
the date-time continuum.
You never make plans with a girl
further in the future
than the amount of time
you've been going out.
You've been dating this girl for,
what, two weeks?
No, you're not taking her
to a Springsteen concert in January.
By that time you won't even remember
this Robin girl's name.
Man, I love Springsteen!
He's like the American Bryan Adams.
But Barney had a point.
As soon as she started talking about
the wedding, it freaked me out.
Oh, that sounds like so much fun.
So I get to look forward
to it for six months.
Which is twice as long
as we've been dating.
I'm sure your daughter Lucy
will come so it'll be like a...
a family trip.
Our first trip
as our funny little family.
So that... that'll be super-exciting.
Oh, boy.
Man, they crank up the heat
in these places.
What's going on, Ted?
We need to talk.
- Oh.
- "We need to talk?"
There's only two situations where
you say that to someone and
unless you're pregnant,
it sounds like you broke up with her.
Yeah, I did.
So how did she take it?
I'm only trying
to be honest with you.
You know, Ted.
- I have to go to work.
- Stella, can we just...
I don't want to leave it like this.
No, Ted, it's okay.
We're good.
Look, I know it sounds rough,
but Stella's a mom.
I have to be responsible.
If I'm having these feelings now,
what if they don't go away?
What if they just get worse and
worse and six months from now,
I break up with her over
tofu salmon at her sister's wedding?
I can't do that to her. And I definitely
can't do that to her daughter.
It sucks, but I'm being
the good guy here.
This is the right decision.
Which brings me back
to the cab ride.
Hello, may I speak
with Marshall Eriksen?
Hey, guys.
Jell-O?
How I Met Your Mother 3x20
- Miracles -
Can you believe this?
You're totally fine.
No, I'm not fine. I made
the biggest mistake of my life.
I want Stella back. I've left her
like ten messages, but her phone's off.
She's at that arcade
Kiddie Funland with her daughter.
Please. Let me go
to Kiddie Funland.
You can say that all you want, buddy,
but you're not getting any morphine.
No, I'm serious.
I got to get out of here.
You're not going anywhere
until we get the tests back.
You could have internal bleeding.
Your brain could be all full of blood.
Think that's good for it?
It ain't.
This sucks.
- This sucks. This sucks.
- Are you...
are you kidding me?
You walked away from
a car accident without a scratch.
A miracle took place today.
Here we go.
You don't think this was a miracle?
There's no such thing as miracles.
March 2006, MacLaren's Bar.
- That's terrible. That's in!
- Gentle. Gentle.
Here we go.
Bravo. Cheers...
- No... way.
- That did not just happen.
Am I dead?
Miracle!
A pencil went up Barney's nose,
and you call it a miracle.
Well, do you have a better
explanation for it?
A drunk jackass
with a box of pencils?
A drunk jackass called "God!"
And a box of pencils called "destiny!"
Speaking of Barney,
I should give him a call.
Why? We're not friends anymore.
You'd want to know
if this happened to him.
Go for Barney.
Hey, Barney. Listen,
I have something to tell you.
Oh, boy, here we go.
I've been waiting for this one.
You talked to Robin.
She told you
what's under the hood
and you want to take it
for a spin yourself.
Not even if you
boiled it in detergent.
It's about Ted.
Ted? Ah ah, ah ah.
My former best friend Ted who I
asked you never to mention to me again?
Yeah.
He's been in a car accident.
He's at Saint Anthony's hospital.
Everything's...
No, I understand.
You've got that important thing.
Okay. Oh, of course...
I'll tell him you love him.
Okay.
Suit up!
He is always saying
stuff like that!
- He hung up, didn't he?
- Yeah.
See, I told you.
We're not friends anymore.
My best friend need me!
What did he say?
A hundred and thir... What?
You... Ah, come on!
I'm coming, Ted.
So, what made you change
your mind about Stella?
Well, I was in the cab,
and the car was coming at me,
and you know how they say
that your whole life
flashes before your eyes
in a near-death experience?
It doesn't.
You don't see everything.
Just the things you love.
I realized in that moment that
Stella is the most important thing
in my life and I have to get her back.
Miracle!
Very sweet.
Very romantic.
Not a miracle.
July 1999.
Kennedy Airport.
So, did you enjoy...
Amsterdam?
No. Nothing illegal.
Just a paintings.
All right, Bob Marley.
Let's have a conversation.
Shift change.
Oh, Amsterdam.
All right.
Float on through, brother.
Miracle!
Don't you go into the light!
Don't you do it!
Hey, Mosby,
you got a visitor.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Can you guys, uh,
give us a minute?
Stella, before you say anything...
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Can we just forget about...
- It's forgotten.
Is this your chart?
Okay. Uh-huh.
Everything looks good.
I think you can handle it.
Handle what?
Aww!
This morning he dumped her and now
she's dry-humping him
on a hospital bed.
- Miracle!
- Yeah,
you know, I bet
if you call up the Vatican,
they will tell you that most of their
certified miracles involve dry-humping
so.
April 2008.
Lily's kindergarten classroom.
You're gonna go in there
and beg for your old job back?
That's crazy.
You hated it there.
I know, the job market
is just really bad right now.
Hey, kids,
who wants Uncle Marshall
to get his old job back?
They'll cheer for anything
if you say it like that.
Kids,
a super tanker spilled
five million gallons of oil
off the coast of Alaska
this morning!
Hello, Marshall.
Mr. Hewitt, I came here to apologize.
I'm going to go grab some more glue.
Will you watch them for a sec?
Of course.
Leaving Nicholson, Hewitt, and West
was a huge mistake,
and I can see that now.
So...
who wants to see the big guy
put on these tiny hats?
My behavior was disrespectful.
It was unprofessional.
I'm a pilgrim.
I know it looks like
I have a tiny hat,
but in reality, I have
an abnormally large head!
I was going through a stressful time.
I wasn't getting enough sleep.
Fourscore and seven years ago,
I had a great, big giant head!
I had just bought an apartment, and
there were some problems. I don't
want to bore you with the details.
I only regret that I have but one
giant head to give for my country.
Sir, if you could just see your way
into giving me one more chance,
- I promise...
- Marshall.
I'm willing to give this
a second chance.
I remember my first years
as an attorney.
Why, I don't know how many hours
I spent. I don't think I ever left...
Oh, my God!
I have lice.
Those little bastards
gave me lice.
God, it itches.
Don't scratch it.
You'll look like a fool.
You'll never get your job back.
You can scratch,
but just make it subtle.
Okay, that's not working.
Oh, sweet,
sharp corner of the desk,
how I long to rub
my infested scalp against you.
- You okay, Eriksen?
- Oh! Oh, yes, I'm good.
I am good.
Continue.
Mind over matter.
There are no lice in my hair...
laying eggs,
burrowing into my scalp,
eating their way all the way
down to my brain!
I have lice!
"Lice"?! Lice! Get out!
Get out of my office!
We've got lice!
Everybody out of the building.
If it weren't for the lice,
I would have gotten my job back,
and I would have been
working there when,
two weeks later, the Securities and
Exchange Commission came a-knocking.
God sent those lice to my head
like he sent the locusts to Egypt:
to liberate me
from corporate bondage.
Miracle.
Hey, guys.
I'm just so glad you and Ted
are back together.
Wait, um, what do you mean
"back together?"
Well, you know,
since you guys broke up.
What? Oh, no. It was just a
small fight. That wasn't a breakup.
Was that a breakup?
Did he think that was a breakup?
What?
Son of a bitch!
That was a breakup. Wasn't it?
You broke up with me.
Yeah.
I didn't know that was a breakup.
Are you kidding?
I said, "I feel awful."
You said,
"We're good."
Then you got up and left.
Yeah, I said, "We're good,"
as in "We're good."
Like when the waiter comes around
and asks if you want any more muffins,
and you say, "We're good."
Exactly, and I took that
"We're good" to mean
you didn't want any more
metaphorical relationship muffins.
This is crazy.
Forget about all that.
That was a whole
life-changing car accident ago.
I love you.
I don't want to break up.
But you did.
You did want to.
If you had
those feelings once,
then you're going to have
those feelings again,
and you're going to keep
on having them.
And I can't count on that car
to hit you every time you do.
What are you saying?
I'm saying...
you wanted your breakup,
- you got it.
- What?! Stella, wait!
No, you know what, Ted?
We're good.
So you broke up with her
and she didn't know it.
Apparently.
And you actually said,
"I want to break up?"
No, of course not.
Who says "I want to break up?"
That's a horrible thing to say.
Well, that's true.
- Hello?
- Hi, Ted Mosby?
We have you listed as the
emergency contact for Barney Stinson.
What is it?
What it was was this.
I made it.
I made it!
Dude, I...
I can't believe you ran
all the way up here.
Jeez. Flatter yourself much?
What an ego on this guy.
Um, I was up in this part
of town because
I had to attend a very important
international business meeting.
If you're here to come
crawling back, just save it.
I'm doing awesome without you.
Even better now, 'cause I can play
the sympathy card with the females.
And BTW, there's one bone
downstairs that ain't broken.
Marshall, you know
what I'm talking about.
Up top!
Are you sure?
Yeah, dude. Why do you think
I had them set it this way?
Okay.
Worth it.
Barney, you, uh...
You could've died.
Ted, I'm sorry I broke the Bro Code.
No, I'm sorry.
Ted, can we be friends again?
Barney, come on, we're...
we're more than friends.
We're brothers.
- You're my brother, Ted.
- You're my brother, Barney.
Did you hear that, Marshall?
We're brothers now.
Marshall's my brother, too.
We're all brothers.
Yeah, but I'm your
best brother, right?
And that's how your Uncle Barney
and I buried the hatchet.
It got pretty mushy and
embarrassing after that.
Let's skip ahead.
I had to look away because
if I watched what
the paramedics were about to do,
I would have passed out.
Then they took out this electric
blade thing and I kept thinking,
"This isn't happening.
This isn't happening."
Oh, my God.
What did they cut?
My suit.
My beautiful suit.
But you're alive, and, and Ted's alive.
This is amazing!
Two miracles in one day.
What is the matter with you?
How can you possibly
be this cynical?!
You want to know?
You really want to know?
Fine.
When I was a kid,
I had this dog,
Sir Scratchawan.
Anyway, Sir Scratchawan
got really old,
so my parents decided
to put him down.
It was the
toughest day of my young life.
Good-bye, Sir Scratchawan.
I love you.
And when they
took him to the vet,
he told them that earlier
that very day,
he had learned about
an experimental procedure called
a canine/testudine
cerebro-xenograft.
- Ever heard of it?
- No.
Well, it saved
Sir Scratchawan's life.
He lived another seven years.
Miracle.
Except for one... kind of big
side effect from the surgery.
Sir Scratchawan!
Welcome home!
He turned into a turtle.
I know. It's weird, right?
Apparently, a very
common complication from
canine/testudine cerebro-xenografts.
And he didn't seem to remember
any of his old tricks.
Go get it, Scratchy.
Go get it!
Go get it! Get it!
Go get it, Scratchy.
Go get it.
- How long was it before...?
- Longer than I'm proud of, Lily.
Longer than I'm proud of.
And that's when I realized
miracles ain't real.
Excuse me.
Mosby, you're still here?
Your tests came back, like,
an hour ago. You're fine.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't you tell me?!
I'm sorry.
I guess it was rude of me to keep
resuscitating that guy
with a rake sticking out of his chest.
I have to go right now.
Barney, I...
Go.
Run, Ted. Run.
If there's anything I've taught you
over the years, it's...
Barney, he left.
Hey, Ted said that
right before the accident,
his life flashed before his eyes.
You know, all the stuff he loves.
- Did that happen to you?
- Oh, yeah.
I know what he saw: boobs.
- Scotch.
- And money.
- Suits.
- A suit of money.
A suit of boobs.
A giant boob
wearing a suit of money.
And the boob is lactating scotch.
I guess that's pretty much
everything you love, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
Kids, a lot of weird, random things
have happened in my life,
but that car accident is one
of the few I'd call a miracle,
not because of what happened,
but because of what happened next.
Hi.
Can I talk to you?
Okay.
I got you this orange kangaroo.
Thanks.
So I've been thinking
about what changed
from the moment
I broke up with you
to the moment I knew
I wanted you back. And, um,
I think I finally figured out
what happened.
Your cab got T-boned
by a jackass on a cell phone?
I changed.
I'm ready to give you
what you need.
That's why I spent
ten minutes on the
damn claw machine trying to get
the big, fake diamond ring.
But all I could get
was this orange kangaroo.
Diamond ring?
Will you marry me?
www.tvsubtitles.net