kids,everybody make mistakes
Take this girl Meg for instance.
She made a mistake, a mistake named Barney.
Yeah I thought I was gonna get married to my last boyfriend
but, boy, did that guy have commitment issues.
That whole relaonship--
that's three weeks of my life I'll never get back.
Well, I love commitment.
I wish I could marry commitment.
I met a girl last night.
Really?
So perky and full of life and not at all fake.
You're talking about her boobs, right?
C?
And that wasn't Spanish, that was cup size.
What up?
So, these boobs... Hmm.
paint me a word picture.
All right, Ted.
Imagine the heads of two Irish babies. Mmm.
Let's call them...
and...
Please stop!
When you get married,
you start out growing certain parts of your life.
And for Lily and Marshall, those certain parts were,
for the most part, me
Why would you come in?
You hear me shaving!
I thought you were shaving your face!
Well, clearly I wasn't!
Oh! No, no!
Pay up! Ugh! pussy!
Guys,it's 3:00 in the morning
and it reeks in here.
Ted said it was okay.
Ah, hey, Marshall.
You're still up?
Aren't you taking the bar tomorrow?
Discontent was bubbling under this surface,
until one day...
Ted!
How many times have I asked you to put the lid
back on the peanut butter jar?
It's this sort of incoiderate,
immature jackassery
that makes me feel like I'm living in the Realworld house,
and not the early years when they all had jobs
and social consciences.
I'talking about Hawaii and after!
I can't take this anymore!
ted, Lily and I are married now!
It's time! we're getting our own place!
Actually, I left the lid open. Sorry, baby.
But still,it was time to move forward.
So, they set out to find a new apartment to rent.
Hey, here's one.
Prwar building, recently renovated,
hardwood floors, tons of light,
two bedroom, two bath.
Oh, yeah, but that one's not for rent.
It's for sale.
Oh, right.
Kids, Uncle Marshall always like to say
that he had made three big mistakes in his life.
This was the first.
Jump, you big chicken!
Jump! You afraidy cat!
Jump! Jump!
This was the second.
No!
And this was the third and biggest.
We should buy a place!
-What? -Baby,
real estate is always a good invesent.
It's not.
And the market is really hot rightnow.
It wasn't.
And because of my new job,
we are in such atrong place financially.
They weren't.
Because lily has a secret.
My name is Lily and I'm a shopaholic.
Hi, Lily.
Oh, you guys don't do that here?
Sorry.
Proceed.
I buy designer clothes and accessories that I can't afford.
I have 15 creditcards and they're all maxed out.
And no one outside of this room,
not even my husband, knows.
And I, I feel terrible
becaus all I want to do right now
is ask you where you got those shoes.
They're adorable.
we can't buy; we have debt.
Yeah, I know,
my student loans are pretty big.
I forgive you.
What?
Well...
I'm just saying as your wife,
you know I'm cool that you spent tens of thousands of dollar
on a brand name law school.
cause I know it make you feel good and pretty.
Let's just go take a look at this place.
Where is it?
Uh, it's in a neighborhood called..
Dowisetrepla?
Dowisetrepla
Dowisetrepla.
Oh, I see, you're not New Yorkers.
Oh, actually we live on the Upper West side, so...
No need to be emrrassed, listen,
here in New York we just shorten the names of all t ighborhos,
So, TriBeC Nolita--
oh, right.
Dowisetrepla
I'm, I'm from New York.
I know this nighborhood.
i am down in the D-town
Oh, well nobody calls it D-town.
Dowisetrepla
the up-and-coming neighborhood.
And I have to tell you, for the prices
you're not going to be able to find an other...
I'm, I'm gonna stop you right there.
Don't bother with the hard sell.
This place is, is way out of our price range,
and besides, we've only just started to looking.
Is what Marshall should he said.
I'm gonna stop you right there.
I love it!
Let's get it!
thank you gays, for coming down here so quickly.
I've never been to this neighborhood.
kind of thought this part of town was water.
No, dude.
This is Dowisetrepla.
Dowisetrepla? Yeah.
Is that abbreviation for something?
He'from Ohio.
Dowiatrepla is th up-a-coming neighborhood. Oh.
I think this right the place where Lily and I start a family
I can see it now
Two three,four.
All right, bring it home, boys.
Sounds great, boys.
Who wants chocolate pancakes?
Thanks, Mommy!
Man,
life is gonna be sweet!
oh, my God, Lily, have you seen this kitchen?
I know. It's... Isn't it amazing?
-I just love it so... -What the hell are you doin
You can't buy this place.
Lily you have a debt the size of Mount Waddington!
Waddington?
It's the tallest mountain in Canada.
It's like 4,000 meters high.
Meters?
Don't let Marshall fa in love with this apartmt.
I know, I know, I know, I know
but what do i tell him?
I-I don't know, tell him,
tell him you saw a ghost. Tell him it's haunted.
You really don'know Marshall at all.
So, uh, the owners,where are they? Oh.
-They're on vacation in France for two weeks. -I see.
Between you and me,
I'm also interested in the artment.
So is there any way I could come back later and check it out
while you're showing them other places?
The lockbox combination is 1421.
And heres my card.
Are you serious?
You're trying to sneak this apartment away from Marshall and Lily
Ted, do you think I have no morals whatsoever?
I simply want to fool a girl into thinking this is my apartment
so I can nail her once and never have to see her again.
I'm not a monster.
Now, listen I don't want to put a lot of pressure on you,
but there is one other couple that expressed very serious interest.
I see what you're doing here.
"Another couple."
Please
That crap is page one out of the Realtor's playbook.
And we're not buying it.
Is what Marshall should have said.
Another couple? No!
We want it. Sell it to us. We'll give you so much more money.
Oh Marshall, can I talk to you?
Marshall, I just...
I don't know if now is the right time to buy.
But we're not doing this for now,
we're doing this for our future.
Can't you imagine starting a family here?
Oh, Persephone!Oh Daphne!
These'll be perfect additions
to our upcoming mother-daughter exhibit at the Met.
Looks great, girls.
Who wants crapes of chocolate?
Merci, papa.
So... what do you guys think?
I love it, but Marshall,
I should have told you this long time ago.
We can't afford to buy an apartment.
because I have too much credit card debt.
I am so sorry.
Is what she should have said.
I love it. Let's get it.
Can we charge it?
To Lily and Marshall
and their momentous step forward into adulthood.
Cheers.
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Drink it!
Yes! Well done. Nice! Yeah!
Anything else?
Yes.
I've been staring at that thing for years.
Wendy
bring me the comically large bottle of champagne.
Really? Are you sure?
It's neve been refrigerated.
And I think at some point there was a fish in it.
Honey, once you've made the sale,stop selling.
All right, but you guys have to help me carry it.
All right, let's do it. Let'do this.
I know what you're thinking.
I should tell Marshall the truth
I've got the whole thing figure out.
We'll apply for the loan under Marshall's name,
and h'll never need to know.
And then in the meantime, I'll slowly work down debt.
Right after I furnish the apartment.
I saw this amazing leather sofa today.
You should be a reality show.
Nice! Nice.
Wait!
That cork is the size of a softball
and you're pointing it directly at Wendy the waitress's face.
Is what he should have said.
Now if you are thinking about buying an apartment,
it's always good to check the place out at night.
Welcome to my humble abode.
This place is so nice.
Ah, make yourself at home.
Please, get comfortable.
If you see something you like, just take it.
Who are these people?
Uh... that's my parents.
They're Asian.
Yeah.
They're a Chinese couple that wanted a white baby
It works both ways.
Cookie. Wow.
Did you make those?
You got me. My sisters taught me how to bake and how to listen.
I feel so at home here.
I'm glad.
Sometimes, I don't.
A place like this really needs a lady of the house.
I know it's early to be thinking of you as...
Oh, God I'm freaking you out, aren't I?
It's just  you make me feel so safe.
I didn't...
The next day
Lily and Marshall went to the mortgage broker to get a loan.
Hey, uh, can we get this in singles?
Before we get the apartment I want to put in a kiddie pool
and swim around in it naked.
Great, that is great
Thank you.
Okay! all right, back to business.
All right, Mrs. Aldrin, I'm going to need your social as well.
What? Why?
I mean, you already have Marshall's.
Yes, but since you're a married couple,
you'll be applying for a joint loan, so.
Well, can we just go ahead an do it in my husband's name?
He is the head of the household.
He earns the big bucks.
I mean, can women even own property?
Go ahead, just give him your social.
Okay my... my social is, uh...
Got it.
Let's see what kind of rate I can get you two.
Under six percent Under six percent.
Under six percent,please.
There we go Congratulation
You ve been approved for a loan
18%
at 18%.
No, way. That-that can't be right.
You' lucky to be getting mortgage.
Let's get out of here, Marshall.
Hold it, I-I don't undersnd.
did we do mething wrong or...?
You have quite a bit of debt.
My student loans.Great.
I thought we were friends.
You know what, it's fine
to penalize me for trying
to get an education and bud a career,
but I will not let you deprive my beautiful wife
of her dream home just because I...
Okay, actually, it's because of youwife's credit card debt.
Oh my God.
Marshall, there's something I have to tell you,
and I want you to hear it from me first.
Okay,  let me get this straight.
You just snuck this girl into some stranger's apartment?
yeah, we spent the night.
Hey, look at you.
I'm wearing your bathrobe.
I hope you don't mind.
The only thing missing from that bathrobe
are your initials.
My mom's gonna be in town next week.
Is iokay if she stays with us?
Only if she sleeps in the bed
and I sleep on the couch.
You're so sweet.
I love you.
There, I said it and I'm not taking it back.
Oh, my God! I love you, too.
I'm finally not the first one to say it!
How about you get in the shower,
and I will make us some waffles.
Works every time.
Wait.
That time that you offered to walk my dogs
when I went to visit my dad in Vancouver...
Yup.
Is that why my Yorkie trembled
for like a week after I got back?
Yeah.
That little guy saw some stuff I'm not proud of.
-Wh.  -What?
There was a fight here.
What do you mean?
whenever Mshall anLily have a big argument, they always
leave a trail of evidence all over the apament.
Oh, god, here we go.
He had a detective club as a kid.
Uh, the Mosby Boys
cracked a lot of big cases
The Mosby Boys?
You mean you and your sister.
We solved the mystery of the missing retainer.
let me guess
it was in the garbage.
Why are you like this?
Anyway, this is serious.
I know Lily and Marshall.
All the tell tale signs are here.
Like this
-A water bott? -Don't touch the evidence
I got your back partner.
It's not stny water bottle.
Notice the label is peed off.
Lily always peels labels off
the bottle when she's feeling guilty.
This lab is not only peele off, but torn up
Oh, man, she must have done something bad.
Which means Marshall must have been really angry,
and when Marshall gets rely angry.
he eats.
Just as I suspected,
Cherry Garcia.
Given the liquid consistency,
I place the fight between... noon and 1.
Ew, that was on the floor.
If you want to get to the bottom of this,
you're gonna need a stronger stomach than that, doll-face.
Marshall stood here.
Eating and yelling, yelling and eating.
Lily stood here.
Crying.
Ew, Ted.
And thenarshall tried to
storm out...
but Lily went for the Hail Marpass.
Which would mean...
What do u think, makeup sex?
There'd be a bigger mess.
Tempted as he was, Marshall was still too upset.
He had to get out of here, any way he cld.
He chosehe doo
slamming it bend him.
Whh is why this picture is crooked.
Nice catch, robin.
I'll jus uh, take this down to the lab.
Now alwe need  a motive.
The milln-dollar question.
at were they fighting about?
I ow what they've been fighting...
Bup, bup, bu b, bup, bup.
There's only one possible conclusion.
Li and Marshall're fighting about
-peanut butter. -Ah.
Lily left the lid off...
and mashall blew heads
I know what they were fighting about,
and it wasn't peanut butter.
Robin, just... I appreciate your help,
but there's a reason you name is Robin, not Batman.
Just...
They were fighting because they didn't get the loan
and it's all Lily's fault.
Robin, just... What?
Yeah, she has a pile of debt the size of Mount...
Rushmore
Nice try, Robin.
So, the next thing Lily did
was give Marshall a few hours to cool off about
the peanut butter.
Then she called him
to apologize, which is why the last number dialed is...
Greenstein and Lee, Divorce Attorneys.
This can't be happening.
They can't... get divorced.
Not Lily and Marshall, no way.
Well, it's been nice knowing you guys.
What do you mean? Well..
Marshall's gonna get you guys, Lily's gonna get me.
even if they did break up, that doesn't mean
we can't all ill hangout.
I mean we broke up and we still hang out. It's not weird.
It's a little weird.
Yeah, it is. It's weird.
The world needs
Marshall and Lily... together.
I'm not crying, there's something in my eye.
They're back.
Hey, hey, guys.
We have annnouncement.
I know, it's a terrible idea.
You can't do it!
Just look at me.
I hit redial on the phone.
Divorce lawyers?
Oh, I should explain.
We got in a pretty big fight.
Yeah, I know.
Marshall stormed out.
I went, uh, to the bar.
still drinking that?
I paid for it.
And apparently money's tight now, so...
Listen, I've been thinking about this,
and I know there's no way to undo what I've done,
but, well, I made an appointment with a divorce lawyer.
What?! What?!
Oh no, no, no, no-no.
-What, you want a divorce now? -No.
I just mean on paper,
so that you can buy the apartment
-without my bad credit dragging us down. -Lily...
are you trying to kill me?
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have led with the divorce lawyer part.
No, you shouldn't have
I love you, Lily.
I love you, too.
And I want us to have our dream home.
And, well, I don't know.
It seems like this is a way to do it.
So...
Marsllriksen,
will you divorce me?
That's the sweetest divorce proposal I've ever heard.
So is that a yes?
You can't sleep with other women though.
No, we're not getting divorced,
not even on paper.
When I married you, I married your problems, too.
The ones I knew about and the ones I didn't.
So, that was the deal.
We'll figure this out together.
Can I get you guys anything else?
you're not getting a divorce?
No. Wow, you guys
scared us. Oh, thank God.
Cause, I mean if you did,
then who'd be the lame married couple I get to make fun of?
Like, "Hey, Marshall, you married Miss Right.
You just didn't know her first name was Always."
That stuff is cold.
So, what's the announcement?
I just got off the phone with the Realtor.
We told her that, uh, because of our finances,
we're not getting the place.
It's just-- it's not the right time.
Is what Marshall should have said.
I just got off the phone with the Realtor.
We got the place!
We' re home on earth!
Are you insane?
Have you lost your mind?
Is what we should have said.
Yeah!
Aw! This is exciting!
Yeah. There it is!
Our new home.
Shall we?
We shall.
Oh! what a horrible smell.
It reeks.
Oh, that's just the plant.
Don't worry, they shut it down on the weekends.
Wh-What plant?
What are you talking about?
Don't you know?
Baby, this whole neighborhood is downwind
of the sewage treatment plant.
Wait... what did you just say?
I said, we're downwind of the sewage treatment plant.
www.tvsubtitles.net