Now kids
She was
but by 2008
Coming up next,is your baby trying to kill you
啥maybe
so,
so I
and
because
what
I know
I spent
cotton balls,
half of a Nerf football, but it works, right?
Totally. What's the occasion?
And old friend from Canada  is in town
and I'm meeting him  for a drink.
Ooh! Somebody you went   to Degrassi with?
No. Actually, he was  my first boyfriend.
Simon. I thought   he was the coolest guy ever.
He smelled like Drakkar.
He could ollie on a skateboard.
He had the most amazing   collection
of Hard Rock Cafe T-shirts.
We spent the whole summer  madly in love.
Tell me more.  Tell me more.
Like, did he have a car?
So he's the guy who...
How shall I say this   like a gentleman?
Robin, did he take your maple leaf?
No, it wasn't like that.
Sounds to me like he gave you  your first "O, Canada!" face.
NARROR:   This went on    for a really long time.
Some of them jokes were elegant   and well-crafted...
Wait, wait. Did he break up with you
and tell you he's just not that Inuit?
(laughing)
NARRATOR:  ...others were crude,   and ill-formed...
Um, something about fur trapping.
NARRATOR:   ...and others were obvious,    but needed to be said...
Did you ride his Zamboni?
Oh! Come on!  Oh!
(laughter)
Wait, wait, wait.  Did he...?
I think I'm out.
Yeah, I'm also "oot."
Okay, now I'm really out.
Well, I'm sorry, guys.  It was all very tame.
We only dated for a week and a half.
Wha...? I thought you said  you were together all summer.
Yeah. Summer in Canada is pretty  much the last week of July.
Anyway, one night,
his band just finish playing  this gig...
(panting)
Oh, my God! Simon.
That was such a good show.
You guys totally rocked out.
Yeah.
I know.
I figure we're about  four or five gigs away
from really exploding.
We're gonna be big, babe.
I mean, like  Crash-Test-Dummies big.
So, that everything?
Yeah.
All right.
Listen, babe...
It's over.
What?
I'm getting back together  with Louise Marsh.
Louise Marsh?!
That's a whore's name if I ever heard one.
Yeah, why would he want to get back together  with Louise Marsh?
Well, the thing is...
her folks just put in a pool.
Oh...  So...
I totally... I get it.
Pools are great.
Swimming's awesome.
We have a sprinkler.
Run right through it.
Well, I should go.
Uh...
Babe, wait.
Yeah, Simon?
You forgot to load the drum set.
No!
Tell me you did not load the drum set.
(drums feet):  I did.
(all groaning)
And now he's coming here?
Robin, why do you want to see this guy?
Oh! I know why.
You're gonna win, aren't you?
I have no idea what   you' talking about.
Yes, you do.
Whenever you haven't seen someone for a long time,
no matter how much you want to deny it,
there's always a clear winner and a clear loser.
Well, since you brought it up,
let's add up the points.
You're starting out with two big ones right there.
Thank you.
Okay. So, Simon still  lives with his mom.
Point Robin.
Um, he never became
a rock star.
Point Robin.
He now works at a water slide  park outside of Ottawa.
Point Simon.
Wait. Do they have a wave pool?
No.
Ah. Point Robin. That's five-zip.
There's no coming back  from that.
Yeah, he's going down.
I mean, unless somehow,  he got hotter.
There he is.
NARRATOR:    And sure enough,   there was a clear winner,
and a clear loser.
NARRATOR:   It just wasn't clear  to everybody.
Hey, babe.
(giggling):  Oh, my God.
Okay, what the hell just happened?
Oh, come on, it wasn't so bad, was it?
(others groan)
Hey, Simon.
Wow, look at you.
You got old.
ROBIN: Yeah.
You look great.
You got hotter,
like that's possible.
(giggles)
So...
Look, I know it didn't go  as planned,
but I can't help it.
I mean...
he's still got it.
Whoa! Four bucks for a brew?
What a rip.
Good think I'm packing.
(giggles)
So he's not a snob.
He's from a different part
of Canada, you know?
The maple leaf flag on the back  of the pickup truck?
He's Red Province.
He's from the Deep North.
The thing is,
we gave you so many  opportunities.
So, Simon,
Robin's a bit of a local celebrity here in New York.
She's the lead anchor  at Metro News One.
Tell him, Robin.
No. It's stupid.
It's not cool, like Simon's shirt.
I'm sorry, Simon.
Here we are nattering on   about our big celebrity.
What do you do for a living?
Oh, I work at the Splish Splash   Ottawa Water Slide Park.
Huh! A water slide park.
That sure is different than what Robin does.
Yeah, it is...  because I save lives.
If I'm not sitting in that stool
at the top of the slide,   going...
Go...
people die.
What, you think it's so easy?
You try it.
Um... (clears throat)... okay.
Go.
You didn't put your hand up;  kid just died.
No, I didn't know...
Another kid just went; he died too.
Oh, well, sure.  I mean, if I was actually...
Another kid just went; now you've got a pile-up
and Robin's got something  to report on the news.
This just in:  My friend, Ted, just killed  a bunch of kids today.
Well, that's cool.
You got to pay the bills somehow
since your whole music thing didn't really pan out, did it?
Well, it hasn't panned out yet,  but the band's still going.
About four or five gigs
away from really  exploding.
The Foreskins are still playing?
The Foreskins?
How'd you guys come up with that name?
(sighs)   Well, there's four of us,
and we play without shirts.
Babe, seriously.
I know. I'm sorry.
But you guys just   don't understand.
The fact that he kept the band  going-- that's impressive.
I mean, I gave up   my musical dream.
Which brings us  to the most important piece
of information from tonight.
So, Simon,
how did you guys meet?
Oh, I was in her video.
Starred in it is more like it.
Well, once you win  Mr. Teen Winnipeg,
everybody wants a piece  of the moneymaker.
I'm sorry. I've seen "Let's Go to the Mall"
about a thousand times,  and you, sir, are not in it.
No, I was   in the other one.
There's another video?!
Robin, seriously,
just make this  easier on yourself
and give us the tape.
No.
All right.
You leave me no choice.
From this moment on,
I will spend every waking minute   ching down this tape.
I will not sleep. I will not eat.
My life will be a living hell   of search engines
and overseas phone calls,
chasing down something  that possibly can't be found.
Okay.
It's just...
It was so hard to watch, Robin.
You're usually so cool.
I don't know  what's wrong with me.
I'm sitting next to Simon,  and suddenly I'm 16 again.
Oh, it's actually a common thing.
When you're around someone from your past,
you kind of revert back to who you were
when you knew them.
There's not really a name for it, though.
It's called "revertigo."
Yeah, I don't know about "revertigo."
You know who gets   really bad revertigo?
(whispers): Lily when she around
her high school   friend, Michelle.
Michelle? She sounds hot.
You don't know about Lily and Michelle?
No. What about  Lily and Michelle?
Oh, my friend,  you are in for a treat.
Hey, Lil? What?
You know, I was  just thinking,
we haven't seen your friend  Michelle in a while.
Oh, yeah. I'll give her a call,  see if she wants to hang out.
Yeah.
What... (stammers)   Do they make out?
Better.
Comparable. Comparable.
Whatever.  It's over. I lost.
I guess you, uh,  you don't get second chance.
I got a second chance.
What happened?
He came by my place tonight...
Simon.   What are you doing here?
I just feel like there's   some unfinished business
between you and me.
Seeing you now...
has made me realize   that breaking up with you
is the biggest mistake   I made in my entire life.
Oh, I like where  this is going.
I know this is crazy,
and I'm only in town  for a couple of days,
but do you want to go  on a date?
He asked you out?!
Oh, step into my web, Simon.
The coup de grace.
(a la Mortal Kombat):  Finish him!
I'd love to!
Wait. You're going  on a date with Simon?
That Simon?The one we met?
Robin, this guy doesn't deserve a second chance.
Not after the way  he treated you.
That was ten years ago. People evolve.
I mean, are you the same person that you were in high school?
Oh, hell, no!
I think you're gonna enjoy this.
That my girl Michelle?  Bitch, you know it!
How she livin'?  She living only way she know how to.
Large!
Oh, girl, you gots to get your drink on up in here.
I'm hoping my t ass can  hustle me up a vodka-Gatorade.
For reals.
I want her around   all the time.
I'd even consider not trying to sleep with her
if that's what it takes.
Guys, I've decided  to seduce Michelle.
(rock music playing)
(laughs)
(song ends)
(Robin whoops)
Yeah!   Guys, that was great.
Let's take five.
Hey, babe,  did you like it
after my bass solo when   I flicked my pick at you?
That rocked.
Yeah.
Uh, 'cause I'm gonna need that pick back.
Oh, uh, sure.
Um, I think it...
It's cool. You'll  find it later. Oh, cool.
I wish I didn't have to go to work in the morning.
Oh, but, babe, you  got to go to work.
You got to play our  demo on your show.
Oh, well, you know, it's not a show.
It's the news.
Right. So you   can be, like,
"Hey, did you hear  there's some news?
There's a rad band you  guys should check out."
And then play it.
Or just, like, the  first three songs.
And now it's time  for "Puppy Corner,"
some little angels looking for a new home,
courtesy of the Midtown Animal Shelter.
* Murder
* Climb aboard  the Murder Train *
* Climb aboard  the Murder Train... *
Hey, a lot of puppies got adopted.
Of course, a lot of the   people calling in thought
we were going   to kill them.
Robin, your revertigo is really   starting to affect your work.
What's revertigo?
It's a stupid, made-up word   with no meaning.
No. It's a   phenomenon where,
when you're around  people from your past,
you start behaving  like them.
Oh. One example of that springs to mind.
I think we all know what it is.
You do?
Yeah. Ted.
Me?
Whenever Ted's friend Punchy comes into town,
it's like, all of a sudden, Ted's in high school again.
TED: Okay, okay.
First of all,  his name is Adam Punciarello,
and I don't do that.
(both scoffing)
(knocking, classical music plays)
Ooh. That must be Adam.
'Sup, Punchy?  'Sup, Shmosby?!
You want to go?  I'm alrey there!
Come on!  This is it!
Dude, seriously,   I'm sorry about your dad.
Yeah, it was   a real shock.
I can't believe you, of all people, are saying this.
Why?
No reason.
Robin, the point is,  what are you doing?
I mean, this guy?
Okay, you want the truth?
Yeah. I like Simon.
I do.
We have fun together.
Oh, we know you do, honey, but we're worried about you.
You're worried?
Okay, hold on.
Is there any version  of this conversation
where you guys don't sound   like my parents?
I don't know. Is there any version
where you don't sound like a 16-year-old?
That's exactly what   my mom would say.
No. If I was your mom, I woulsay,
"We forbid you from seeing this boy."
(scoffs)  Lily!
No, I'm sorry, but it's for your own good.
(teary):   This is my life!
You guys just don't get it!
You've never felt the way  that I feel!
Now, now. We were once  young and in love, too.
Yeah, like, a  billion years ago.
You've been drinking, haven't you?
Yeah, we all have.
You bought the  last round.
You're not going to that show tonight!
Oh, yes, I am, and you know what else?
Tonight, after the show,
Simon and I are going  all the way!
(all gasping)
Young lady, get back here!
(teary): Thanks for your help.
Hey, so, today at work...
Not now, Ted!
Geez.
Ooh!
Oh, hey, Simon.
Great show.
You guys still rock.
Yeah.
They totally dug my bass solo.
Man!
Why can't I always   feel this alive?!
God, I just love  seeing you so happy.
Yeah. (laughs)
About that.
Listen, babe.
It's over. What?
I'm getting back together  with Louise Marsh.
(laughing):  What?
You're kidding me.
You're breaking up with me?
Again?
F-For the same ex-girlfriend?
In the same van?
What is it?
Her-Her parents got a pool?
Is that still the reason?
Well...
I'm sorry, Robin.
I'm fine, really.
Oh, Robin, I'm gonna tell you for real.
Simon's a dawg.
You feel me, Chelle?
Mm-hmm, for reals.
He a scrub.
Mm. True dat.
I'ma get me my champagne  and grape soda on.
So, how's Columbia?
Great!
I'm almost done  with my disstation.
Hmm. I'm getting a PhD in  behavioral psychology.
Um, can I make an observation?
Oh.
I know.
Whenever I'm around Lily,
she just brings out   that side of me.
There's a psychological term  for the phenomenon.
Revertigo? No.
Actually, it's associative  regression. You see,
the neural pathways that...
*
Oh, no, you did not just
put on my jam!
Oh. Put your hands up, girl!
Holla! Holla!
NARRATOR:   One by one,  we all had to go home.
Soon, it was just Robin.
BARNEY: All right.
I can't find your video.
I've wasted three days tr...
*
What's the matter?
Uh... Simon dumped me
in his van after the show.
Yeah, Robin, that was,  like, ten years ago.
No, tonight.
Ooh.
(laughing): Really?
Oh! Oh, come here.
(sobbing) Come here.
*
It's just...
when I was young,  I was so...
vulnerable and-and open to things, you know?
And... I guess I just... I wanted to feel that way again.
I wanted to be 16 again.
Robin, that is the stupidest thing
I've ever heard come out of your mouth.
You want to be 16 again?
I have watched your first
Robin Sparkles video 1,000 times,
and it's not because I'm proud of you as a friend.
It's because you were totally, totally lame back then.
But now, come on. Pa-cow!
You're the most awesome person I have ever known.
Well, second most awesome.
Right. Of course, the-the first being you.
No.
No. The first is this guy
who lives in a place called the mirror.
(laughs) What up.
Oh.
I'm saying
that you are way more awesome than Simon ever will be.
*
Barney, do you want to  come back to my place?
Your place?
*
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yeah. I am.
Let's just not tell anyone   about this, okay?
Of course.
So, should I just put it in?
Yeah, why not?
(sighs)
(instrumental intro  to pop ballad plays)
* Met you at the mall...
This was my big artistic follow-up
to"Let's Go to the Mall."
It kind of tanked.
* My friends said I was a fool
You're a fool.    Shut up!
Is that Tiffany? Mm-hmm.
* 'Cause you were older and got kicked out of school *
You are so rad.
* Together we we gonna  travel the globe *
* From Alberta to Ontario
It's everything   I want it to be and more.
Oh, I'm so glad.  Mm-hmm.
* And now I'm building   sandcastles in the sand *
* Sandcastles in the sand *
* Thought I could fly when you held my hand *
* Thought I could fly *
But now...
* Eternity returns to black and white... *
Is that Alan Thicke?
Yeah.
* It was the greatest   week and a half *
* Of my life
* We used to go to the beach
You know, if  you reedit it,
there's a tampon commercial  in here somewhere.
* On our favorite bench
* We'd sit and talk  and you taught me to french *
* You're good at...
Do you seem how lame  you were back then?
Yeah, you're right. I was lame.
Totally lame. Ugh.
* ...so unfair...
ROBOT: You don't understand about love.
And, of course, the robot  makes an appearance
in the sad love ballad.
He was my sidekick. He had to be.
NARRATOR:  And so they watched it again.
* Come back, please
* I've changed my mind
* Let's go all the way
I love you.
Let's do it.
I miss you.
NARRATOR:   And again.
* Sandcastles may be cute
I'm on the pill now.
NARRATOR:   And again.
* But now all they do   is remind me of you... *
They watched it over and over   that night until finally,
they stopped watching.
www.tvsubtitles.net