Kids, there's more than one
story of I met your mother.
You know the short version,
the thing with your mom's
yellow umbrella.
But there's a bigger story.
The story of how I became
who I had to become
before I could meet her.
And that story begins here.
...dary!
Legendary!
Dude, I am so excited
that you're single again.
We are going to conquer
New York City.
I already have a girl
from work lined up for you.
Right boob bigger
than the left boob,
which some choose to look
at as bra half empty,
I choose to look
at as bra half full.
I don't know.
Robin and I broke up
two weeks ago.
I'm... I'm not ready.
When will you be ready?
It was a good question.
After a big relationship ends,
you need some time
to recuperate.
Robin took a trip to Argentina,
and I went through
my usual routine.
I grew my breakup beard.
Ted Mosby, suit up,
'cause here's the plan.
There's a Miss Nassau
County pageant.
We'll pretend to be judges
and, yes, our votes
are for sale.
I'm not ready.
I repainted the apartment.
Finish Line of a women's 10K.
Salty girls on
an endorphin high
who just want to lie down.
Yeah.
I'm not ready.
And the truth is,
I was doing really good.
Female acrobats
from Montreal.
Hmm.
Super flexible.
We are going to get
Cirque de So-Laid.
What up?
Barney, come on,
we've covered this.
Robin!
Hey, guys.
I just got in last night.
Um, uh, this is Gael.
Hola.
Okay, I'm ready.
Subsfactory presents:
How I Met Your Mother
Season 3 Episode 1
"Wait For It"
Synch by: redman
I just can't believe her.
We have this totally
amicable split,
everything's cool.
And she comes back
from vacation withthatguy?
You know what she's doing?
She's trying to win the breakup.
What do you mean "win the
breakup," old-timey inventor?
What our 21st president,
Chester A. Arthur,
is trying to say is that
in every breakup there are
winners and a losers.
It's not a
competition.
Now, your 80-day
balloon race around the world,
that was a competion.
That's my wife.
Of course it's
a competition, Lil.
How else do you explain...
what's his name?
Gael.
I'm sorry, Gayle?
Kyle?
Gael.
Girl?
It's pronounced "guy-el. "
It means "joyful. "
That is why I live
my life by bringing joy,
good energy
and happiness to others.
Especially those
less fortunate that I.
I'm sorry, so it's Gayle?
What a jerk.
I don't go
to your stupid country
and try to seduce women
with my sexy accent.
That's a great point,
Persian nightclub owner.
Oh, and he's a masseuse.
With a massage,
everything is connected.
I can touch your foot,
cleanse your kidney.
I can touch
your earlobe,
and slow your heartbeat.
One time, I used warm water
to make a guy pee.
Of course, I didn't
make a career out of it.
Career?
Such an American idea.
My career is living.
Windsurfing.
Making love.
Sometimes at the same time.
How?
How would one do that exactly?
Seriously, don't giggle.
Tell me.
Not possible.
You cannot have sex
on a windsurfing board.
How do you know?
Glad you asked, Lily.
I have crafted a list
of every vehicle...
land-based, aquatic
and airborne...
in which/on which it's
possible to have sex.
And of those 33 vehicles,
I have had sex in/on 31.
Windsurfing board,
not on the list, not possible.
Oh, P.S., in order
to hit 33, all I need is
bobsled and the Apollo 11
space capsule.
To get that last one, you'd have
to break into the Smithsonian.
This conversation
never happened.
All right, you're suited up,
I'm bearded down.
Let's get out there
and win this thing.
Yes!
You guys, have fun
on your double date.
Oh, for the hundredth time,
I'm sorry, there was a lull.
And then we fell asleep
on the beach
while counting the stars.
Do you want to have
dinner with me? Uh, us?
There was no lull.
You just think
he's incredibly hot.
No, I don't!
Not incredibly.
It's a little hard to believe
how hot he is.
But, I mean,
she's serious
about him.
The girl never marries
the hot guy.
Well, you did.
I'm one of the lucky few.
Lily, Ted is our best friend,
so let's get something straight:
Male Gayle is not hot.
He's not our friend.
Don't even look at him.
Just... no eye contact.
So that night,
as Lily and Marshall
did their best to hate Gael...
Hey, Robin. Gael.
...Robin pulled me aside
to check in.
Now, I'm sure
she meant the best,
but she said the worst.
I just want to make sure
you're okay with this.
"I just want to make sure
you're okay with this"?
Damn it! I can't
believe she's the one
that gets to say that.
She's winning, isn't she?
Not for long.
Okay, pep talk.
Take a knee.
Ted, tonight we're going to get
you someone way hotter
than Robin.
Okay, Robin's a ten.
Fine, we'll get you a 12.
Or, you know...
two sixes.
Failing that, four threes.
And break glass
in case of emergency,
we'll go to Staten Island,
I'll get you 12 ones.
Ted, my boy,
I am going to re-teach you...
Amy.
Ted.
Barney.
Ted, we are back!
Up here.
Up high.
Fivin' it up
five-style!
I'm sorry this is
all so weird.
Weird, why would it be weird?
Because you used
to date our best friend
or because my wife thinks
your new boyfriend
is incredibly hot?
I do not! Shut up!
Oh, my God!
I just hope Ted's okay.
Hmm.
I hate to see you so tense.
I mean, we had a really
clean break up, you know?
We really acted like adults,
so the last thing... oh!
Gael, are you a properly
licensed massage therapist?
What?
Are you legally
certified by some type
of governing entity?
I train for three years at
an institute in Buenos Aires.
I have a card.
I can show you.
Is the card laminated?
What do you mean "laminated"?
Covered in protective plastic.
Oh, yes.
Damn it.
He checks out.
Ted. Ted.
What?!
Let's bail, this
place is dead.
Yeah, you're right.
We're both totally striking out.
Exactly, plus,
we're on a tight schedule.
I've got this entire evening
perfectly planned
out... spoiler alert:
our last stop is
an after hours club
so after hours, it's
three days from now.
What up.
Are you blind?
I'm making out with a 12.
I am winning.
Yeah, but I didn't get to help.
So you're saying
you want me to throw away
a super hot girl just because
you didn't help me get her?
Apology accepted.
Let's go.
Who's the suit?
This is Barney.
Barney, Amy.
I'm not gonna remember that.
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
random chick from
earlier tonight,
as you shall
henceforth be known,
Ted and I have a
schedule to keep.
Oh, well, you can check off
8:54, dress up like a dork
and bother the cool kids.
Beat it, nerd.
Wow. Wow.
Great stuff, Tommy Lee.
See, what you don't
understand is
I'm Ted's wingman.
It's a sacred bond,
much stronger than any...
They're making out again.
Massage therapist.
And you know what, "Gayle"?
Your piece of chicken
looks a little tense to me.
Oh, oh, does that
feel good, Mr. Chicken?
Well, guess what?
I didn't wash my hands.
Got him.
Lily!
We carry so much
ancient emotion
in our neck
and shoulders.
Things we should have
let go of years ago.
I forgive you, Mom.
Lily, we are Ted's
best friends.
Our job is to hate that guy.
Oh, yeah,
that's what I was doing.
I was just building him up
so a few minutes later,
I could totally cut him down.
Weren't you wearing a bra?
The night was going great.
Amy was cool and dangerous.
She found a friend for Barney.
She even paid for drinks...
sort of.
They know us here.
You're gonna get
us in trouble.
Tell me something.
Do you ask your tailor
to leave extra room
in the crotch
for your huge vagina?
You... your vagina...
Ted, this chick is crazy.
We're leaving.
Good idea.
Let's all go back
to my place.
Your place?
Thanks but no thanks,
1994 Courtney Love.
I have a hot tub.
Okay, this is
actually pretty nice.
I like your tatts.
Thanks, you can play
with them if you want.
They're a hundred
percent real.
No, your tatts... toos,
your tattoos.
Thanks.
You should get one.
Wrong. Ted has a classic,
clean-cut look
that never goes out of style
season after season, burn.
Yeah? Well, I think he
would look hot with some ink.
No, he wouldn't.
Yes, he would.
Yuh-huh.
Nuh-uh.
I'm ready to do anything
you want by the way.
Anything. Right now.
Ted, who are you gonna side
with on this tattoo thing?
I think I'd look
way hot with some ink.
Yeah, you would.
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Tyler?
Mommy! Daddy!
She's back!
Damn it, they're supposed
to be in the Hamptons. Run!
Sorry. I used to nanny
for those jerks
before they fired me.
So unfair.
Unfair?
I wouldn't let you take care
of the imaginary kids
I make up to score
with single moms.
That's it, Ted.
We're going home.
Ted?
Ted, you okay?
Hello, Ted.
Robin and I are about to make
fantastic aquatic sex
on this windsurfing board.
And I just want to make sure
you're okay with this.
Okay, how do we do this?
I think your leg
goes up, up...
Okay, how about if I, um...
No, mine...
I'm okay.
In fact, here's
how okay I am.
I'm getting a tattoo.
You're not getting
a tattoo, it's not you.
Ted, you are heading
down a dark path.
That dark path
is my driveway.
But you need a plan
and you need a wingman!
This is so going
in my blog!
Want to have sex?
Okay.
And underneath,
it should
say, "I win. "
And then it should have
flames coming out the bottom.
Fire!
We should start a fire.
After this maybe.
Oh, man, this is
going to be legend.
Wait for it.
And that's all I rember.
The next morning,
I woke up alone back home.
Hey, buddy, how
was your night?
You know,
it was great.
I met this crazy girl,
I almost got a tattoo.
Don't worry.
I didn't, but it was...
It was amazing.
I think it's safe to say,
I am winning this breakup.
Look.
Oh, my God.
What?
Nothing.
This J. Crew catalog.
Who brings two Golden
Retrievers in a canoe?
We got to
call Barney.
Way ahead of you.
Hey, guys, what's
the big emergency?
Oh, and B the W:
I am never speaking
to Ted again.
Mm.
Really? Never?
Not even if, say,
butterflies flew out of his ass?
What?
Ted?
Could you grab me
the fondue pot?
He has no idea.
And up we go.
Thank you.
What?
Ted?
Mm?
I came here
this morning because...
I want to apologize.
Apology accepted, Barney.
As you can see, I do
just fine on my own.
I don't need a baby-sitter.
See, all this time,
I thought you need
a wingman to fly,
but the truth is, you...
you've got your
own wings now.
Mm.
Since you and Robin split,
you've been gestating.
Growing in your coon.
And last night...
...you burst out of
that cocoon like a...
like a majestic, uh...
Gosh, what is it that
comes out of a cocoon?
I was always
bad at science.
He's going to say it!
A butterfly?
What?
Nothing, buddy.
Ow! Why did that hurt so...?
Oh, my God!
I have a tattoo!
Oh, that's not a tattoo.
That, dear boy,
is a tramp stamp.
A tramp stamp.
You know, a ho tag.
Ass antlers.
A Panama City license plate.
And suddenly,
it all came back to me.
...dary!
Legendary!
Man, I am so winning
this breakup.
Mm. I just broke up
with my boyfriend Steve.
He was totally annoying.
He was, like,
"I think you're the one,
I want to marry you. "
What a wuss.
Do you think
exes can be friends?
Yeah, sure.
I mean, we're still friends,
right, Steve?
Hey, your
name is Steve.
And her
ex-boyfriend's name is Steve.
What are the odds of that...?
Wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Give me this.
Oh, yeah, that'll
get it out.
Maybe you should
try club soda.
Ow. Damn it, it really hurts.
I need, like,
some ointment
or something.
What's this?
Spanish massage oil.
Spanish massage oil?
What happened here last night?
Last night got weird.
Feel the emotions release.
Think I just got over
being chunky in the ninth grade.
You're beautiful.
I am beautiful.
Experience your food.
Try the mango.
Okay, that's enough
of the fruit.
We're sorry, Ted.
It'll never happen again.
It meant
nothing to us.
It just felt really,
really, really good.
Oh! I can't even look
at you two right now.
Ted...
He got a tramp stamp.
All right, first of all,
this isn't one of those,
"I came all the way over here
because I want you back" things.
There'll be no startling
confession of love,
no sweet indie rock
song that swells up
just as we're about to kiss,
none of that crap. Got it?
Okay.
Good.
Now, here's the thing.
It sucks that you came
back from Argentina
with someone as
awesome as Gael.
And I know I have no
right to be upset at you.
We're broken up, life
goes on, whatever.
But you know what?
We-We never did this.
We-We had this
polite breakup
with no irrational
yelling, and...
and that's just wrong!
So, I'm going to yell
irrationally for a little while,
and you're just going
to have to stand there
and deal with it, okay?
If you feel like
you need to do that, then...
I think I do!
I really think I do!
So now I'm yelling!
You shaved.
I did!
I liked the beard.
I liked it, too, but it
was getting kind of hot!
Maybe in the winter,
I'll grow it back out!
Okay, I'm done.
I know it was weird
showing up with Gael.
I'm sorry.
Look, us breaking up...
it was the right thing.
But it took some time to
get over you, you know?
I- I'm still
getting over you.
But you? You were over it
the minute they started
the in-flight movie.
Over it?!
My first three days
in Argentina,
I cried my eyes out.
I missed you
so much.
I wanted to go
and prove how adventurous I am,
but the truth is...
it was really lonely.
And that's why Gael happened.
You weren't trying
to win the breakup?
I was trying to survive it.
Okay.
No.
See, look, that
all sounds good, and
we'll still be friends
and move on, but...
did he have to be so hot?
The guy's
an Adonis.
He's not an Adonis.
He's the Cadillac
of rebound guys.
Marshall has a
crush on him!
The guy's perfect.
He's not perfect.
Oh, come on.
He's hot, he wind surfs,
he massages things.
Name one way I'm
better than that guy.
You're bigger.
Don't patronize
me. If anything,
he may even be a
little bit taller.
No. Ted... you're bigger.
I win!
Kids, I can't remember exactly
what helped me get through
the whole Robin-Gael incident.
I'm sure that it was something
profound and meaningful,
and not at all macho and petty,
but after that,
I was back on my feet.
And what followed was a new era
in my life,a crazy time
unlike anything
that came before.
It's funny looking back
at those days,
knowing now exactly
what I was heading towards.
And what was heading
towards me.
Go for Barney.
Hey, man, it's Marshall.
Check your e-mail.
Sent you something.
What is it?
Just a new Web site.
Slapcountdown. com.
What does this mean?
M- Marshall?
Ma...
No.
}; before I could meet her.
And that story begins here.
Host: www.CsSubs.org - Thanks Guys
www.tvsubtitles.net