kids I know you think you have ever heard of a story
from back before I met your mother,
but there are some stories you tell
|| and some stories you don't.
(breathless): Oh, my God!...
(s||aking gibberish) Oh, my God...
Use your words, Ted.
Okay. Barney, I'm about to go for the belt.
||The||belt?
||The belt.
||But that's impossib||.
You were up here less than half a||hour ago.
(grunts)
||runts)
(groans) Yes! Advantage-- Ericksen.
Don't get cocky. Wimbledon ||sts a fortnight.
|| "Fortnight."
|| British words are so cool.
|| ||Plus, did you know lawyers there get to wear wigs?
I wear a wig to work, I'm a jackass.
|| TED: ||l right.
I'm We can't go. Tournament.
|||| What? We agreed. I suited up...
|| You take too long to get r||dy.
|| What are you talking about?
||I got the low maintenance, just-rolled-||t-of-bed look.
Yeah, which takes an h||r and a half
of waxing, tugging and teas||g to achieve.
|||||| And then he starts on his hair.
Ac|| ||(feigned laughter)
|| Look, are we ||going or not?
Just go without us. We'll be there in five minutes.
Really?
Yes! Yes!
|| All right, I'm going down to the bar.
|| I'm ordering three beers||
||I'll see you guys in five mi||tes.
Three beers, five minutes.
|| Wii AN||UNCER: Love-30! (door closes)
Thanks for lending me these boots.
|| Where'd you get them from?
This sto|| in the Village had one of those crazy sales.
It was a footwear ||feeding frenzy.
|||| (shrieking and shouting)
|| I saw it f||st!
|| (screams)||
You just made the list, bitch!
So many questions.||
Firstly, w||t do you think would happen
if a guy walked into that store wearing a suit of boots?
|| You look fantastic in them, Robin.
But don't you think they're a little high for that dress?
|| Well, that's the po||t: it's to hide that||act
|| that I h||en't shaved my legs.
|| I've begun a strict no-shave policy
|||| ||for the first three dates.
It's all about self-control.
If I don't shave, I mu|| behave.
|| FYI: It doesn't matter, baby.
Guys just want to get ||on the green.
They don|'t mind going through the rough.
|| Shh-clackey! (phone ringing)
Stinson.
All right, the beers are here.
|| BARNEY:||Yeah, we're not go to make it.
Oh, come on! We agreed...
|| Did Marshall take his pants off?
Yeah, pants are off.
This is Wimble||n, Ted.
|| I need the freedom and mobility that only underwear can provide.
|||||||| Cheerio!
|| Fine.
I don't need friends.
|| I got you guys.
|||| You guys are my friends,
mI'm talking to beer.iends.||||||
Ted? Trudy.
|||| Trudy.
Oh, my God. I haven't seen you since...
|||| (moaning ecstatically)
|| I slept with||ou and then climbed down the fire es||pe.
That was you?
I'm kidding. I was super-wasted.
|||||| These are not all for me.
|| No, I was going to call you, but I was so embarrassed.
|| You were embarrassed?
I was like, "I really like this guy,
"and now I'm ||imbing out his window,
|| ||and I forgot my underwear..."
|| God, I thought they felt kind of tight.
I'm ki||ing. I don't wear underwear.||
|| Ladies' underwear.
|||| Often.
Ah! Again, I'm ||dding.
|| I'm so glad I ran into you.
I know. Do you want to...? Trudy?!
|| No way!
|| ||Oh, my God! Rachel, how ||e you?
|| (both shrieking and laughi||)
|| Ted, this is Rachel.
Hi!||
Kappa Epsilon Gamma! Kappa Epsilon Gamma!
|||| Whoo! Whoo!
Wait, let me guess. You guys met in ||ison.
|| (laughing)
No! We were ||rority sisters.
And best friends forever all sophomore year.
|||| When we weren't at each other's throats.
We could be so competitive.
||Uh, but that's all behind us now.
|| (chanting): Hey, m||ta! Hey, mista!
|||| Stay away from m||sista! Stay away from my sista!
|| Whoo! Whoo!
|| We have so||uch catching up to do.
Okay. Are you going to Stacey's wedding?||
Oh, it's off. Apparently, he's into dudes.
Nah! Again|| That's like her third one.
TRUDY: I kn||!
|| Well, beers, what do you want to do?
We could stay here...
|||| or I know this o||er place called "My Belly."
|||| So, Trudy and I got a table.
Oh, that'||s cool. I was going to get out of here anyway.
|||| I'm really t||ed.
I want you to stay.
|||| Tired of people who fold early, 'cause I am wide awake!
|||||||| (giggl||)
|| Okay, gu||... be cool.
||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||
||You've been vanquished, old bean.
That's 'cause you distracted me.
You've been hanging crumpet ever since the third set.
(phone rings)
||... Stinson.
I've got a situation.
Trudy is here-- you know, from the pineapple inc||ent?
||Oh, you mean the girl that chalked your pool cue
and then snuck down ||e fire escape?
Respect.
||So, we're hitting it off and then her f||end shows up
and they're kind of compet||ive.||
I think the new girl's kind of into me.
So you now have two on the line?
And I don't know which one to go for.
Given the choice, always party with Dr. Strangelove.
New girl? Wh|| new girl?
Two girls are allegedly vying
for Ted's affections, and I think...
Oh, you don'||kn|| what you'|| talking about.
Give it to me.
||Are they friends?
Yeah. Uh, no-- I-I d||'t know. ||They're old sorority sisters.
||Are they Betas?
BecI didn't want to beuts, andin their sorority anyway.now||
||||They're Kappas, and...
||||||I think I can score ||th one of them.
||don't know which one,
||and if I chose wrong, I lose them both.
||Okay, well, don't worry.
I'll-I'll come down and help you figure it out.
||I thought we were in ||for the evening?
That's what I thought about your bangers and mash down there,
but I guess we're both wrong, guv'na.
||Hey. Oh||Ted. Okay...||
Settle an argument. Mm-hmm.
Is it stealing if you go out with someone's boyfriend
after they've broken up?
Well, that's very complicated...
||||See?! || agrees wi|| me.
||||||u're||uch a li||le man||hief.
||||Oh, somebody should lock you girls up.|||
||||(giggling)
You're so funny.
I think Ted || funny.
||Really? I think Ted is hilarious.
||||||(phone rings) I am never not wearing a suit again.
||||||Hello?
It's me. I'm at t|| bar.
Don'||t lo||. Just call me "Mom."
Uh, hey, Mom. How's Dad's... colon?
||||||What? What's the matter with you?
Anyway, both of these girls are into you; take your pick.
||They are? Are you ||re|| Yes, of course.
|||||| They're playing with their hair and touching your arm.
|| Classic green light.
Are you positive?
||Oh, that is so fascinating.
|||| So what happened?
Well, after 18 hours of surgery,
|| I closed, and, thankfully,
|| both girls just celebrated their second birthday.
Wow. Gosh, separating conjoined twins,
|||| that must be the most amazing feeling.
|||| True, but now the parents don't ||ow what to do
|| with their huge supply of four-legged overalls.
|| (laugh...||That is so funny.
|| You're so funny.
|| LILY|| Positive. They both want you bad.||
|| It's a clearance sale ||and you're the boots, ba||.
|||| Oh, it's Robi|| Good luck.
|| Bye, Mom.
|| ||That'||my mom.
Hello?
||Bring me a razor.|| What about the no-shave ||le?
What happened to your conv||tions?
|| They've been surgically removed||by Dr.
||||No, I'm not doing it.
The whole point to not shaving was to...
Lily, please! He's really cute,
|| and I really like ||m, and he's got a British accent.
I'm on my way.
So this college boyfriend, ||who won h
|| Neither of us.
|| He left. Junior year abroad.
|||||||| It's really too bad, 'cause...
|||| there was that||ne thing we wanted to do.
|||||||| We wer|| going to do...
but we never did.||
Why? Wai|| what were you guys going to do but never did?
|| No, it'||s too embarrassing.
You tell him. No, you tell him.
No, I don't care if y|| don't care.
Well, I don'|| care. I just...
Nobody cares! Just say it.
|| Why do|'t we tell him together.
|||| Okay.
On three.
|| Well, he's right: One.||it'...two...heat.||||||||
||Neither one is givi|| ground.
I could not tell who was the th||d ||eel.
|||||| ...three.
It's a tricycle.
No way, no way, no way!
|| ||What's happening?
|| It's a tric||le.
|| || way, no way, no way.
|| It's a tricycle.
|||||| Well, I'll just say it right now.
|| All ||rority girls are sluts.
|||| Put him on speaker.
||So what you're saying to us right now
is that you have a ||ot at the belt?
|| Wait-wait-wa||. What belt?
Well, Barney and I have
this running joke that the first gu||to actually pull this off
would "win" the championship belt.
|| Oh, so it's a me||phorical belt, right?
*******
|||| You actually bought a belt....||||
That's right. It'||resplendent.
Come on, it was just a thing we said.
|| We were kidding ar||nd.
|| I never kid.
Remember you said if I e||r slept with that girl
from Days of Our Lives, I'd be the king?
Well...
|| Why wasn't I told about the ||lt?
I could go for the belt.
(Barney, Lily, Ted laugh)
|||| If Lily would've died before me, then I could ride the tricycle.
|||| Guys, come on! Help me out.e back aWhat do I do? penis.||||
All right, Ted, if you're going to go for the belt,
|| then t|| bylaws require me to ask the following questions:
One: Is the aggregate age of all participants under 83?
|||| Yes.
Two: Is the aggregate weight of all participants
|| under 400 pounds?
|||| Yes.
Theodore Mosby...
are you pWhat? No.se women?||
Ted...
|||| No. Look, I got to go. They're going to think
|| I inherited my dad's imaginary ||throom issues.||||||Oh, are yo
|| Well, it is ||tting pretty late.
|| Righ|| Well, well, it's been...
|||| Mayb||we could all g|| listen to that Wilco||D
|| you talked about before.||
Great! I have it right upstairs.
It's in my apartment upstairs. Let'||s go upstairs.
|| I'm sorry. Where was ||Ha, that's funny. I love that.
|| You should tell more jokes in my apartment upstairs.
|||||||||| Scenario #12: We're in a horrific car crash.
|||||| You die. I'm left paralyzed.
|| Two sexy nurses, with a six-pack of wine coolers,
sneak into my room late at night.
I try to blink at them in Morse code.
|| "P||ase, d||'t. I love my dead wife."
|||||||||||| But they're medical profes||onals,
and I got to think||somehow, they're saving my life.
|||||| Fine. Sleep with your nu||es.
|| To||ght you ride the unicycle.
|||| I already did this morning.
|||| (p||ne rings) Hello.
Lily, I have pounded three cappuc||nos waiting for you.
Pretty soon, I won't have to shave--
the hair is going to vibrate off my legs.
I'm sorry, I can't leave now.
Lily, he can'||t see my legs like t||s.
|| I look like a Turkish lesbian.
|| There's, um, a pharmacy across||he street.
|||||||| Would 20 b||ks buy me a razor?
No, but 50 will.
|||| (phone beeps) Hold on. Ted's texting me.
|||||| "We're combing||p-sars."
|||| "Combing It means they'||re What does coming upstairs.
|||| (laughter)
|||||| Got 'em.
|| (chuckles nervously)
|| Ooh! Nice ||||e.
Hey, are these your roommates?
Yes. Uh, yes, but they are not here.
|||| They are somewhere else.
We have total privacy
because privacy is ess||tial when you're listening to music.
|||| You know what else is essential when you're listening to music?
|| Music.
That's hi||rious.
|| You are hilarious!||
I'll go get it in my bedr||m.
||The CD's in my bedroom.
|| Bedroom...
|||| Okay. We'll try and stay out of trouble.
|| Of course, we can't promise anything.
|| (both giggling)
|| This is going to be awesome.
|||||||| (whispering loudly): No!
**
****
We know, Ted, well done.
mpressive.|||||| Up top. Yeah, bro, up top.
*****8888
|| Oh, don't be gross.
TED: You guys need to get out of her||
Please, take the fire escape.
|| No, no way.
The other day I saw ||a pigeon take a ap on it
and the whole thing shifted.
Oh, you can use our bedroom.
Okay, all I need to seal the deal
is the Wilco CD, Barney.
|| (gasping)
|| What are you doing?!
|| I cannot allow Ted to do this.
|||| Wh-what? Why?
Because the belt is my birthright!
||You cannot claim it before I do.
|| That would be like Jimmy Olsen capturing Lex Luth||
|| while Superman watches ||impotently from the bedroom.
But, B||ney, you|'ve done||||way dirtier
|||||||| You're disgusting.
I've never ridden the tricycle.
||||||I was on the verge last year.
|| I was so close.
(all giggling)
|| So ladies, why don't we||ove this party
|||||| to a||ore horizontal location?
|| Oh, my God, my new carpet!
Oh, my God, this is a disaster.
You get the ca||et cleaner. I'll get a||owel.
|| Okay. ||I'll get the video camera.
Get out! Okay then.
|| So let me get this straight.
You're going to trike-block me?
That is so petty. It's like you're...
|| Tom Petty. Tom Petty.
|||| You're Tom Petty.
|| Wh|||'s Lily?
|| ||ill looking for that CD,
so...
|||| (whispering): What are you doing?
I knew it. I had a hunch about that girl
|| and I was right.
(shouting): I saw it f||st!
You just made th||list, bitch.
|||||||| I ||nnot give up my bedroom to a boot thief.
||She should be punished, not rewarded.||
Fine, then I'll try to work in a little light spanking. Just do this for me!
|| No, never.
Wh|| if I reimburse you for the boot|| full retail?
|||| Please enjoy||ur bedroom. Great.
Just take it.
Okay, wish me luck.
|||||||||| Oh, my God. It looks fine.
You're such a girl.
Where's the shaving cream?
||ll, you didn't ask me for shaving cream.
|||| Well, it w|| implied.
Who bu|| a razor without buying||having cream?
Well, who doesn't shave their legs for a date?
||Well, who's not ge||ing a tip because of her attitude?
Well, here's a little tip for you:
shave ||ur legs before you leave the house, Sasquatch.
|||||||| Hey, Robin, um, the valet's brought the car ||ound.
|||| I thought we'd go to my place,
if you're in the mood for a nightcap.
Absolutely. I just have to go to the ladies' room.
|| I've got TB.
|||| Tiny bladder.
|| I'll meet you out front.
Yeah.
|||||||||||||| You'vExcuse me. Sorry.ng me.||||||||
|||||||||||||||||||||||||| So, I'm having a little ||trouble finding the CD.
|| That's okay.
|| We don't need music t||have fun.
|||| ||actly.
|||| You do like to have fu|| don't you, Ted?
|| (heart pounding)||
|||||||| It|'s getting late. I'll get your coats.
|||||| "I'll get your coats"?!
|| I don't know why I said that|| Why'd I say that?
|| It's the opposite of what I meant.
|| I wanna take clothes off them, not put more on.
Ted, you're ruining this for ever||ne.
|| Leave him alone!
|| Sometimes even
the greatest warriors shoot them||lves in the foot.
|||| What are you talking about?
If you must know, it wasn't a freak beverage malfunction
|||||| that stopped me from riding the tricycle that night.
||So, Barney, why don't we
|| take this party to a more horizontal location?
|||||||| (heart pounding)
|||||||||| Oh, no, the night's ruined!
|||||| No, baby, it's not.
Ye|| it is! Whatever this night was heading towards is ruined.
||||Where's my coat?
|| Why would you do that to yourself?
Because you get up in your head, man.
Yo||start thinking,
"I can't do this. It's two women."
|| That's two of everything, four of some things.
The ||gistics alon||are enough to cripple even a pro like me.
Se|| if a complete degenerate like Barney choked,
what chance do I have?
|| The best chance in the world.
|||||||||||| ||Fear took the belt from me.
|||||||| Fear rode th||tricycle that night, my friends.
|||||| ||But fear will not get a second turn.
|| It won't? No.
|||| Because I now realize it isn't my destiny to win the belt.
|||| It is my destiny to help my friend win it.
|||||||||| Ted is fated to go there first.
|||| He is our Neil Armstrong.
|||| ||(laughs): Spacesuit up, Ted,
'cause you're||oing to the moon.
Step||ne.
|||||| Ladies.||
|||| I couldn't find your coats,
but I di||||nd... tequila.
(squealing)||
Wait, wait, wait, a remote control fireplace?
We don't ha|| a remote control fireplace.
Right, that's my apartment.
|| The dressing gown's mine, too.
Damn, this should be me.
Anyway, continuing...
(music playing)
|||| Whew! (moans)
||I am so exha||ted.
So exhausted.
Wait, why would I want to tire them out?
|| That's your excuse to unleash pretext
for physical contact #1.
Oh, you give the mo|| a||zing foot massage.
|||||| That's 'cause I used to practice
all the time on my grandmother.
|||| Why in God's name would I say ||at?
|| It's endearing. You're a caregiver.
||||||Never take||amily values ||out of the equation.
|||||| Step thre(sighs)
Te|| what's wrong?
I was just thinking about this documentary I saw once
|||||| about something called a super volcano.
|||| Okay, what the hell?
Wait for it.
|| It can happen at any time.
|| And obliterate ||||all life on Earth,
which is why I live by thresimple words.
|||||| ||n't postpone joy.
|||||| Oh, my God.
|||| That's so true.
|||| Yeah.
|||| The mortality angle.
|| That's actu||ly pretty good.
|| I can do this. Yes, you can.
|| Yeah. I can't believe I'm going to say this,
|||| but I'm ||tually moved.
All right. it in, guys.||||||||
I'll see you on the other side.
|||||||||||||||||| (giggling)
|||||||||||| (giggling)
|||||||||| So what happened next?||Did you do
|| It doesn't seem right to talk about it.
What? No! Tell me.
Don't tell m|| because you don't have to
because you didn't do it.
You didn't do it. You did it.
You did it, didn't you?
Did you?
You didn't do it.
|| Yes, you did. You did.
No, you didn't.
|| Tell me!
Some stories you tell, ||me stories you don't.
That's because you didn't do it.
||He didn't do it.
You did it. u did it, didn't you?
You did it. Tell me, did||ou?
|||| Ted, belt. Did you?
Did you || didn't you?
Did?
Tell me,||lease. For the love...
Do you||now if he did or didn't?
Oh, hey, um, Hmm?
would you go in there and ||e if my date's okay?
|| No problem.
|||| Thank you.
|||||| No, nobody's in there, but the window's actually open.
|||||| I guess I shouldn't be so surprised.||
I mean, she wa||acting weird ||l night, right?
Yeah, you know... (laughs)
|||||| ||why don't I buy you a drink?
|| Okay.
|| Did I overhear that you're a surgeon?
Guilty as charged.||
|| ||(chuckles)
Oh, you're so funny.
|| I'm here!
||||I'm fine!
|| My head is bleeding.
|| Going down again.
www.tvsubtitles.net