Narrator: In December of 2010,
my friends and I decided
to go see It's a Wonderful Life
on the big screen.
It seemed like
something we all needed.
After all, it had been
a crazy couple of days.
It all started...
With a pregnancy test.
This is taking forever.
Are you sure you did it right?
Is there a wrong way
to pee on a stick?
Hey, can I ask you a question
that's plagued me for years?
Can girls aim?
Um, can boys aim?
'Cause it seems to me
like I'm taking a mop
to that bathroom floor
every two days.
Okay, you're the one who
put the Far Side calendar
up over the toilet.
You know I laugh
with my whole body.
(Gasps)
It's been two minutes.
(Both exhale)
Both:
One, two, three.
It's positive. It's positive?
It's positive?
It's positive.
It's positive!
Whoa!
(Screaming)
I'm pregnant.
What?!
I've never seen that
woman before in my life!
Sorry. Force of habit.
Congratulations!
To Lily and Marshall.
Well, thank you.
I mean, we've never been happier.
Mm.
Can't imagine anything
bringing me down right now.
You're not pregnant.
Well, that did it.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Narrator: Kids, this is the
story of the 36 hours
we all thought
Lily was pregnant,
and how it caused each of us
to reexamine our own lives.
Because while
this was happening...
Are you sure you did it right?
...I was on the phone
with Punchy,
my best friend
from high school,
who had recently asked me
to be his best man.
Hey, Punchy, I've given this
some serious thought.
I think I know
how we can crush these
floral arrangements.
Ah, here it comes.
Hit me up, Schmos!
Peonies, lavender blossoms
with a halo of baby's breath
for an ambiance
of springtime rejuvenation.
(High-pitched):
¶ Crushed it! ¶
That's exactly
the accent of whimsy
this celebration of love needs!
It's gonna be a magical day.
I know what you're thinking.
I wish I was a dude.
I do wish you were a dude.
Because if I was a dude, I could
have Ted Mosby as my best man.
No, and here's why.
Ted, the best man's job
is not to crush
the floral arrangements.
It's to get the groom
down the aisle,
because, no matter who
he is, he will freak out.
And I just don't think
you have what it takes
to get that get that soldier
to pick up his rifle
and charge up the hill.
Uh, are you forgetting
I've done this before?
I was Marshall's best man.
And how did that go again?
(Both yelling)
Oh for one.
Oh, come on.
That wasn't my fault.
And need I remind you,
I gave a beautiful toast.
Ted.
(Both yelling)
Oh, do you take one
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
Oh, God, I'm freaking out.
Why did I chose Ted
to be my best man?
Uh, yeah. It's hard
to take criticism
from someone who just recorded
seven episodes
of Million Dollar Heads
or Tails.
Narrator: Kids,
Million Dollar Heads or Tails
was an extremely popular show
with an extremely
simple premise.
All right,
your practice flip came up
tails...
But our Vegas oddsmaker
tells us
that the next toss
is still just 50-50.
And so, Jordan,
for one million dollars...
...Heads... or tails?
(Audience shouting suggestions)
What was the year
of the coin again?
Why this sudden obsession
with Heads or Tails?
Well, it turns out
that Heads or Tails
has a job opening.
(Audience shouting suggestions)
Ta... heads.
Marni, flip that coin.
Ooh! Damn!
(Audience groaning)
So now, because
of that incident,
Heads or Tails is looking
for a new
currency rotation specialist.
You mean coin flip bimbo?
They're not bimbos!
You auditioned, didn't you?
And you're Canadian?!
Mm.
Robin, aside from that coin,
this is the other thing
that's flipping right now.
What is my lid?
For you.
You're the new coin flip bimbo?
Currency rotation specialist.
Robin, you better check yourself
before you trebek yourself.
You're a journalist!
What is the matter with you?
Well, it's a national audience!
I get to wear shiny dresses!
Robin,
have you forgotten about
your New Year's resolution?
I am never drinking again.
No, before that.
(Slurring): I am gonna finish
this whole bottle tonight.
Before that, too.
I moved here
to work for a big-time
cable news channel
like World Wide News.
Mm-hmm.
Well,
by this time next year,
I will be wearing
a World Wide News
I.D. badge around my neck.
And to show you
that I'm serious,
this is my first and
only drink of the night.
Okay.
Okay?
Oh, damn, that's smooth.
I thought you finally got that
interview at World Wide News.
Well, I did, but they only
offered me a boring,
low-paid,
off-camera research job.
Which could be a stepping stone
to bigger things in your career.
Well, so could Heads or Tails.
(Snorts)
The first currency
rotation specialist went on
to be a semi-finalist
on The Bachelor, and then,
she lost, like, a hundred pounds
on The Biggest Loser,
and now she's totally winning
Celebrity Rehab.
Narrator: It seemed like there was
no changing Robin's mind.
But what we didn't know,
in that moment,
was that our world was about
to be turned upside down.
I'm pregnant.
What?!
Now, kids, when your friends
have great news,
you're happy for them...
For, like, a millisecond.
And then you start thinking
about yourself.
Robin:
Oh, my God!
They're really having a baby.
What am I doing with my life?
Starting Monday,
I'm a currency rotation spe...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm a coin flip bimbo,
and I'm still single.
Okay, let's not go there,
Scherbatsky.
That's a whole other thing.
I've got to take
that World Wide News job.
Narrator: And so, the next night, we
had two things to celebrate.
Well, you are looking at the new
associate researcher
at World Wide News.
(Gasps) Oh, my gosh.
That's amazing news.
What changed your mind?
Marshall and Lily.
I just realized that
I am about to have a little
niece who looks up to me.
And I don't want to be
sad aunt Robin,
the aging coin flip bimbo
who gives her the creeps.
I want to be cool aunt Robin,
the respected journalist...
(Quietly):
Who gives her beer.
What?
What? Oh.
I have never seen you guys
looking so at peace.
(Both sigh)
To Lily and Marshall.
Well, thank you.
I mean, we've never
been happier.
Narrator:
So the next day Robin called
Heads or Tails
to respectfully decline.
Hi, Mr. Trebek.
This is Robin Scherbatsky.
Narrator:
But at that moment...
You're not pregnant.
(Both gasp)
As honored as I am
by the offer, um...
(Phone chirps)
Robin:
Oh, my God.
They're not having a baby.
What am I getting
all up in my head about?
That research job sounds hard.
And I'm pretty.
I'm really, really pretty.
You are looking
at the new coin flip bimbo.
(Imitates fireworks popping)
You took the heads or tails job?
Yeah.
What about World Wide News,
your I.D. badge?
You made a New Year's
resolution.
Okay, I also said I would never
make out with a garbage man.
Life is what happens when
you're busy making other plans.
What's with
the gingerbread house?
We're seeing a Christmas movie.
It's a Christmas-themed
movie snack.
Let's hope Santa brings you
a girlfriend this year, Teddy.
(Mutters mockingly)
Where the hell is Barney?
Narrator:
Where was Barney?
Let's back up again.
You see,
while this was going on...
It's positive.
It's positive?!
...This was happening.
And now she's totally winning
Celebrity Rehab.
Hey, guys.
A yuletide riddle.
What is my second favorite word
that begins with b-o-n?
Bon Jovi?
Yeah.
What is my third favorite word
that begins with b-o-n?
(Imitates buzzer)
Bonus.
As in, my end-of-the-year
bonus check.
(Laughing)
My God, Barney!
I work for GNB, too.
All I got was $15 gift card
to Costa Coffee.
And you earned it, buddy.
Check out what I'm
gonna buy for myself.
The dibiase.
See those pinstripes?
Diamonds.
It is the uppest
a person could ever suit.
Uh, has it ever occurred to you
to give some of this to charity?
Charity? You're seriously
talking to me about charity?
Dude, I am Mr. Charity.
I frequently sleep with sixes,
chubsters, over-thirties...
I am the bill and Melinda gates
of the sympathy bang.
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Hey.
Big announcement.
Let me guess.
You got a huge bonus check, too.
No, just a $30 gift card
to Costa Coffee.
Thirty?!
I'm pregnant.
What?!
What?! I've never seen that
woman before in my life!
Sorry, force of habit.
Congratulations!
Huh. Marshall and Lily are
doing something meaningful.
And it's making me
less happy about this bonus.
And I'm still single.
At least I got
that going for me.
So why do I still feel outside
of awesome looking in?
What am I doing with my life?
We've never been happier.
I can't imagine bringing
me down right now.
Oh, Marshall, you only think
you're happy.
Just wait, because tonight,
(imitating Oprah):
is Barney's Favorite Things!
(All cheering)
That was the reaction
Barney expected.
This was the one he got.
Huh?
I don't know what that is.
Barney's Favorite Things!
I'm gonna give you all a bunch
of free stuff... like Oprah.
Just get excited, okay?
The next hour got pretty weird.
Velour track suits!
Velour is so comfortable.
They're so soft.
Remote control helicopters!
(All cheer)
Condoms!
And last but not least...
There is
a fleet of limos outside
waiting to take us to...
A strip club!
(Applause, cheering)
You get a lap dance!
You're gonna give me
a lap dance!
Everybody gets a lap dance!
That was amazing!
It was like a diamond suit
for my soul.
I gotta keep going.
I gotta do more.
No. No! I cannot go back
to that strip club.
I seen some things.
I'm not going back either.
I'm taking the rest of my bonus
to God's strip club.
Narrator:
The next day, he paid a visit
to the most
charitable man he knew,
his half-brother's father,
Sam Gibbs,
a minister at a church
out on Long Island.
Sam.
Uh, father.
I-I don't mean father father.
Unless...
What's up, Barney?
I'm thinking about
giving some money to charity.
Is that the name of the stripper
you've been e-mailing me about?
You got to take me off
that list, Barney.
No, I don't mean that charity.
That charity is doing peachy.
You'll see pics of the two of
them in next week's e-mail.
What up!
Barney,
I'm a minister.
Unsubscribe.
I-I recently
started giving,
and it felt surprisingly good.
I want to do more.
Well, now you're talking.
We have this program
that helps those in need
get back on their feet.
We give them food,
a place to live,
clothes for job interviews.
Well, I would love to help
by writing a check
for... one, zero, zero, zero...
You're not pregnant.
(Both gasp)
...Zero...
(Cell phone chimes)
Woops. Hold on a second.
Wait. They're
not doing
something meaningful
with their lives.
Well, this changes everything.
Oh, no, I've already
written four zeroes.
(Gasps)
Thank you, decimal point.
One hundred dollars.
That's great!
Thank you, Barney!
Diamond suited up.
Hey, Ted, can you
spot me for the movie?
I don't like to carry
a lot of cash on me.
What happened
to giving the money away?
Yeah, that was back when
Lily was pregnant.
Now she's not.
Ergo, a suit is born.
(Chuckles)
Dude, what's up with
the gingerbread house?
You look ridiculous!
It's a Christmas-themed
movie snack!
Ah, I know that move.
You cut a hole in the floor,
she reaches into the
living room, finds the tree...
¶ O holy night. ¶
Nice.
Where the hell
are Marshall and Lily?
Narrator:
Let's back up one last time.
I'm pregnant.
What?!
I've never seen that
woman before in my life!
Sorry, force of habit.
Congratulations!
This is great.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy,
my heart's pounding.
And I'm sweating.
And I can't breathe.
This is what happiness
feels like, right?
Oh, crap.
Lily's having a baby
and I'm having a panic attack.
I hope she can't tell
what I'm thinking right now.
I can.
And I'm freaking out, too!
There's an alien
growing in my stomach
that's gonna explode
out of my vagina!
Do you think the others
can tell we're freaking out?
What am I doing with my life?
What am I doing
with my life?
I should get a Christmas-themed
movie snack for tomorrow night.
They're totally onto us.
What do we do?
Just keep smiling, maybe wave.
No, don't wave!
That makes no sense!
I'm committed.
I'm riding this wave
straight to hell.
Let's leave, then the waving
will make sense.
Narrator: So Marshall and Lily
headed home.
Marshall:
Lily, we have to relax.
There's no need to panic.
True, there's a lot to do,
but we've got nine months
to prepare.
So I say that we just
make a list of everything
that needs to get done
before the baby arrives
and do everything
on that list tonight!
Let's do it!
(Yelling)
Uh-huh, got it.
Okay, that seems easy.
Nursery's painted!
Blue? What if it's a girl?
Damn it!
¶ ¶
Oh, God, it's 8:00!
We're supposed to meet the
gang at the bar to celebrate.
Oh, God. Okay, listen.
When we meet them,
we have to keep it together.
Can you keep it together?!
No, I can't keep it together!
Robin: I have never seen you
guys looking so at peace.
(Both sigh)
To Lily and Marshall.
Lily and Marshall.
Well, thank you.
I mean,
we've never been happier.
(Rock music playing)
This is a nightmare!
We've done everything wrong!
(Screams)
The iPod was on shuffle!
(Rock music stops)
The Jerky Boys!
Our baby heard the Jerky Boys!
You know what,
the Jerky Boys are funny.
The Jerky Boys aren't funny,
they are awful.
You know what, fine,
if you don't think
the Jerky Boys are funny,
then I'm not sure
that I can raise a child
with you, liver lips.
(Gasps)
Marshall, I don't like this.
I know. Okay?
I don't like it either.
It's like I have a hot, burning
ball of stress in my chest,
and nothing
will make it go away!
You're not pregnant.
Well, that did it.
I know this probably comes
as quite a disappointment.
Yeah.
Huge bummer.
So disappointing.
Hey.
Are you guys okay?
Huh?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't we be?
Oh, the baby thing.
Oh, yeah, whatever.
Oh, Christmas-themed
movie snack. Nice.
(Chuckles) Don't reach
into the living room!
(Both laugh)
Wow, I-I thought you guys
would be devastated.
Oh.
You know, we're actually
kind of relieved.
We were freaking out for about
a day and a half there.
Yeah, this whole thing
got us thinking.
Maybe we're not ready
for kids yet after all.
Yeah, we were thinking
maybe we would just get a dog.
Get a puppy!
Can you imagine...
That would be the cutest thing!
(Yelling)
No!
Oh. Our movie snack.
Are you kidding me?!
All you ever talk about
is having kids!
And now you have
one little freak-out
and you want to get
a dog instead?!
No. Unacceptable!
You're gonna turn around,
you're gonna go home, get naked,
lie together as man and wife
until Lily is great with child.
Right now!
I'm serious! Go, go, go!
(Singsongy): Marshall and
Lily got in trouble.
And you!
Ooh.
Barney, you look real stupid
in that suit.
You're gonna go get your money
back and give it to charity.
And I don't mean that stripper
you keep e-mailing us about,
even though we beg you
to take us off that list.
I can't give this suit back.
Ted, I glow in the dark.
I finally glow in the dark!
Criminals of New York! Attention!
This man is wearing a
diamond-covered suit!
You could retire
on the pants alone!
Merry Christmas!
(Stuttering)
So, if I get a large popcorn,
you want to go split-skees or...
And you...
You did not move
to the greatest city on earth
to become a coin-flipping bimbo.
So here's how it's gonna work:
Heads, you take the job
at World Wide News;
Tails, you take
the job at World Wide News.
Ow!
(Coin clinks)
Hey, looks like
somebody got a new gig!
Fine, I'll call them tomorrow.
I'll call them right now.
(Annoyed muttering)
(Cell phone ringing)
Hello.
Ted, I can't get married!
Yes, you can! You love her!
You're right, I do! Thanks, Ted!
One for It's a Wonderful Life,
please.
Thank you.
Hi.
We're idiots.
This kid doesn't stand a chance.
We're ready for this.
Wow.
That's a lot of zeroes.
Y-you sure you're not
missing a decimal point?
Nope.
And that's the tour.
Uh, staff meeting's at noon,
you'll meet everyone there,
but first you need
to head down to security.
You need to get
your picture taken.
For your I.D. badge.
Oh.
You sure?
Positive.
And there's more.
Do you still do that thing
where you give
people in need
clothes for job interviews?
Yeah. Why?
Bring 'em in, boys!
(Chuckles)
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, son.
Son?!
It's just an expression.
I'm still not your dad.
Congratulations.
You know, that was
really cool what you did.
When we all needed it,
you got us back
on the right path.
It's what I do.
Hey, Ted, if I, um,
if I ever get married
and you're not
the guy I'm marrying...
Big mistake, but go on.
...I could really use
someone like you.
You know, in case I freak out.
When I freak out.
You interested?
Are you asking what I
think you're asking?
Ted, will you be my best man?
Scherbatsky...
I'm gonna crush it.
Hi, there.
We've had a lot of fun tonight,
but on a more serious note,
this is the time of year
when we remember
the importance of giving.
And there's no greater gift
than the gift of booty.
So, this holiday season,
why not bang someone in need?
I'm Barney Stinson,
and that's...
One to grow on.
Um, no.
Hi, there. You know, we've
had a lot of fun tonight...
www.tvsubtitles.net