NARRATOR: Kids, after Uncle
Marshall lost his father,
he decided to stay home a while
to take care of his mother.
(phone ringing)
But the longer he stayed there,
the more it was like
he had never left Minnesota.
Eriksen residence,
Marshall speaking.
(laughs)
Oh, that is too cute.
Say it again.
No.
It's called manners, jerk.
Now, what's-what's going on
in New York?
Give me something.
There is one thing
that's been going on.
Uh, it's about Ted... and Zoey.
to save an old building
from being torn down
and replaced by a new building
that I'd been hired to design.
And yet somehow, despite this,
we had all managed
to become friends.
Which brings us to the night
Aunt Robin decided
to cook dinner.
I thought the oven was Celsius.
It's okay.
We got hot dogs.
Yeah, and it's not like
you can screw up a hot dog.
Oh, God.
This is so good.
I'm gonna finish it
in the bathroom.
Could someone pass the ketchup?
I hope I can pass this hot dog.
Oh.
(glass shatters)
Oops. Well, looks
like someone's
going out in the cold
to get more ketchup.
Oh, come on, man,
I brought the wine.
Which is all gone.
Oops.
(sighs)
All right, I tell you what--
you get this one bottle,
I'll get the next three.
Hmm, tell you what-- no dice.
I'll get
the next hundred.
You're not getting out of this.
You want to go on a date
with my hot cousin?
I'll get the ketchup.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
Robin, I just want you to know,
it's either this story you're
telling me or another game
of Clue against myself,
so make it good.
Oh, it's good.
You see, after that night,
none of us heard from Zoey
for a while.
Finally, Ted called her up.
Hello.
So are we ever gonna
see you again?
Because, if I recall correctly,
you owe me a date
with your hot cousin.
You still want to do that?
Yes. And we miss you.
But the cousin thing mostly.
Let's get that going.
Don't worry,
Ted, she's cute.
(Barney coughing)
"Cute" means "fat""
She's not fat.
(coughing):
"Not fat" means "ugly""
Oh, here she is.
(coughing): I take
back everything I said.
That girl is
extremely attractive.
Hey, Zoey.
Hey.
Ted, this is
my cousin...
NARRATOR:
Kids, to be honest,
I don't quite remember
this girl's name.
None of us do,
because as this story
has been told and retold,
we've always just referred
to her as...
Honey.
Hi, Honey, I'm Ted.
And here's why.
She is a lovely person--
warm, intelligent,
just kind of gullible.
It's like, every word
out of her mouth
makes you want to be like,
"Oh, honey."
Interesting.
Show your work.
My apartment building
is so safe.
My landlord-- he even installed
a security camera in my shower.
Oh, honey.
Maybe I should feel weird
about giving a stranger
my Social Security number,
but the guy's a Nigerian prince.
Oh, honey.
I just had
a great TV audition.
Behind the KFC where
the executive producer works
on the weekends.
Oh, honey.
Long story short,
I'm going to be on Lost.
Oh, honey.
I know.
You just want to wrap her up
in a blanket
and give her a cup of tea.
She's, like, this
little lost lamb
who needs to be protected
from the wolves.
Speaking of whom...
Yeah, I always get those
e- mails from Michelle Obama
and sometimes
Obama himself.
Oh, honey.
ROBIN:
So the night went on,
and eventually
everyone went home,
except for Ted and Honey.
Wow, an architect.
How fascinating.
Why do they call
'em coasters?
And Barney.
Okay, time to go home.
Ted, a word.
God, I hate these situations.
What are we gonna do about this?
What are you talking about?
Come on, Ted, it's obvious.
Honey's vibing on me.
What?
It's called body language.
Remember when she was
touching your arm
and leaning in real close?
Mm-hmm.
Well, while that was happening,
the straw in her drink
was pointed right at me.
I mean...
that's as clear
as a signal gets,
so...
I'm so sorry, man.
You're right.
She's all yours, buddy.
I'd say
hump her brains out,
but someone obviously
already has.
ROBIN:
Good for you.
Ted Mosby does not
take advantage
of poor,
helpless honeys.
Yeah, actually,
there's another reason
that I didn't go home
with her.
Hmm?
He's gay!
Mom, hang up!
I'm sorry.
(scoffs)
Go on.
Yeah, actually,
there's another reason
that I didn't go home
with her.
Hmm?
I'm in love with Zoey.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Mom!
Sorry.
Ted's in love with Zoey?
But, but she's married.
That boy needs an intervention.
Funny you should say that.
Does anyone know
why we're here?
LILY: Yeah, who called
this intervention?
I did. It's for me.
This is
about the coffee breath.
Finally. Hmm, no,
it's the shoulder hair.
BARNEY:
Guys, just let
the man explain
how it's all
about his wearing
a lady's watch.
It's because
I'm in love with Zoey,
and she's married,
so it needs to stop.
And... intervene.
Are you sure
it's love?
(sighs)
Remember the ketchup bottle?
She wasn't the one
who dropped it.
When she reached for it,
our fingers touched, and...
(glass shatters)
I knew, right in that moment,
this isn't friendship.
This is love.
Wuss.
Marcus!
This is a private conversation!
So what'd the wuss do next?
This is love.
And this was
my grandmother's watch.
Anyway, now I have only one
course of action in front of me:
I have to end
my friendship with Zoey.
Isn't that
a little harsh?
Harsh?
Robin, a single guy
and a married woman
cannot be friends
if one's in love with the other.
Yeah, but Zoey is
friends with us now, too.
It's not like Ted can
just ghost out on her.
She'll always be around.
Then what am I
supposed to do?
Okay, just shut it down.
Okay, just ignore
your feelings.
If-If she asks you
for ketchup,
tell her to get it
her own damn self.
Look, I like Zoey.
Without her,
my dinner party wouldn't
have been such a success.
So those feelings
of yours--
shut 'em down.
Fine.
I'll shut 'em down.
And seriously,
mouthwash after coffee.
(phone line beeps)
Oh, um, that's my other line.
It's not a number I recognize.
So don't answer it.
(line beeps)
Yeah.
(Minnesotan accent):
Oh, my God,
you are so Minnesota.
You can't not answer the phone
because it would be rude.
(line beeps)
Well, it would be.
Good-bye.
Eriksen residence,
Marshall speaking.
Hey, Marshall.
Barney.
W- What number is this?
I'm up on burners, playa.
Too many crazies had
my old number,
so now I'm all about
disposable cell phones.
I'll use one for a while,
have my fun,
then dump it and get a new one.
And then I'll do the same
with my phone.
Hey, uh, so Robin told me about
this whole Ted and Zoey thing.
Dude, she doesn't know
how to tell a story.
I'll tell you that story.
Hey, Zoey.
Hey.
Ted, this is
my cousin...
Honey.
MARSHALL:
Uh...
Robin's version was...
That is exactly how it happened.
So Ted did his best
to impress her,
but as per yoozh,
he bored the pants
very much on her.
Blah, blah, blah,
I'm an architect.
I don't wear suits.
Blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
Wow, an architect.
How fascinating.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Rambling architecture anecdote.
Blah, blah,
something about a bridge.
Blah, blah, blah...
(whispers):
Straw.
Coaster.
Okay, time to go home.
Anyway, I get Honey
back to her place.
Who's your daddy?
Okay, can we skip
this part, please?
Sure, I'll just summarize it.
(imitating squeaky bedsprings)
(squeaking accelerates)
(squeaking slows)
Okay, that's been
going on a while.
Only way I know how.
Any-who, next day,
I'm going into work.
I run into Zoey.
Hey, Zoey.
That cousin of yours--
Honey-- yowsa!
I must say, your family
tree has got a couple
of pretty big coconuts.
Thanks.
Yeah, we had a great
time last night.
And then just hand stuff
in the morning, so...
Wait, she didn't go home
with Ted?
Nope, he let me have her.
I have to say, it was
pretty noble of him.
He fell on his sword so that
she could fall on mine.
I won't bore you with the
details, but to summarize...
(imitating squeaky bedsprings)
She hugged me.
What was that all about?
Zoey's in love with Ted.
Marcus!
Wait, hear me out, Marshall.
Zoey's in love with Ted,
but she's married,
so she tried to push him away
by setting him up
with her cousin instead.
But seeing Ted and Honey
hit it off was
more than her gentle heart
could bear,
so Zoey left early,
pricked by love's fickle thorn.
But then, the next morning,
upon learning
that Ted had not tasted
of Honey's sweet nectar,
her joy burst forth like
a blossoming flower in spring.
Wow.
Zoey's in love with Ted.
Oh, Marshall, I stopped by that
new doughnut shop Hertz Donuts.
Would you like a Hertz Donut?
Sure.
Hey, where's the...?
No! Aah!
Hurts, don't it?
I can't believe
you fell for that, bro.
So Ted's in love with Zoey
and Zoey's in love with Ted?
Well, that-that's not
going to work.
I got to call Ted.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Listen, Ted, um,
I got to tell you
something about Zoey.
Yeah, yeah. I need to tell you
something about Zoey, too.
Hey. I was in the neighborhood
and I thought I'd take you up
on that beer
you're about to offer me.
Can I get you a beer?
Oh, Ted, I'm so busy.
But I guess I got time for one.
Lead the way.
(laughing):
Oh, my God.
What?!
Fridge full of ketchup? How?
How, I ask you?
(laughs)
What?
Listen, Zoey, I, um...
I need to tell you something.
Um...
Marshall, I'm going to Byerly's.
You want anything?
Mom! Get off the phone!
Could you get
some more Bugles, please?
Of course, dear.
Marcus, hang up!
Both of you, hang up!
And we need ice cream.
Go on.
I, uh... I can't be
friends with you anymore.
And this may
seem strange, but...
you can't ask me why.
Wow.
Okay.
And that was it.
No more Zoey.
(line beeps)
Oh. Hey, buddy, that's Lily.
I should take that.
But, uh,
you're a good guy, Ted.
Hey, baby.
We hate Ted now.
Get on board
or the sexting stops.
Ted's a son of a bitch!
(cell phone chirps)
Oh, nice.
But, hey, um, baby,
go easy on Ted, okay?
He just, he just
ended things with Zoey.
Oh, I know.
But did he tell you
the whole story?
I, uh, I can't be friends
with you anymore.
And you can't ask me why.
Why?
Lily hates you.
You hate me?
That's crazy.
I don't hate you.
Well, I know that's not true,
Lily. Ted told me everything.
He... Oh, really?
And-And what did Ted say,
exactly?
Lily hates you.
She hates you so much
it's hard to be around you.
So we can't be friends.
Oh, he... Oh, yeah.
Yeah, okay, well,
I- I guess there's no use
hiding it anymore.
I- I hate you.
Bitch.
I can't believe it.
I really thought
you and I were friends.
Lord knows I could
use a friend right now.
I've been going through
some pretty difficult stuff.
Difficult stuff?
What difficult stuff?
I don't know.
Well, you did
the right thing, baby.
Not entirely.
Zoey, wait!
I don't hate you!
We just
can't be friends
anymore because...
Robin hates you.
(line beeps)
And that's Robin
on the other line.
Oh, well,
I'll let you take that.
Love you, baby!
Eriksen residence,
Marshall speaking.
Listen, Robin. I know.
I apologize for my wife.
She never should have...
Yeah, I told Zoey you hate her.
Me?
You dragged me into this?!
You just went through a tragedy.
It's not like she's
gonna call you up and...
(line beeps)
Oh, God, that's my other line.
Oh, God, it's a 917 number,
and I don't recognize it!
I think it's Zoey!
Just don't answer it.
I can't not answer.
It's impolite.
Marshall, you can beat this.
I can't turn my back
on politeness.
You don't have to answer.
You can just let it ring.
Good manners are what
separate us from those "elbows
on the table" Wisconsinites.
You can do this.
I believe in you.
Don't do it, Marshall!
I'm sorry, Robin!
Eriksen residence.
Marshall speaking.
Hi. I spent the night
with your friend Barney
and he accidentally
left his phone
in my apartment, in the garbage.
But I've been
going through
all of his contacts
because I'm sure he wants
to get in touch with me.
After all,
he told me, uh...
I was his first.
Oh, honey.
Oh! Honey!
Zoey's cousin.
Hi.
Listen, um, about Barney...
Oh, yeah.
He's such a sweet guy.
Who's your daddy?
(giggles):
Oh...
Who's your daddy?
(sobbing):
I don't know.
I guess he recently decided
to get in touch with his dad.
His mom gave him
the guy's address.
So I wrote him a letter.
And I poured
my heart out.
And I gave him my number
and I told him to call me.
And he still
hasn't called me.
Oh, honey.
I mean,
I shouldn't be surprised.
Clearly, he wants
nothing to do with me.
Oh, honey.
I mean,
why else would
he let 30 years go by?
He's ashamed
to have me as a son.
Oh, honey,
he's not ashamed of you.
He's ashamed of himself.
I mean, look at you.
You're do so great without him.
I mean, you have an airline
and three Nobel Prizes,
and you play for the Yankees.
Four. Four Nobel Prizes.
Four. See?
That is impressive.
I mean, how many does he have?
Only three.
Well, there you go.
Hey, uh, listen, Honey,
while I've got you,
do you have any idea
what kind of difficult stuff
Zoey's been going through?
Oh, I can't tell you about that.
The only people
that are allowed to know
are me, Zoey and her therapist.
I am her therapist.
Oh! Well, in that case...
Uh, okay, listen, I think we've
made great progress for today.
I got to go. Bye.
Mom! Marcus!
(knocking at door)
What's this really about?
I told you.
Lily hates you.
I think you hate me.
I think you have
some big problem with me,
and you're too chicken
to come out and say it.
All right.
Yes.
I... hate you.
Great.
See?
Was that so hard?
Zoey.
Can you at least tell me why?
Because I'm racking
my brain here,
and I thought...
(sighs)
I just want to know why.
So we got Ted and Zoey.
Ted is in love with Zoey.
Zoey has no idea.
Then Zoey's cousin Honey
went home with Barney,
and Zoey was happy about it.
Which tells us what?
Zoey's in love with...
Zoey's in love with Ted
and Ted doesn't know.
So Ted and Zoey--
they're in love with each other,
which would be fine
if Zoey wasn't
married to Colonel Mustard.
I mean, The Captain.
Except now,
as Honey informs me...
And we miss you.
But the cousin thing mostly.
Let's get that going.
Fine, I will, uh,
make it happen.
Good-bye.
Okay. Well...
I guess I'll take it.
Zoey and The Captain
are getting divorced.
Which means...?
So help me, Marshall,
if you don't call those two
crazy, mixed-up kids, I will.
Give me that phone.
Why do I hate you?
Are you kidding?
Uh, you're actively trying
to prevent me
from realizing a lifelong dream.
So there's that.
Plus, you're stubborn
and-and-and argumentative.
And what kind of name
is Zoey, huh?
What is that, short for Zoseph?
(cell phone ringing)
Go on, get it.
I'll have more in a second.
Hello.
Oh, hey, Marshall.
Yes, I am.
He is?
Bye.
Why was Marshall calling?
Don't worry about it.
Go on.
You talk during movies.
You-You-You
sneeze with your whole body.
Uh, to my knowledge,
you do not speak Portuguese.
Well, actually...
(speaking Portuguese)
You're a show-off.
(cell phone ringing)
You better take that.
Uh, hey, Marshall,
can I call you back?
I'm out in the hallway with...
She is?
Marshall, I got to go.
They're kissing.
They're kissing?!
Yeah! (screams)
They're kissing!
They're kissing, Mom!
www.tvsubtitles.net