My first kiss with Zoey was amazing,
and complicated.
Look...
I know you're going
through a lot right now.
Getting divorced, being single,
figuring out
who you are on your own.
Someone knows how to set a mood.
I just mean...
I'm okay taking this slow.
I wanna do this right.
My friends, as usual,
were completely supportive.
You're doing this all wrong!
Ted, there are couples
in my kindergarten class
who have moved faster than you two.
Granted, their home lives
are not great.
I'm trying. I keep suggesting
these big, romantic dates,
and she keeps putting on the brakes.
Like tonight, she wants me to just
come over and bake cookies.
Translation: booty-call.
Total booty-call.
Private Booty, reporting for duty.
That's crazy.
She wants to bake.
Guys booty-call girls after 2:00 am
with a drunkenly slurred,
"What ya doing?"
But when a lady booty-calls a guy,
she invents a respectable excuse
to mask the fact that she wants
to get stuck real good.
It's called class, Ted.
Wait. That...
You think that's what she means
by "baking cookies"?
Are you kidding?
You're in the kitchen,
it's getting hot,
you start licking stuff
off each others' fingers.
Before you know it,
she's bent over the marble island,
and you're spanking her
with a rubber spatula.
And she's screaming,
"Stop, Marshall, stop,"
but that's just code for "harder!"
Marshall's been in Minnesota
a while, huh?
So long!
And now he's staying even longer.
His mom has been having
a really hard time since the funeral.
He's waiting on her hand and foot.
But it's Valentine's Day.
It's not gonna be the same
without the two of us
watching Predator together.
I should explain.
On their very first Valentine's Day,
Marshall and Lily set out
to watch Sleepless in Seattle.
You know, I saw this in
the theater, like, five times,
but I never got to see it
with the right girl.
I'm so glad none of those girls
were right for you.
What girls?
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
Except Marshall's brothers
had taped over it with Predator.
And it became a tradition.
You sound really lonely.
I am.
Earlier today, I burst into tears...
Daddy's talking now.
Loneliness.
The looming specter
of Valentine's Day fast approaching.
The two key ingredients
to my favorite day of the year,
February 13:
Desperation Day.
- That's not a thing.
- It's a thing.
Much like Valentine's Day itself,
Desperation Day dates
back thousands of years.
Weddings were forbidden
under ancient Roman law,
so Saint Valentine
performed them in secret,
under threat of death.
- That's actually true.
- Wait, there's more.
This won't be.
And right by Saint Valentine's side
was his best bro,
Saint Desperatius,
there to pick off
insecure bridesmaids.
Check out that one.
Her body is a perfect X.
Player, play on.
High V.
Oh, Jupiter,
what are your plans for me?
15 and still unmarried.
And I thought Pompeii was smokin'.
Every woman wants a date
on Valentine's Day.
That neediness reaches its climax...
what up... on February 13.
A magical night
when a ten
has the self-esteem of a four
and the depraved
enthusiasm of a two.
Now, there's only one
thing you can't do.
Please say "widows."
Wherever you are,
or whoever you're under,
you must get home alone
by 11:59 pm.
Otherwise, you're on a
date on Valentine's Day.
Barney, Desperation Day
assumes that all single women
freak out about Valentine's Day.
Which we do not.
Case in point,
I will be spending February 13 with
some lovely single ladies from work...
- Trolls.
- ... who could care less
- about Valentine's Day.
- Lying trolls.
And we will be celebrating the fact
that we don't have to spend it
with some dippy guy carting around
roses and stuffed toys all night.
No offense, Ted.
And none was taken until just then.
Synchro:
MiniBen314 & Strex
Adaptation:
Dark_Chii, H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture: Titou
6x16 - Desperation Day (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
I decided to go to Minnesota
to see Marshall.
He shouldn't have to help his mom
through this rough time all by himself.
- You losing your mind, being alone?
- I'm getting weird!
See, it started off with me throwing
Marshall's jersey on my body pillow.
And, well,
things kind of spiraled from there.
I'm sorry I yelled like that before.
I call him "Marshpillow."
And he calls me...
Nothing because he's a pillow.
How was "baking cookies" last night?
That was a tough question.
You see...
Is that an overnight bag?
- You brought an overnight bag?
- You said I was gonna spend the night.
We said you were gonna have sex.
We didn't say, "Bring a carry-on."
So how did Zoey react?
She thought it was presumptuous
and asked me to leave.
- I didn't brought a ton of stuff.
- Were there slippers for the morning?
Not slippers, exactly.
They're called
British morning socks.
This is such a nice surprise.
Marshall will be so happy.
How are you holding up, Judy?
I'm doin' okay.
It gets a little lonely.
My friends suggested
a body pillow, but...
I'm not a lunatic.
I hate to be that guy,
but I'm pretty sure
it was Hot Pocket o'clock,
like, ten minutes ago.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to surprise you.
My gosh, that's so sweet.
I'm so glad you're here.
Before I forget, Mom, did you remember
to get more double-A batteries?
They're upstairs, sweetie. Right next
to your washed and folded clothes.
Great, okay. I don't want
my Game Boy to crap out.
I'm having the sickest
Dr. Mario run of my life.
I'll be right back.
I love you, Lily.
You're the best, Mom.
Anything for my baby bear.
Get him out of my house.
Take Marshall back
to New York with you.
Please, I am begging you.
I thought he was here helping you.
He was, at first.
But once he saw me starting
to do better, he kind of regressed.
He's been holed up in his room
for days at a time,
playing old video games.
I mean, he is having a pretty
sick Dr. Mario run, but...
- I'll talk to him.
- I wanna be there for him,
but it's like he's a teenager again.
I even walked in
on him abusing himself.
There he was, on the bed,
looking at old photos of his dad.
That's emotional self-abuse,
don't you think?
Listen, that was a dumb move
for me to just assume...
I overreacted. I mean,
I invited you over to
"bake cookies."
- We both knew what that meant.
- We totally did.
I just, you know...
I saw those slippers in your bag,
and suddenly everything
felt really serious. And...
ever since, I've been asking myself,
"Am I ready for this?"
And...
the answer is "yes."
- They're British morning socks.
- Don't get in your own way.
Marshall, your mom asked me
to carry this up.
She turned her ankle
on your Hot Wheels.
Is my track okay?
It's fine, but, Marshall,
I thought you were here
taking care of your mom.
It seems like
she's taking care of you.
My mom loves to feel needed.
Letting her take care of me
is how I'm taking care of her.
She's in a dark place, Lily.
She needs this.
You forgot my chocolate milk
with the swirly straw!
Comin' right up!
She needs this.
Tomorrow's Valentine's.
Don't you wanna be at home
on our couch,
cuddling up under a warm blanket,
watching the Predator
use his heat vision
to stalk helpless prey?
Well, baby,
we could watch Predator here.
My mom can go rent it for us
after she's done digging out the car.
- Your mom wants you out of here.
- What?
Anything else, sweetie?
Do you want me to leave?
Heavens to Bess, no!
Of course not!
- But, Judy, you said...
- If Marshall could stay here forever,
I would be the happiest
mom in Minnesota.
Get him out!
So Valentine's Day is tomorrow.
You know, there's
this new Italian restaurant
on 79th that's
supposed to be amazing.
I would be happier having
just a simple, home-cooked meal.
As long as it's with you.
Tomorrow night, my place.
I'm ready for this, Ted.
I am in it for the long haul.
I can't wait for our first
Valentine's Day as a couple.
The one we'll remember for years.
- Isn't that great?
- Yeah, if you say so.
What do you mean?
She just got out of a marriage, Ted.
That's heavy.
I'm kind of freaking out,
just listening to you.
My heart is pounding,
I'm hearing this weird clicking noise.
Well, it's romantic, right?
Zoey and I are getting serious
on Valentine's Day.
See, that just amps up
the pressure even more.
Boy, it's a good thing
that you're sure.
Who said I wasn't sure?
I'm glad we're
in a serious relationship.
Right away.
And if I screw this up,
I'm the devil,
because she's going through a divorce.
But I'm not gonna screw this up.
So stop freaking out.
Stop freaking out!
Kids, I'm not super proud
of what I did next.
I'm here to help Marshall.
Meanwhile, as Desperation Day
turned into Desperation Night...
God, these girls are so hungry
for male attention.
It is like being a hunter
and having the deer walk up,
tie itself to the hood of your car
and beg to get mounted.
This is Bev and Anna,
my coworkers and my friends.
Bev, Anna, this is Barney,
a high-functioning sociopath and my ex.
Enchanté.
That's French for
"What's with the purple?"
Well, tomorrow is Valentine's Day,
and everything is pink and red, so Bev
very thoughtfully
suggested that we wear purple
to show how little we care.
I use colors to express emotion.
Purple is for pride.
It was a stupid idea.
Bev, you look at me.
It's not a stupid idea.
Tonight, we are queens.
And we don't care about some stupid,
sexist, corporate holiday.
Please!
You might as well be dog-earing
a tear-stained bridal magazine
while wolfing down the box of chocolates
you had delivered to yourself at work
from your "fiancé"
who no one's ever met.
Gerard is real!
I thought you were gonna talk to
Marshall about coming back to New York.
Yeah, but, you know,
things move so fast in New York.
Why not hang out here until
at least after Valentine's Day?
Plus, we're helping Marshall's mom.
Mrs. Eriksen,
we're running low on SunnyD!
Is orange juice okay?
When your "fiancé" Gerard comes back
from fixing cleft palates in Peru,
maybe snatch a photo
of the two of you together,
and then I'll totally believe you.
Well, he's going to
Kenya after Peru, so...
Hey, guys, so sorry I'm late.
This is Barney.
You wanna see Anna
- beat him in an arm wrestle?
- My elbow slipped!
Marshall, I'm going home.
What?
I'm flying out tonight
before the big storm,
and I want you to come with me.
I can't right now,
'cause my mom needs me.
While I'm sure it's been really
helpful for her to have you here
playing Super Mario Kart
for 14 hours a day...
- You have Super Mario Kart?!
- Hell, yeah.
But your mom doesn't need you.
Your life in New York needs you.
It needs you really bad.
Baby, don't go.
Please come home soon.
- So, you were an Olympic gymnast?
- Silver medal.
Sorry. Gold's the only thing
that really counts.
That's what my dad said.
And she sticks the landing.
Why don't you start
stretching, and I'll...
be right back.
Sorry. Quick question.
Why aren't you wearing purple?
I told them I forgot, but the truth is,
I'm kind of protesting their protest.
- Can you keep a secret?
- Sure.
I love Valentine's Day.
My gosh! Me, too!
Is it getting crowded in here, 'cause
I think there are two peas in this pod?
- You're a gooey romantic, too?
- Guilty.
This is embarrassing,
but every year,
I buy flowers and a box of chocolates,
even if I'm not with someone.
Just in case, you know?
- We are pitiful.
- The worst.
Although there is
one difference between you and me.
What's that?
I'm not saying any of this
to get in your pants.
I miss my dad, Ted.
I miss him so much.
I know.
When I was a kid, we would spend
the summers in the Upper Peninsula.
And every year, we wouldn't get to the
cabin till the middle of the night.
So, it would be pitch black,
in the middle of the woods.
And I could never see anything
in front of the headlights,
but I always felt so safe
'cause my dad was driving.
He was like some sort of superhero
who could just see way out
into the darkness.
Now he's just gone.
And it's pitch black.
I can't see where I'm going.
I can't see anything.
All right.
I was playing you before.
But I was really doing you
a public service.
It's February 13th.
A day many are now calling
Desperation Day.
It's kind of a thing.
And you,
walking around,
saying you're a gooey romantic?
It comes across a bit desperate.
What's desperate
about knowing what you want?
Life is really short, Barney.
Who wants to spend
Valentine's Day alone,
distracting yourself from the fact
that nobody loves you
with some sad little activity?
Or you could be in the 47th Semi-Annual
Laser Tag Tournament
in Poughkeepsie.
I have no idea
what any of those words mean.
I'm all stretched out!
Here's the first thing
you need to know about laser tag.
Thanks a lot
for coming out here, man.
Are you sure it's okay with Zoey
that you're here for Valentine's Day?
Well, I mean,
technically, she doesn't know yet.
- What?
- Things with Zoey
are moving really fast,
and the divorce just makes everything
more complicated. I just...
I needed to take a step back.
You're not taking a step back.
You're running away.
And hiding out here
is not gonna solve anything.
You're just holed up in Minnesota
because you're too scared
to face reality...
We gotta go back to New York,
tonight.
We're snowed in.
Lily got the last flight.
So, we drive. It's time.
It's time to get back to real life.
It's time to grow up.
Can you make us
some PB and J's for the road?
Crusts cut off!
No, Ted. What are we...
We're men.
Leave the crusts on!
They forced their opponents to scatter,
picking them off, one by one,
in a swift and merciless slaughter.
That is how Boy Scout Troop 15
became the 2010 Tri-County Champions.
- Laser tag sounds brilliant!
- It is.
Plus, if you win,
you get free pizza!
- This is my teammate for tomorrow.
- Yeah, I agreed to that.
Where are Bev and Anna?
- So, we're taking off.
- What?
Those guys are gonna buy us
hot dogs at Grey's Papaya.
So that's it?
A couple of white Urkels
offer you sausages, and you're gone?
What about the sisterhood?
Solidarity?
The color purple?
But tomorrow's Valentine's Day.
I thought we didn't care about it.
You'll find someone, too.
You're a queen.
You've got so much to offer.
Maybe do something with that hair.
I'm telling you.
The power of Valentine's Day.
I'm Huey Lewis,
and you just heard the news.
I think I'm heading out, too.
What? No, don't go!
You wanna see a magic trick?
It's late, and I have a date
with my pillow.
I mean, not literally.
I'm not a lunatic.
Boy Scout Troop 15
doesn't stand a chance.
Speaking of the power
of Valentine's Day...
- What are you talking about?
- Come on.
It's past midnight.
Desperation Day has come and gone,
and you have neither gone nor come.
You know why?
You like Nora.
No, I don't. She's gross.
You like her.
You think she smells like rain.
Whatever you say.
Here's a secret.
I couldn't see
worth a damn, either, buddy.
I just kept driving forward,
hoping for the best.
Look out!
Gotcha.
And so we drove through the night, out
of Desperation Day and into Valentine's.
And there was no trace
of my little freak out, except...
Really? An overnight bag
for your own living room?
Looks like we got a matching set.
Well, that was kind of presumptuous.
Where are you?
Those Boy Scouts have grown a foot
since last year. They're terrifying!
Change of plans.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Robin told me to meet you guys here.
And that's how,
for the first time in his life,
Barney Stinson wound up on a date
on Valentine's Day.
You will be avenged.
Come on!
Kill me! I'm here! Kill me!
Baby!
You're back.
Happy Valentine's Day, Lily Pad.
We both knew
this would end eventually.
www.tvsubtitles.net