Kids, I bought the house we live in now
way back before I ever met your mother.
It needed a lot of work
but I had a vision for it.
Vintage rolltop desk here.
I haven't decided whether to put
the fern on the right or the left side,
but you know,
sometimes you just gotta wing it.
Left side.
And right outside, I want to put up
a basketball hoop for the kids.
This is your seduction lounge.
Sex swing there,
vibrating Jell-O pit right there,
rotating Vietnamese Shame Wheel
right here.
Don't ask, you're not ready.
And that basketball hoop?
Outdoor stripper pole.
We'll just tell the ladies
to be careful in the winter.
You think a tongue stuck
to a frozen pole is bad...
Let's go outside for a second.
We have a confession.
This wasn't really about
seeing Ted's house.
It's an intervention.
Thank God.
I'll go first.
Ted, this house you bought
for your hypothetical family
is super weird.
We talk about it behind your back.
This intervention isn't for me.
It's for you.
Why did Barney need an intervention?
It all started a few nights earlier.
I can't believe your giant TV is broken.
It's March Madness.
Okay, I think I see what the problem is.
Barney, can you grab me a screwdriver?
Sure thing.
Luis. Barney Stinson, 12 H.
I got a hundred bucks
if you can be here in five, thanks.
You call the Super for a screwdriver?
Here's the thing
about me and tools...
The only one I know how to use
is attached to me,
and I am not going to try
putting it in the TV.
Again.
That's ridiculous.
Everyone should know how to use tools.
Well, here's our screwdriver now.
Guys, I'm pretty sure
that's not Luis.
But I can't be certain.
Someone introduce yourself.
I got your letter.
Dad?
Team Who's this fucking mother ?
Synchronisation :
Kyros, MiniBen314, Strex, Titou
Adaptation :
H3AV3N, Kenji, Luoleilina, tactactac
Relecture :
Titou
6x19 - Legendaddy (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
I can't believe Barney is talking
to his dad right now.
What do you say after three decades
of not seeing each other?
"So, how about those
last 30 Super Bowls"?
Now I feel bad about making fun of him
for the tool thing.
My dad was the one
who taught me all that stuff.
To be fair, everyone has
some glaring gap in knowledge,
something really obvious
you somehow never learned.
Okay, but a screwdriver?
I don't have any gaps
that fundamental.
I seem to recall...
Daniel Burnham was an architect
whose ever-shifting style and aesthetic
made him a true architectural
chamma-leeon.
And only the most gifted chamma-leeon
could've designed
classic beaux arts masterpieces
right alongside
sleek modern flatirons.
His name might as well have been
Daniel Chamma-leeon.
Professor?
Do you mean "chameleon"?
Betty, I'm pretty sure
it's pronounced "chamma-leeon," so...
Class dismissed.
No homework.
For a while.
Okay, I learned that word
by reading it.
That's how I've always pronounced it.
That wasn't easy.
It took a lot of "ch-aracter"
to admit that.
- Scherbatsky, you want to tussle?
- I'll tussle.
- Let's tussle.
- Marine biologist.
Please, no.
So this really sucks,
but I'm going to be in the North Pole
for three months.
Seriously?
The North Pole?
If you want to break up with me,
just tell it to me straight.
Don't pretend you're going
someplace we all know doesn't exist.
I'm going to be studying
the mating habits of...
Of who?
Santa's elves?
Rudolph?
You know what?
I'm going on a trip, too, Scott.
It starts in Narnia.
It works its way up to Candyland,
and then, congratulate me,
because I'm the new Defense Against
the Dark Arts teacher at Hogwarts.
Expelliarmus!
The North Pole is a real place.
You know that, right?
You want to get pizza later?
I think we should break up.
I still think about him
in the shower.
- Tell us everything.
- How'd it go, bud?
Where do I begin?
I'm not sure how to start this.
I think I need a drink.
Me, too.
Glen McKenna, neat.
Nice order.
Up top.
It's been 30 years.
And now you just show up
out of nowhere?
This is going to take me a minute.
Yeah. I understand.
By the way, hell of a tie.
Italian silk?
I love you.
I'm so glad we're best friends now.
Make a muscle.
Guys, my dad's awesome.
He's the mother of all fathers.
Check this out.
Back when I was a kid,
you were a roadie.
- Do you still do that?
- Not anymore.
Back in '83, I'm lugging amps
for The Stones through West Germany,
and their tour manager loses his arms,
bus-surfing through a tunnel.
Gnarly.
Long story short,
I've been managing tours ever since,
and that dude high-fives people
with his face now.
You're funny.
My dad's funny.
So, all these years,
there's this one question
I've been dying to ask him.
- Why did you abandon me?
- Why'd you wait so long?
You've hurt me before,
why should I trust you now?
Do you... get laid a lot?
Big-time.
Observe.
That took you five seconds.
Was it that long?
Life's too short for chatty chicks.
You're a master.
You are legen... wait for it...
daddy!
Legendaddy!
The man is a god.
And he's still out there,
living the dream.
So I'm going to Sydney tomorrow
with Bon Jovi.
I'll be on the road all the year.
That's cool.
You want to join me
for the tour's Asian leg?
This is going to be the second-most fun
I've ever had on an Asian leg.
We know you're psyched, but...
- be careful.
- What do you mean?
Well, this guy has flaked out
on your whole life.
He might be telling you
what you want to hear.
We just don't want
to see you get hurt.
First of all, Robin,
my dad could beat up your dad.
Second, you don't have to worry.
He's cool.
Now if you'll excuse me.
I have to go renew my passport,
and get a travel-sized rotating
Vietnamese Shame Wheel.
Don't ask, you're not ready.
I hope Barney's dad isn't pretending
to be something he's not,
That would make Jerry
a real chamma-leeon.
You have gaps, too, Lily.
You got nothing on me.
Can you toss me a beer?
Sure, honey.
You have terrible aim.
That's not true.
At our apartment,
you're the one who pees on the floor.
Barney's dad.
You're Barney's friends, right?
Aren't you supposed to be off
managing some tour in Australia?
What?
I'm a driving instructor
up in White Plains.
And I need your help.
Barney won't return my calls.
Barney won't return your calls?
He said you two
had an amazing night together.
That's not what happened.
I'm not sure how to start this.
I need a drink.
Me, too.
- Glen McKenna, neat.
- Milk, skim.
Milk?
You're taking it easy.
Crazy night?
I'll say.
Between you and me,
I had a lot of acid last night.
I think it was the chili dog.
I had to take four Tums.
I was up till, like, 9:30.
When I was a kid, you were a roadie.
You still do that?
I switched lanes years ago.
I should explain.
I'm a driving instructor.
Now you get it, right?
I get it.
But when I was a kid,
you were this total badass.
I know.
I was a real hard partier.
Now we're getting to the good stuff.
The drugs, the alcohol, the women...
- I was out of control.
- Out of control
So when your mom said
I couldn't see you anymore,
it was rock bottom for me.
I'm so sorry.
You ever bang Stevie Nicks?
Barney wasn't interested in my apology.
He just wanted me to be cool.
And I was so desperate
to connect with him,
I did something I'm not proud of.
I started bragging.
I bet you didn't know this about me,
but I've published
two nonfiction books about Asparagus.
And one fiction.
I'm credited with inventing
the word "furgling."
It means fumbling for keys.
So then all the county fair
judges started chanting,
"More quiche! More quiche!"
I guess you could call me
the LeBron James of drapes.
I could tell he just wanted me
to be this big ladies' man,
so...
What a hottie, huh?
I'm sure you're a real player.
Big-time.
Observe.
Excuse me, that's my son over there.
I'm trying to reconnect
with him after 30 years.
Would you just write down
any seven numbers here,
so that I can impress him?
Please, I'm desperate.
My God, you're a natural.
Think of the pickup plays
we can run as a father-son duo.
There's the "Father Knows Breast,"
there's the "Bush Dynasty,"
the "Lick Father, Lick Son."
I couldn't do that.
- Why?
- I have a family now.
That's my wife, Cheryl,
my daughter Carly, she's in college.
This is my son JJ.
I was hoping you could come over
to dinner sometime and meet them.
You're all wearing matching sweaters.
That's cute.
I gotta get going, Jerry, but...
This was great.
Glad we did this.
I made him wait
all these years for me and...
I'm just not the guy
he wanted me to be.
I know I don't deserve it, but...
I need another chance
to connect with my son.
We think you should
give him another chance.
That's the real reason
we're out here.
He lives ten minutes away.
- What?
- You're having dinner with him tonight.
No, I most certainly am not.
I met him. He's not my kind of bro
and that's that.
- It's not more than that?
- Get it through your heads.
I am never gonna
talk to my dad again.
I'm never gonna talk to my dad again.
But your dad is alive
and he lives just down the road.
- Fine, I'll go.
- Awesome. Lily, keys.
I'm literally 11 inches from you.
And so Barney agreed
to give his dad one more chance.
You must be Barney.
I'm Cheryl.
It's just so nice
to finally meet you.
I love that suit.
Thank you very much.
And I love your...
... coat.
I love your coat.
That's your coat, Barney.
I just took it from you.
Well, I do love it.
It's doing a nice job
covering up that chair.
Guess now we wait.
I got an idea how to pass the time.
A little trivia game.
Reindeer: real or fake?
I'm not an idiot.
Reindeer are obviously...
Yikes! I'm surrounded
by a bunch of dum-dums.
Good thing I don't have any gaps
in my knowledge.
I am perfect.
For the love of God, guys,
enough already.
What, baby?
You've been treating me with kid gloves
ever since my dad died.
That's not true.
- Robin, don't disagree with Marshall.
- I'm sorry.
I first noticed it at the bar.
Can you get me a mojito?
Normally, you would've given me crap
for an hour about a voice crack
that pubescently girl-like,
but nothing.
So then I started to test you guys.
The Phantom Menace is by far
the best Star Wars movie.
It ages well, that's the thing.
You guys like my new soul patch?
Righteous hair tab, brotha.
And once I figured it out,
I started doing
crazy stuff
to see how far you'd let me go.
This is Rex.
He's a possum.
I found him in the trash.
He lives with us now.
I love him.
We are living with a possum.
Rex is violent and he hates us.
But, baby, you just lost your dad.
None of us wants to upset you.
Please.
If you guys really want me to get over
the worst tragedy of my life,
I'm begging you, tear me a new one.
But not like Rex tried to
in my sleep last night.
JJ, dinner.
When I got your letter,
I dug this up.
You were probably
too young to remember,
but this is you, this is me,
and, of course, ZZ Top.
I do remember that.
I climbed up on his lap and told him
what I wanted for Christmas.
I used to love taking you backstage.
You were the coolest little kid.
Hi.
It's great to finally meet you.
JJ, I'm talking to Dad right now.
Seriously,
it's time.
What are my gaps?
I guess maybe one gap you have is...
you can't wink.
Don't you think that
maybe we should go home
and... do the laundry?
You can't swallow pills.
I got one.
You think John Kennedy
and Jack Kennedy are the same person.
Right?
What?
So, Barney,
You have a pretty big job
with a bank?
I do.
I make a ton of money.
How much do you make, JJ?
I'm 11.
Now we all know you make excuses.
I was talking about money.
Actually, JJ has a job.
Tell him.
I got a paper route.
Good time to get into print media.
- Right, Dad?
- Good slam, Barney.
Jerry.
It's all good fun.
Just ribbing
among long lost brothers.
JJ's a heck of a basketball player.
You don't strike me
as the athletic type, Jayj.
Dad, check it.
Triceps.
What gym do you go to?
Fourth period?
Sounds like you're having
your fourth period.
- Am I right, Dad?!
- Got him again.
Uh, maybe that's enough.
Why? JJ started it.
What does JJ even stand for anyway?
Jerky... Jerkface?
JJ stands for Jerome Jr.
Jerome Jr...
He's named after you.
Excuse me.
I like having a brother.
You add too much water to oatmeal.
I drown the son of a bitch.
You consistently miss
at least one belt loop.
It's like I'm blind.
You're too old to ask
to see the cockpit.
Guys... my dad just died.
Honey.
No, I'm just kidding.
This is great.
I really, I really missed this.
What is going on?
- This is mine.
- I don't understand.
JJ gets a childhood, a dad,
a real family and> a basketball hoop?
No. I at least get the hoop.
I'm taking it with me.
Come down and talk to me.
Why? Why should I?
You're lame, okay?
You're just some lame suburban dad.
So why are you so mad?
If you were gonna be
some lame suburban dad,
why couldn't you have
been that for me?!
I know I screwed up.
"Screwed up" doesn't even
begin to describe...
I know, I know!
I want to fix this,
and I don't know how!
Tell me what I can do!
I'll do anything!
You're never gonna
get it down like that.
Just put the pointy end
into the grooves.
That's it. Now turn it.
Righty tighty, lefty loosey.
I have no good excuse, Barney.
It took me years
before I was even able
to look myself in the mirror
for the way I let you down.
It took courage
to send me that letter.
More courage than I've ever had.
I owe you a lifetime of apologies,
and I...
I just have no idea where to begin.
Can you help me with this?
Here, got it.
Look, if you...
ever feel like you're ready,
I'd love nothing more
than to be a part of your life.
Are you sure
you don't want to talk about it?
I'm fine.
Buddy?
You, still want
a basketball hoop out there?
I also really liked
your outdoor stripper pole idea.
You were right.
A kid needs a hoop.
www.tvsubtitles.net