NARRATOR:
Kids, in the fall of 2010,
our friends
Stuart and Claudia had a baby,
and Marshall and Lily
were the first
to visit the happy new parents.
MARSHALL:
So, have you guys
landed on a name yet?
We're trying, but it's
tougher than you think.
You see, I like "Tiffany."
And I don't want my daughter
to have a whore's name.
That's my mother's name.
I know.
Oh, I got it.
How 'bout we name the baby
after you-- "Frigid Shrew."
Oh, that's good.
No, no, no, no.
Let's call
her "Vodka."
Then at least we know
you'd hold her tight
and never let her go!
Don't knock the vodka.
Wouldn't have a kid without it.
(chuckling)
Stuart, you are so...
That's not gonna be us, right?
I mean, how hard can it be
to name a baby?
Right? I mean, just
look at her. Yeah.
She's clearly a...
Emily.
Lisa.
Lisa?!
Emily?!
(baby crying)
Uh-oh.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Okay!
I made a list of
awesome baby names.
Starting at the top:
number one...
I'm gonna stop you
right here, Marshall.
You name
a chubby white kid "LeBron,"
and he's the one getting stuffed
in the basketball hoop.
Then I'm also crossing off,
um, "Shaquille"...
Mm-hmm.
"Hakeem,"
and "Dikembe."
Hey, what about "Rob"?
"Rob"?
No.
Why not?
Hey, Rob. What are
you gonna make?
A turkey?
Honka, honka!
(gasps)
Not "Rob."
Okay, um, how
about "Ryan"?
TED:
Ooh.
(all screaming)
Not "Ryan."
"Johnny?"
Hey, where's the goldfish?
(gasps)
Not "Johnny."
Or "Gil."
(whimpers)
"Jeremy."
(music playing)
Jeremy, no!
Definitely
not "Jeremy."
His stuff was
so derivative.
Well, I mean,
geez, Lily.
Well, whatever you do,
do not name your
baby "Becky," right?
Why? What?
What?
Becky.
My new co-anchor?
Don't you guys
ever watch the show?
Oh, honey, I really try.
Our DVR won't recognize it
as a television program.
Mm-hmm.
I watched.
Robin insisted I confirm
how "awful" Becky is,
so last night I
checked it out.
Peace talks
in the region
have been described
as, "productive."
Becky?
(in baby voice):
Last night, in Staten Island,
a taco cart owner
was robbed at gunpoint.
Aww...
That's so sad.
Becky,
we're-we're journalists.
We can't get emotional
about the news, we...
Oh, no!
They stole all his money
and then pelted him
with his own taco meat!
Who would do that?
Well, if you read the story,
we might find out.
Oh, can I do this one,
about the horse?
I love horseys.
Mm-hmm.
Aww, the horse died.
Guys!
This news is
all really sad.
Okay, no holds barred--
what'd you think of Becky?
Mmm...
(muttering)
I thought she was charming.
ROBIN:
You, too?
Can somebody please
explain to me
why the little girl act
works on men?
You want the long version
or the short version?
Short version.
Who's your daddy?
(all groan)
You know, when you
think about that,
that phrase
is really creepy.
No, it's not.
It's fun.
Here, watch this.
Hey, Lily...
Who's your daddy?
(laughing)
Okay, uh, let me
get this straight.
So, in, uh,
in this scenario,
because you make such
sweet love to Lily,
she is now
your daughter.
No, she is not
my daughter.
I'm just her daddy.
Wow. That is disgusting.
Exactly. And it's not like
the opposite would work.
There's no way a guy
could pick up a girl,
going around talking
like a little boy.
Challenge accepted.
No.
I, Barney Stinson,
will pick up a girl whilst
talking like a little boy.
(all grumbling in protest)
Okay.
Here's my list
of baby names.
Oh.
What about "Tara"?
No.
Not "Tara."
Tara was the hottest girl
in my high school.
We were all, like,
obsessed with her.
MARSHALL:
We didn't just talk about her
and fantasize about her...
We wrote songs about her.
♪ Tara, your booty
is so smooth ♪
♪ And I hope this isn't rude ♪
♪ But I want to get up on it. ♪
Not "Tara."
What about "Esther"?
(rock song plays)
ANNOUNCER:
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Coming up on the main stage,
give it up for Esther!
Oh. Oh. Hey, Barney.
That prime rib
was surprisingly good,
but it's 10:30
in the morning.
I don't need to see
a lady get naked and dance.
Oh, Esther gets naked.
But she doesn't dance.
Then what does she do?
(blowing up balloon)
(balloon pops)
Sweet mother nature!
That was my card!
ANNOUNCER:
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Give it up for Esther!
(explosive pop,
men cheering and whistling)
Not "Esther."
I need a drink.
Ted? Ted?
Marshall, your list
is entirely boy names.
You do realize there's
roughly a 50% chance
of you having
a daughter, right?
Okay, honestly, I've never
thought about having a girl.
I don't want to think
about having a girl.
Tara, Esther--
can you imagine being
one of those girls' dads?
♪ Marshall's daughter ♪
♪ Your booty ♪
♪ Your booty's so smooth. ♪
ANNOUNCER:
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
On the main stage, give it up
for Marshall's daughter.
He screwed up
my childhood.
That's why
I do this.
I have no idea how
to raise a daughter!
What if she
makes bad choices?
I mean, what if
she winds up dating some...
Oh, God.
Papa, I want you to
meet my new boyfriend.
Hey, bro.
Thanks for making
such a hottie.
(weak laughter)
Who's your daddy?
You are, 'cause
of all the sex we have.
(Barney chuckles salaciously)
(vomiting)
I don't want a girl.
I just want a little boy.
It's not what it
sounds like, folks.
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
JUDY:
Marshall? Is that you?
MARSHALL:
Oh, okay, um...
You guys, you're a little
too close to the camera.
Can you back up a bit?
How's this?
Every time.
Um, can you just sit
in front of the computer
like normal human beings?
Perfect!
Perfect.
What's up, shooter?
Um, to be honest,
I'm getting a little freaked out
about the idea
of having a daughter.
I know you two probably
aren't the right people
to talk to about this.
You had all boys.
Oh, well, that was
just dumb luck.
Hey, honey, would you get me a
brewski from out of the shed?
Sure. You want
anything, Marshall?
I'm in a computer, Mom.
Oh.
Yeah, all boys.
Total co-winky-dink.
It was no co-winky-dink.
Since the Viking age,
the Eriksen men have
passed down ancient secrets
for conceiving boys.
Number one, avoid lemons.
They're baby girl fertilizer.
Okay... No offense, Dad,
but I doubt there's any
scientific data to support--
(mocking tone): "I doubt there's
any scientific data to support..""
I had all sons.
Your grandfather
had all sons.
Your great-grandfather
Scoreboard!
Who you gonna listen to?
Me? Or "scientific data"?
Members of the G-8
convened today in Vienna
to discuss plans to fight
climate change by re-- What?
Ask me what I
did yesterday.
Hey, Becky, Becky, this is
our news segment, okay?
Nobody cares
what you did yesterday.
Lighten up, Robin.
(in baby voice):
What'd you do, sweetheart?
Mike!
Well, I'm new in town
and don't know many people.
But yesterday,
I met the sweetest man,
who took me
on a tour of the city.
(whispering):
Guys, New York is kind of cool.
Okay, back to the
G-8 conference.
Hello?
Mike, can I get
in the shot?
Fantastic.
Then this cutie patootie
took me to this bar
called MacLaren's,
right underneath his apartment.
Wait-- did you go out
with Ted Mosby?
Yes!
Guys, I went out
with Robin's roommate.
I saw her bedroom.
(whispering):
She's a messy Bessie.
In other news, later today,
a Manhattan architect gets
punched in the throat.
Ow!
Ted, of all the
women in New York,
you had to go out with
an eight-year-old girl?
Not what it sounds like, folks.
Ted, you know that I hate her.
How could you go out
on a date with this girl?
It wasn't a date.
She came over to
the apartment looking for you.
I made Robin my famous
chocolate chip cookies.
But instead of chocolate chips,
I used gummie bears.
Aww...
(shrieks)
A spider!
Let me guess: she acted
like a helpless little girl,
and you stepped in
as the big, strong man.
I don't know
if that's totally true.
It's okay, little darlin'.
Poor spider.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Spiders gotta die
so trees can grow.
Then I held her tight and told
her it was all gonna be okay.
By the way, I think
I only wounded the spider.
It crawled off into my bedroom.
Wait. Is that why you slept
on the couch last night?
(scoffing):
Yeah, I slept.
I'm dying out here.
Talking like a little boy
is not working with the ladies.
(in childlike voice):
Wow, lady.
You got some tig
ol' bitties!
(stammering)
Gosh!
Your body's a perfect...
this many.
Hi.
Do you want to wrestle with our
special bathing suit places?
Come on!
Mm, I just need
two seconds, baby.
I know you think
that's a compliment,
but I'd rather
you took your time.
No, um... I'll
be right back.
Ancient Norse wisdom
tells us that, to sire a son,
you must do three things right
before you lay with your maiden.
First, eat pickled herring.
Eat it!
This is ridiculous.
ANNOUNCER: Gentlemen,
gentlemen, on the main stage,
throwing her life away,
give it up
for Marshall's daughter!
(applause)
(sobbing)
Who's your granddaddy?
That guy.
(sobbing)
(groans softly)
(gagging)
(little boy voice):
Hey, want to have a three-way
with me and my imaginary friend?
His name's Otis.
Hey, hey, want
to come to my house
and play telephone?
I got the string;
you got the cans.
(giggles)
I wet myself!
Will you change me?
Can't blame her on that one.
Guys...
I have some terrible,
terrible news.
I, Barney Stinson,
can't pick up a girl whilst
talking like a little boy.
Challenge forfeited.
(high-pitched gasp)
Yeah, we don't care about
this... No one challenged you,
so it wasn't really a challenge.
(sobs)
(whispers):
I'm sorry.
MAN: Hey, Gerard,
what's with that shirt?
Nobody could pick up
a chick wearing that thing.
Challenge accept...
(sobs)
Wow, I'm glad that's over.
It was creepy watching Barney
talk like a little kid.
Oh, but you find it irresistible
when Becky does?
I don't get it.
The Ted that I went out with was
attracted to the kind of woman
who could use a steak knife
without supervision.
For your information,
Becky doesn't like steak,
she likes pasghetti.
Spaghetti.
And more importantly,
she makes me feel needed.
Needed? (scoffs)
She makes
training wheels feel needed.
Hey, it's nice to feel needed.
And you know what?
It's not a feeling guys get
when they're with you.
(groans weakly)
Son...
Viking lore tells us
that to ensure the continuation
of your noble male lineage...
get a big old bowl of ice
and dunk your man sack
right in there!
(laughing)
You two and
your football.
(sighs)
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
(chuckles)
(ice cubes clack)
(screaming)
Now get in there,
point Lily due north
and make me a grandson!
Eriksen!
(crying)
When we were dating, I...
I didn't make you feel needed?
Come on! You always
took charge of everything.
Oop.
I got this.
Thanks.
This okay?
Am I hurting y...
I got this.
Whoa!
(grunts)
(door rattling)
Someone's trying to break in--
call the cops.
I got this.
Did that really bother you?
Well, yeah.
It's nice to be needed.
Look, I'm sorry.
(phone chimes)
I didn't mean to upset you.
It's Becky.
Aw, she's trapped
in a revolving door.
I got this.
Yeah.
(goofy voice):
Let's make a baby!
Mm, mm, mm, mm!
Whoa!
Baby, you're packing snowballs,
and your breath smells
like a mermaid fart.
Loving the dirty talk-- but
you know what's even hotter?
If we face this-a-way.
Ooh, we're bad.
Wait... hey, baby,
why are you facing me north?
(gasps)
You're trying
to make us have a boy.
I... can ex...
How do you know
about the north thing?
Um, um...
And what are you doing
with those lemons?
Baby girl fertilizer!
You're trying to make
us have a girl!
You are trying to
make us have a girl.
All my least favorite students
have been boys.
So I Googled
"how to make a girl"--
some really weird
stuff came up--
but finally, I found
this conception Web site
that said you should...
point south at the moment
of conception...
eat a lemon...
(sighs)
(groans)
...and heat up your lady parts
to a balmy 105 degrees.
(blow-dryer whooshing)
Ooh... ah...
Oh, that's not bad.
MARSHALL:
Eriksen!
Lily, how could you do...
exactly the same thing I did?
You're supposed to be
the sane one.
See that?
Another boy expecting a woman
to clean up his mistakes.
That's why girls
are way better than boys.
Oh, really. Well,
then how come whenever there's
a creepy kid in a horror movie
it's always a little girl?
Or twin girls, who speak...
(eerily):
in unison.
Oh, well, what about Chucky?
Okay, A) He was a doll;
B) He was possessed
by an adult serial killer;
and C) How could you bring up
Chucky right before bed?
(doorbell rings)
Hey.
Hey. Um, when we were dating,
did... did I
make you feel needed?
No, I didn't feel like
you needed me at all.
(sighs)
That's what I thought.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Wait, where are you...
That's a compliment.
You are the least needy woman
I've ever met-- that's awesome.
I mean, no guy's gonna say
"Who's your daddy?"
to Robin Scherbatsky.
You're your own daddy.
And mommy.
And weird survivalist uncle
who lives in a cabin
with a shotgun
blaming stuff on the government.
And that
is what makes you the most...
amazing, strong...
independent woman
I've ever banged.
Thanks, Barney.
You know, um...
there's something
that I wanted to ask you,
and I don't really know how
to say it so... here goes.
Who's the crazy chick
in the apron?
(baby voice): Someone naughty
left his toys on the floor
and needs to be spanked
on his tushy-tush.
(baby voice):
Uh-oh, I'm in "twubble."
You did it? How?
Last night,
after admitting defeat,
I just let myself go.
Mmm, that looks so good.
Can I have some?
No!
It's my ice cream;
you can't have any.
(baby voice): Someone needs
to teach you how to share.
Who's your mommy?
Challenge completed!
(chuckles)
Now, uh, can you get
this freak out of here?
I'm really scared.
I got this.
Oh, so you finally
agreed on a name?
CLAUDIA (sighs):
Uh, well,
the other night she ran
a really high fever.
STUART: We rushed her
to the emergency room
at 3:00 in the morning,
but they wouldn't
admit her without a name.
Right then and there, we
realized how stupid we were being.
We looked
at each other
and, well, we just knew.
Our baby's name is...
Esther.
(chokes)
Esther?
ANNOUNCER:
Esther!
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
We're idiots.
Baby, names and gender,
it's just, like...
it's some way of giving
ourselves the illusion
that we have any
control whatsoever.
I- I just want a healthy,
happy, 12-pound--
Whoa.
Ten-pound?
Eight-pound?
(sighs)
I guess, but, dude,
you're writing checks
my vagina can't cash.
(laughs)
I love you.
And I'm gonna love the crap
out of whatever baby we have.
Me, too.
You know what?
We should just think of a name that's
good for either a girl or a boy.
Like, um...
Jamie.
Marshall...
we just named our baby.
Jamie.
Mmm...
Not Jamie.
(merry-go-round calliope
playing) Shoe's untied. I got it.
Yeah, this is over.
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net