Kids, the heart
is a mysterious muscle.
You never really know
what's going on in there.
So after Uncle Marshall
lost his father,
he decided to get
his heart checked.
And so did I...
and so did Lily...
and so did Robin.
And then Marshall went again,
just to be sure.
There was only one holdout.
I don't need to go
to a heart doctor.
I drink every day, I sleep
three hours every night,
and I have multiple
sex partners.
I'm doing everything right.
Barney, come on,
this is important.
We need you around
for a long time.
Without you, we'd have to find
some other sex-fueled,
depraved animal to entertain us.
Actually,
I'm thinking about
getting a dog again.
Oh, can she? Can she get
a dog, please Dad?
No. If you get a dog,
I'm going to be the one stuck
taking care of it.
You wouldn't have
to take care of it.
Really? And who watered
the philodendron
on your bookcase
and sang it back to life?
Yeah, that was made
out of silk, Ted.
Okay, Robin, what you need is indeed
something that buries a bone,
but I'm not talking
about a dog.
I'm talking about a man.
Here we go.
You're clearly trying to fill a hole...
in her heart.
You feel like the seventh wheel,
because now Ted is with Zoey
and Barney's with Nora
and Lily's with Big Fudge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, Big Fudge.
"With"?
I am not "with" Nora.
Wrong preposition.
Later tonight I'm hoping
to be on Nora, right?
Or under Nora, right?
Or, we're all adults,
I'll just say it...
behind Nora.
I don't know.
This will be your second date.
Oh, Barney's got feeling for a girl.
Yeah. Penis feelings.
Because she's hot.
Guys, as you know,
I only have one rule...
Barney said this a lot.
if you're gonna get it on
in a Port-O-Potty,
do it early in the day.
Never screw over a girl
whose last name
ends in a vowel.
'Cause she's got brothers.
Never date a girl
with a hook for a hand.
Never go out with
the same girl more than once.
Then why are you going
out with Nora again?
There is an exception.
And it was always
the same exception.
...unless she's hot.
Arr!
And she is indeed hot.
Which is why nothing,
not even God himself...
yeah, I said it, Beardy...
is going to stand in the way
of tonight being legend...
Wait for it.
Uh-oh.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, Nora, sorry I'm late.
I'm just, uh, just
getting over a cold.
Oh, no. How long
have you been sick?
About 20 minutes.
Can't seem to shake it.
Okay, 'cause I was going
to say you look a little...
Handsome? Rich?
Well-endowed?
Huh, let's say well-endowed...
with phlegm.
All right, let's go.
It's bedtime.
The bed...
that's where all the...
...happens.
Come on, let's get
you sorted out.
That night, Barney didn't
take care of business.
Instead, Nora took care
of Barney.
Ah. Thank you.
Good night, Barney.
Good night, Mommy.
Wow, she nursed you
back to health?
No. I didn't even
see her boobs.
She just took care of me.
Oh, hey, guys.
This is Nate.
- Nate, these are my friends.
- What's up. guys?
Nate Scooberman.
But everyone calls me Scooby.
I'd love to hang out,
but I really gotta hit the john.
Uh, yeah, it's right in here...
Scooby.
Thanks, brah.
I like you guys.
Oh, Robin,
if you weren't so much stronger
than me, I would slap you.
What? You told me
to meet someone.
I know, and, look,
he seems plenty nice,
but I didn't mean bring home
the first guy
you bump into on the street.
Actually, I met him in the park.
- Oh.
- Oh. -Oh.
Should have just
let you get a dog.
Oh, oh, I should go.
Lily, can I talk to you for a second?
So, um, I made an appointment
with that cardiologist.
Aw, and you want me
to go with you
'cause you're a little scared?
No.
Do you want me to go with you
because you're a lot scared?
Yes!
Okay, fine.
On one condition.
You have to promise me
you won't lie to Nora.
She seems like
something special.
Okay, I promise
I won't lie to her.
I may, however,
lie on her.
I said, bang-bang,
bangity-bang.
♪ Bang-bang-bang,
bangity-bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang,
bangity bang... ♪
Are we done?
♪ A bang-bang,
bangity-bang. ♪
Well, Barney,
your heart sounds fine.
See, Lily?
She was worried.
Although it seems like you might
have a slight arrhythmia.
Ow! Nails, nails!
It's probably nothing
to worry about,
but I'd like you to wear
this heart monitor
for the next 24 hours.
Twen... Flag on the play, Doc.
I have a date tonight.
Don't worry. It's totally safe.
Unless part of your big date
involves connecting yourself
to a car battery.
Well, now it doesn't.
And exactly 24 hours later,
they returned for the results.
Okay, everything
looks fine here,
although I did notice
a few irregularities.
There's nothing to be...
...alarmed about.
Go on, Doctor.
What happened
at 8:46 p.m. last night?
Well, let's see...
uh, Wheel of Fortune,
naked push-ups, naked chin-ups...
I was at dinner.
This might be a little forward,
but do you have a bomb
strapped to your chest?
This? No, no.
It's a heart monitor.
It's a medical thing.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I've been trying
not to stare
at your chest all night.
What's that like?
So is everything okay?
My friend's dad passed away
from a sudden heart attack.
So I'm just getting
myself checked out, too.
Oh, I am so sorry.
Thanks.
Um, Barney, what
I'm about to say
is going to sound
a little weird,
but I think I'm starting to like you,
so I have to say it.
Well, for what it's worth,
I'm not easily shocked.
Unless you dump water on me,
'cause I'll just...
No. What is it?
I want to get married.
I mean, not tonight,
or even to you, necessarily.
But that's what I want.
And if that's going
to scare you off,
then I'd rather
it scare you off now.
I want a family,
and I want to live
in a little house
with a garden and a tree
for the kids to climb.
And I want to go
to sleep every night
with the same person
by my side,
and wake up next to him
in the morning every morning
for the rest of our lives.
Just thought
you should know that.
You have to promise me
you won't lie to Nora!
That's exactly
what I want, too.
I'm really into gardening, but these
squirrels keep messing with my tomatoes.
Every time I see them
in the backyard,
I'm like, "get out of here!"
And they run off,
but sure enough,
a few minutes later,
there they are again.
And I'm like,
"get out of here!"
So annoying.
I smell food.
Does this place have a kitchen?
I'll be right back.
Okay, but you have to admit
that he is a lot of fun.
Oh, I actually think
he's quite intelligent
for what he is.
And what is he?
He's a dog.
He's totally a dog.
What? You saw him
hitting on someone?
No, I didn't say,
"He a dawg."
I said, "He's a dog."
As in, a dog.
I think we've all noticed
a few curious mannerisms.
Or rather, doggerisms.
Uh, Scooby, the tag's
still on your jeans.
Where?
Okay, Scooby, you ready?
Oh!
Good boy, Scooby!
- Good job, Scoob!
- Good boy!
- That last one did not happen.
- Okay, you're right.
He dropped it.
He's not a dog.
Robin, it's fine.
You said you wanted a dog
and you got one.
And the best part is,
he got his shots.
Hey, guys, got my shots.
You are so playful.
- Nice job fetching those.
- Guys...
Yeah, guys, cut it out.
Scooby, sit.
So, Scooby, we were thinking
if you're going to be
hanging out with our Robin,
you should be properly vetted.
Uh, yeah. We hope our nosiness
doesn't give you "paws."
How did you meet?
Tell us the "tail""
Yes, how did you
"whisker" off her feet?
Shed a little light
on the matter.
Did you send her an e-mail,
or did you "collar"?
Guys, just stop hounding him.
Oh, geez.
No, no, you're right, Robin.
We don't want your
new guy to "flea."
We're just trying to make
sure he's not a heel.
So, moving from Canada,
that transition must have
been pretty "ruff."
Sure was. My part of Canada's
pretty different from New York.
Oh, I bet it was
an "Incredible Journey""
- What part of Canada is that? Speak.
- Labrador.
This isn't happening.
Hey, Nate,
why don't you go play
some music on the jukebox.
- No, I'm good.
- Oh, shoot, dropped my keys.
- I'll get 'em.
- Okay.
Hey, guys, this is Nora.
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you. - Hey.
- Nice to meet you.
- How's it going?
We were just passing by,
and I wanted to pop in
for two reasons.
First, I wanted to let you know
that your friend Barney
is being a perfect gentleman.
Well, it's still early.
I'm being serious.
I had no idea that deep down,
he's such a romantic.
I had no idea he
had a deep down.
Oh, you should have
heard him at dinner.
I mean, I like being single,
but secretly,
I want to have kids.
How many do you want?
Three...
one of each.
You?
Three.
All in an old stone house.
Yeah, with ivy growing on it.
Cocktails on the patio.
And we must have a pool.
We?
A pool sounds brilliant.
Are you for real, Barney?
I really am.
Unbelievable.
I know, right?
And the second reason
we popped in
is 'cause I need
to use the loo.
But when I get back,
I'm dying to hear all about
Mr. Softy here.
I assure you, that's not
a nickname that I...
And that explains your
14-second cardiac arrest.
Barney, you promised
you wouldn't lie.
I'm not lying!
Guys, Nora's really special.
In fact...
I think I'm...
falling in love with her.
Guys! I'm serious.
I'm not going to
let you do this.
When Nora gets back here,
I'm blowing the whistle.
Just make sure it's not
a high-frequency whistle,
because we don't want to
torture Robin's boyfriend.
Guys, this is real.
And if you don't make me
look good in front of Nora,
just remember: I've got dirt
on each of you,
and I am not afraid to spill it.
Barney, you can't blackmail us
into lying to Nora.
Really, Lily?
Even if I were to mention,
oh, I don't know...
your kindergarten class's
pet guinea pig?
Mr. Buttons?
Oh, you son of a bitch.
Fine. I'll be nice.
- Marshall?
- You got nothing on me.
- The calzone?
- Checkmate.
Robin.
Don't say the Mr. T dream,
don't say the Mr. T dream,
don't say the Mr. T dream...
The Mr. T dream...
I'm lost.
Ted?
Go ahead. Give me your best.
My life's an open book.
The ballet class.
I once took a ballet class.
Not ashamed.
The 'N Sync concert.
1998. Cleveland's Gund Arena,
front row. Caught JC's shirt.
What else you got?
Okay, Ted.
The thermos.
I suppose it's possible Barney
has real feelings for Nora.
I do!
So be cool!
There's a man back there
who seems fascinated
by the records
flipping in the jukebox.
Sorry, toots.
He's taken.
So. How do you
all know Barney?
Oh, I don't know
how we know Barney.
How does anyone know
how they know anyone?
I like your pretty hair, help me.
We did not meet him
at a strip club.
No, sir.
Because...
Barney don't go
to no strip clubs.
Oh, come on. Barney's been
to a strip club once.
- Once?
- Thermos.
Nope. Not even once.
Really? So Barney really is
a genuinely a nice guy.
I don't recall.
Okay, I think that we're done
here, I think that we have
adequately established
that Barney is...
the kind of guy that you would
bring home to meet your parents.
Okay? So...
let's just drop it, all right?
It's funny you should say that,
because, as it happens,
my parents are in town.
They're only here
like once a year.
We're getting brunch tomorrow.
Do you want to meet them?
This was a big deal for Barney.
I only have one rule.
Never, ever, ever
meet a girl's parents.
Not even if she's hot?
Not even if her mom's hot.
I'd love to meet your parents.
It's a date.
Well, we should get going.
Walk me home?
Walk? Somebody say walk?
I'll go for a walk.
I love a good walk.
No, Scooby, you, uh...
stay!
Oh, no. I got called
back in to work.
Can you keep an eye
on him until I get back?
He's new to the city, and he
doesn't really know anyone.
I knew it. I knew it.
I knew if you got a dog,
- I'd wind up taking care of it.
- He's not a...
Good night.
What do we do now?
Oh! I got an idea.
I was in the park today, and
this guy sold me a big bag of...
Kids, it was a big bag
of sandwiches.
- Whoa.
- Put that away.
- You guys want to fire these up?
- Scooby, we're in our 30s.
We don't smoke
sandwiches anymore.
- Sandwich brownies?
- Okay.
Sandwiches make me hungry.
Truth.
Hey.
- I have a question.
- Yeah?
What did Barney mean
when he said "calzone"?
- Okay, I'll tell you.
- Okay.
One time Barney saw me drop
a calzone on the sidewalk,
pick it up,
and then keep eating it.
- It feels so good to finally say that
out loud. I... - Dude.
Listen to me.
You have nothing
to be ashamed of.
That calzone sounds amazing.
Guys, I found this on the floor.
Oh, my God.
Scooby ate the whole tray.
Ruh-roh!
Wait. Where is he, anyway?
Oh, dude.
Scooby got out!
Here we are.
I had a really
great time tonight.
Yeah, me, too.
Do you want to come upstairs?
I'd love to.
There's just one little thing,
and it probably
doesn't matter, but...
I don't want to get married.
I've been saying that all night
just to get in your pants.
Whoa!
Oh! Ahh!
Can you believe...
- Oh, my God! I found Scooby's wallet.
- Oh, no!
That means the poor guy's
out there with no identification.
Robin! Hey. Hey, um, remember Scooby?
Uh, well, he got out.
"Got out"? What do you mean?
He just walked out
of the apartment.
Someone must've
left the door open.
- It wasn't me.
- Me neither.
He must've figured out
how to open it himself.
He's so smart.
We should get him
on Letterman doing tricks.
I know Paul Schaffer's
sandwich guy.
This could happen.
Guys. Get yourselves together
and start looking for Scooby.
I'm on my way home.
Wait wait! Robin.
Can you pick up some calzones?
Wait... Nora, wait. Wait.
I'm sorry I misled you.
Misled? You lied to me!
You had your friends lie to me!
- I was on the spot. This is your fault.
- My fault?
Yeah, with the whole "I want
to get married" thing.
You can't just tell someone
exactly what you want
out of a relationship.
This... isn't England.
Good-bye, Barney.
Scooby!
Scoob!
- Great idea.
- No, great idea!
Okay. If you were new in town
and had just ingested an eighth
of sandwich, where would you go?
Of course.
Back to the pizza place!
Yeah! Maybe that's
where Scooby went.
Who's Scooby?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, have you seen Scooby?
Uh, yeah. Isn't that him taking
a leak on that fire hydrant?
Scooby!
Oh, hey! It's my friends!
No!
And that explains 12:51 a.m.
Okay. None of this suggests
a systemic issue.
Your heart's fine.
With a healthy diet, you can
live a long and happy life.
If nobody stabs you.
Day's not over.
Okay.
Lily, I'm sorry that I lied
about wanting to settle down.
No, that wasn't the lie.
The lie was when you told Nora
you were lying.
Because you weren't.
You want that stuff, Barney,
I know you do.
Okay. Maybe, eventually,
I could settle down.
50 years from now, if I have
like a Hefner thing going on
with some really hot twins.
But those twins
won't even be born
for another... 32 years.
I mean...
Nora's great.
She's wonderful. But...
What time was
your dinner reservation?
Last night? 8:30.
What did his heart do at 8:30?
It... literally
skipped a beat.
Your heart's talking to you,
Barney.
Do you have the guts
to listen to it?
- I lied.
- Barney.
When I said I lied,
that was a lie, and I'm sorry.
- I'm confused.
- So am I.
This, all of this,
this is totally new to me,
but I know it's what I want.
I want to be confused.
With you.
Mom, Dad...
this is Barney.
Hi.
I'm Barney.
Great to meet you.
Hey, you want to see
a magic trick?
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net