NARRATOR:
Kids, in the fall of 2010,
I was hosting my
very first Thanksgiving.
And I wanted it
to be unforgettable.
Instead of stuffing, I'm going
to fill the turkey with...
a slightly smaller turkey.
It's called a Turturkeykey!
A Turturkeykey?
Mm-hmm.
Uh-uh, oh-oh. ROBIN:
Yeah, I was there for
the "insertion."
He used shoehorns.
I'll be having sides.
Your loss.
All right, it's dead in here.
I'm gonna call it
a little early.
What? No!
You can't go now.
It's the night
before Thanksgiving.
College chicks
are back in town.
Their moms just made
a snide comment
about the weight they gained.
They called her a bitch,
but deep down,
they know she's right.
And they're about to walk
through that door,
where we will be waiting
with some light beer
and some rock hard approval.
Wh-what u-up?
Yeah. You don't want
to bail early, man.
You could become The Blitz.
(all groan)
NARRATOR: Blitz was a guy
we knew in college.
Sadly, he was cursed.
Well...
I'm calling it a little early.
Wh... you sure?
We got big plans.
Yeah. Remember how last week
we fired up a sandwich,
and we listened to Pink Floyd's
Dark Side of the Moon
while watching The Wizard of Oz?
Well, tonight,
we're doing the same thing,
only with "Weird Al" Yankovic's
Greatest Hits
and Apocalypse Now.
We'll see what happens.
Nah, it's Kraft/Croft night:
mac and cheese and Tomb Raider.
Biz-zow!
NARRATOR: You see, every time
Blitz left a place,
something amazing happened.
Oh! I'm sorry.
I thought this was my room.
(giggles)
Completely naked!
Aw, man!
And the movie
was awesome.
Aw, man!
At the exact moment
Brando first appeared,
"Weird Al" launched
right into "Eat It."
Aw, man!
NARRATOR:
And over the years,
"The Curse of The Blitz"
continued.
Well, I'm gonna call it.
I just got Madden 2K1, and I
can't stop thinking about it.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
All right, bye-bye!
Okay, later!
Good-bye!
Bye-Bye!
(pop)
Tap's broke!
Can't turn 'em off!
Free beer for everyone!
(cheering)
Aw, man!
You know what?
Ted, go ahead-- leave early
to do something lame.
Just don't blame us
if you become... The Blitz.
(random groans) All
right, first of all...
there's nothing lame
about brining a Turturkeykey,
copyright pending.
And secondly,
I don't believe "The Curse
of The Blitz" is real. (gasps)
NARRATOR: Kids, I'd live
to regret those words.
You see, the "Curse of Blitz"
could be passed
from one person to the next,
at any moment.
Blitz had gotten the curse from
Jerry Windheim,
back in freshman year,
who got it years before that
from Davey Beaterman.
The original Blitz, Matt Blitz,
was a guy who went to Wesleyan
back in the '60s.
He dropped out right before
the school went co-ed.
And then,
Thanksgiving morning...
What the hell happened here?
Hey! Morning, Blitz!
Aw, man!
No, no! Let's get
one thing straight, okay?
I am not The Blitz.
♪ My Blitzy lies
over the ocean ♪
over the sea ♪
♪ My Blitzy lies
over the ocean ♪
♪ So bring back my
Blitzy... ♪ Please stop.
Okay, fine.
♪...To me. ♪
The Gentleman!
THE GROUP: The Gentleman!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
What's that?
What's "The Gentleman"?
Oh, you had to be
there, Blitz. Yes.
I'm not The Blitz!
(person yawning)
Zoey?
Morning, Blitz!
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
NARRATOR:
Kids, you remember Zoey.
For the last two months,
she'd been making my life hell.
Thanks, guys!
Last night was amazing!
The Gentleman!
ALL:
The Gentle...
(all groan)
How could you,
my best friends in the world,
hang out with
my mortal enemy,
then let her sleep in the tub
where I clean myself?!
Sorry, Ted.
We can explain.
After you Blitzed out
last night...
I'm not The Blitz!
LILY:
Oh, my God...
That's Zoey!
That's Ted's enemy.
Which means
she's our enemy.
Let's take
this bitch down.
Huh? Huh?
Who's got your back?
Now let's have dinner!
Finish the story, Red.
Okay, well, we all
started brainstorming
ways to mess with her.
There were a lot of different
ideas kicking around.
And then I'm just going to leave
her there... buck-naked,
covered in candle wax,
tied to the bed.
Barney, I know that
Ted doesn't like that girl,
but that's a little extreme.
Wait-- Ted doesn't
like that girl?
Okay.
Wh...?
Well, I got it.
You see that silk scarf?
I'm going
to steal it.
Can I... help you?
Yeah. Yeah!
My name is Lily Aldrin.
I'm a friend of Ted Mosby's,
so you better...
You're Lily Aldrin?
The painter?!
Well, yeah.
You're amazing!
I bought a bunch of your
paintings online.
(gasps) That was you?! Yeah.
Oh! Thanks!
Look, none of us meant
for it to happen, but, well,
we had an awesome night
with her.
ALL:
The Gentleman!
(whooping, applause)
And then, the craziest thing
happened.
(cheering)
I missed a skateboarding dog?
Yeah, but that
wasn't the crazy part.
It wasn't?
Okay, Marshall.
Truth or dare?
Okay, awesome.
Well, Lily doesn't
let me do truths.
So, dare.
Okay.
I dare you to send
a picture of your junk
to a complete stranger.
(all laughing, gasping)
Best idea ever!
Worst idea ever!
My junk ended up in
some stranger's pocket.
If there phone was on vibrate,
I basically dry-humped them.
Ho, ho, ho, ho! Whoa!
Yay!
Yeah.
Okay.
Everybody shout out
random numbers.
Um.
4, 8...
15, 16, 23, 42!
And... send!
(cheering)
Wait. Blitz was there, too?
The Gentleman!
Oh, I was there
for the whole thing.
Something inside me
just said
"Grand Theft Auto"
can wait a night.
It was legen--
wait for Ted to leave,
'cause he's now The Blitz--
-- dary.
Legendary!
I'm not The Blitz!
I'm afraid you are, Ted.
You see, when you left
last night,
you changed
the course of Blitztory.
(cheering)
MYSTERIOUS VOICE:
Blitz...
(mysterious theme plays)
(gasps, chokes)
I'm finally free!
I mean, you have no idea
what I've missed
all these years:
The university
president's toupee
being snatched by a hawk
at graduation,
Zeppelin reuniting
at my cousin Ira's bar mitzvah,
countless nip-slips,
crotch shots,
shooting stars
and double rainbows.
I've missed them all!
Well, not anymore, Blitz.
My name's not Blitz.
My name is Steve!
Colors seem so bright now.
Thank you, Blitz.
What? No!
N- n-n-n-no! N-n-no!
I'm not The Blitz!
The only thing I missed
last night was my best friends
stabbing me in the back by
hanging out with my worst enemy.
Guys!
I hate Zoey!
That means you're supposed to
hate her, too!
Th-that's your rule, Lily!
I tried.
Tried?!
Lily, do you have any idea
how many people
I've blindly hated for you?
I hated Renée Zellweger
with a burning passion
for eight years,
only to discover
you meant Reese Witherspoon!
Hey, I will hate her
until I get my money back
for You, Me and Dupree!
That's Kate Hudson!
Oh, yeah.
That's who I hate.
Guys, we hate Kate Hudson.
No, we hate Zoey!
(grunts)
I'm so furious
at you all right now,
but it's Thanksgiving, and
I have a Turturkeykey to make.
And not that I'm The Blitz,
but could everyone please come
with me into the kitchen?
(all murmuring)
Okay, I'm, uh,
just gonna preheat the oven.
The oven.
Hey, Robin,
you should dance
on the oven.
(all agreeing, whooping)
ALL (chanting):
Make out with Zoey!
Make out...
Did they tell you about
the skateboarding dog?
It was awesome!
Great. So not only did
you guys betray me,
but you broke my oven
on Thanksgiving?
Full disclosure.
We also used all your butter,
greasing up Lily
so we could see how far we could
slide her down the hall.
But if it helps, I reached 4G.
It doesn't help. 4G?
Mm-hmm.
No.
What-What are we supposed
to do now?
This is
awesome!
I'm part of this!
Barney, I don't know
if the oven
is deep enough. Plus,
it's a display
made of cardboard.
Huh. I should probably
disconnect the gas.
Hey, just so
you guys know,
there was a tiny explosion
at the sewage treatment plant
across the street
from our apartment,
but I'm sure
it's fine by now.
This is awesome!
It's not awesome!
I think the smaller
turkey just tried
to crawl further
inside the bigger turkey.
Um...
Um... I'm have...
I'm having trouble breathing!
Mom keeps an extra
litter box in here.
There you go.
Good as new.
Oh. Hey, Ginger.
Ted, you're not
gonna like this,
but we do have one other option.
Hey, you guys
should come to my house
for Thanksgiving.
My husband always spends
it with his daughter,
so I'm going to be alone anyway.
Could we bring Ted?
It's Thanksgiving.
What the hell?
(group cheering)
No. Absolutely not.
Come on. Give her a chance.
Ted, you violated a dead turkey
with another dead turkey.
Don't let that be in vain.
Guys? Wait a minute.
Where's Barney?
(chuckles)
And here's the twist, Babaka.
Because Ted left early,
he's now The Blitz!
But Barney,
now you left the group.
Wouldn't that put you in danger
of becoming The Blitz yourself?
No. I c...
Because...
Step on it.
(laughing)
You missed it.
Oh, my goodness.
Our cab took
a wrong turn.
We were in the
Thanksgiving Day parade!
Tony Bennett passed Ted the mike
and he sang "Twist and Shout!"
But he's The Blitz.
No. I'm not The Blitz.
I'm The Bueller.
You know what this means.
You're The Blitz.
MYSTERIOUS VOICE:
Blitz...
Oh, God, no!
Life moves
pretty fast, Barney.
If you don't stop and
look around once in a while,
you might miss it.
Chicka-chicka!
Happy Thanksgiving!
Ted.
Zoey.
Best friend alert!
Okay, the Turturkeykey
is officially cooking.
Oh, God, that is disgusting!
Okay, guys,
that's starting to hurt.
No... no, Ted.
Random number guy just
sent me his wang back.
Wow.
You sent a wang out,
and you got a wang back.
It's a boom-a-wang.
Nice.
Thank you.
No, I meant the wang.
Barney, could you
get me some more ice?
Sure.
But... no one move
while I'm gone.
(whispering):
I'm scared.
You're safe.
It's okay to leave the room.
You have to actually
leave the building
for something cool to happen.
Thanks.
You're the only one
who's nice to me about this.
Okay, I got to test this.
(all yelling happily)
What happened?
You missed it!
Dude, you walked
out of the room,
the laws of physics stopped
and the laws of awesome tripled.
Aw, man!
You said I could leave the room!
I just wanted to see
something cool happen.
I'm sorry.
But I was on that island
for what seems like eternity.
I'm going to enjoy
things on the other side.
No! Y-You...
Robin, Robin.
I will pay you to be The Blitz.
$100! No-- $10,000.
No-- 60 bucks.
That's a lot of money
for someone like you.
Dude, The Blitz isn't something
that can be bought or sold.
Yeah, it's not like
Ted's integrity.
Oh, what was that?
I was distracted by
the four-caret diamond
your 53-year-old
husband bought you.
Facial!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a turturkeykey
to baste.
I'm coming
with you.
No... I baste alone.
Oh, I'm sure
you're a master baster, Ted.
Word play. Loving it.
But relax.
I've got a ton of sides
to heat up
since my plans fell through.
Who canceled? Your coven?
Coven. Group of witches.
Boom.
Yeah. They were worn out from
putting that spell on your hair.
Oh! Serve returned.
Are you happy?
You're ruining Thanksgiving.
Well, you're not exactly
who I thought
I'd be spending
Thanksgiving with, either.
God, I'm so happy to be here.
My face hurts from smiling.
Oh...
I'm sorry, Lily.
I'm just never going
to like that woman.
Ted, give her a chance.
Enemies can't become friends.
Yes, they can.
Right, guys?
(all murmuring in agreement)
No, no, no.
You guys can't be objective.
You still feel guilty
about last night.
Well, let's get
an outside opinion.
Who are we gonna--
"Dear Wang Guy..."
Oh.
"Can enemies
ever be friends?
Just wondering."
Really?
Wang Guy?
We're asking Wang Guy?
He's bold and uninhibited,
so why not?
And guys, you know what?
For fun, why don't we ask him
what he does for a living?
Wouldn't that be fun?
Just ask...
Aww.
You've got a little crush
on Wang Guy, don't you?
What? No. Shut up.
I hate him.
(laughs)
(cell phone chimes)
Oh, look.
We got an answer.
Here it is.
"Yes, enemies
can become friends.
"Remember what Gandhi said.
'Be the change you want
to see in the world.'"
Uh, did Wang Guy
just quote Gandhi?
(laughing):
That is amazing.
And I was here for it.
Now Zoey is The Blitz.
Ha, ha!
(weak laugh)
Burn on her.
Come on, man.
Don't be that Blitz.
I'm not any Blitz!
You're The Blitz!
You're all The Blitz!
I slept with that cute
Indian girl who cuts my hair!
What does that have
to do with anything?
Nothing! I just forgot
to brag about
it before!
Guys, despite the wit and wisdom
of Wang Guy,
Zoey and I are never going
to be friends.
We're just here for
her oven and that's it.
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
Did you do that on purpose?
What? No. It was
an accident.
Oh, yeah. Well,
like this is.
Oh, great. Real mature.
Yeah, well,
you started it.
(Ted and Zoey shouting)
Just stop it!
God, can't you two just
stop fighting for one day?
Like, when
the Roadrunner and the Coyote
clocked out
and had a beer together?
Or-Or-Or Tom and Jerry
shared a cup of coffee.
Lily, those are
cartoon characters,
and I'm pretty sure
you're making up episodes.
And if Zoey is a
cartoon character,
she's Cinderella's
evil stepmother!
Oh, get out.
All of you, out!
But it's Thanksgiving.
And I'm a part of it.
Out!
Wait... Where's Barney?
Hey, guys, the most amazing
thing just happened
to me in that other roo...
Aw, man.
I don't get it.
Why'd she just
kick us out like that?
NARRATOR:
And then the cab driver said
the last thing any
of us wanted to hear.
Where to?
(sighs)
I guess we're going home.
Yeah. I don't know
where that is.
(sighs)
Lily, where'd you get that?
Oh.
When Zoey booted us,
it made me want to steal
something of hers again.
Apartment full of designer
labels, and what do I grab?
"Happy Turkey Day, Hannah.
Love, Zoey."
I wonder who Hannah is.
Hey, you guys should come
to my house for Thanksgiving.
My husband always
spends it with his daughter,
so I'm going
to be alone, anyway.
Well, you're not exactly
who I thought
I'd be spending
Thanksgiving with, either.
And if Zoey is a
cartoon character,
she's Cinderella's
evil stepmother!
Get out!
All of you, out!
We have to go back to Zoey's.
You gotta throw me
some addresses, buddy.
(Zoey gasps)
Oh, God.
What are you doing here?
Barney let us in.
Barney was here?
I was walking around half-naked.
Aw, man!
Wait. Which half?
Look, I'm sorry your
stepdaughter didn't want
to spend
Thanksgiving with you.
How do you know that?
I just do.
It must be tough.
It was the first Thanksgiving
Hannah agreed to spend with me,
and then at the last minute,
she changed her mind.
She hates my guts.
I get that.
(chuckles)
Uh, you should
hang on to this.
You can give it
to her next year.
Yeah...
Right.
Next year.
Hey, you never know.
People don't
stay enemies forever.
And that's the story of how
Zoey and I became friends.
ALL:
Cheers.
Before we eat,
we should take a group picture
and send it to Wang Guy.
Ooh. Oh. Great idea.
All right.
Okay.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
(shutter clicks)
Ted, that is the
best-looking turturkeykey
I have ever seen.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Let's just hope it tastes
as good as it looks.
NARRATOR:
It didn't.
It tasted wrong.
Oops.
We forgot to light the candles.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
And just as Barney looked away,
it happened.
ALL:
The Gentleman!
What happened?
I saw it!
Aw, come on, Blitz.
Now it's just sad.
Aw, man.
Oh, go ahead.
I forgot my jacket.
Oh, hold the door!
(elevator bell dings)
(fabric rips, woman screams)
BARNEY:
Thank you, God!
Aw, man!
MYSTERIOUS VOICE:
Blitz.
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net