Kids, in the fall of 2010, our friends
Stuart and Claudia had a baby,
and Marshall and Lily were the first
to visit the happy new parents.
So, have you guys
landed on a name yet?
We're trying, but it's tougher than
you think. You see, I like "Tiffany."
And I don't want my daughter
to have a whore's name.
- That's my mother's name.
- I know.
I got it. How'bout we name the baby
after you... "Frigid Shrew."
That's good.
Let's call her "Vodka."
Then at least we know you'd hold her
tight and never let her go!
Don't knock the vodka.
Wouldn't have a kid without it.
Stuart, you are so...
That's not gonna be us, right?
I mean,
how hard can it be to name a baby?
Right?
I mean, just look at her.
She's clearly a...
- Lisa.
- Emily.
- Emily?!
- Lisa?!
Team Who's this fucking mother?
Synchronisation:
JoJo, Karim, Kyros, MiniBen314
Adaptation:
Dark_Chii, H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture: MiniBen314, Titou
6x06 - Baby Talk (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
I made a list of awesome baby names.
Starting at the top: number one...
I'm gonna stop you
right here, Marshall.
You name a chubby
white kid "LeBron,"
and he's the one getting
stuffed in the basketball hoop.
Then I'm also crossing off,
"Shaquille"...
"Hakeem,"
and "Dikembe."
What about "Rob"?
"Rob"?
Why not?
Hey, Rob. What are you gonna make?
A turkey?
Honka, honka!
Not "Rob."
How about "Ryan"?
Not "Ryan."
"Johnny?"
Hey, where's the goldfish?
Not "Johnny."
Or "Gil."
"Jeremy."
Definitely not "Jeremy."
His stuff was so derivative.
Well, I mean, geez, Lily.
Well, whatever you do, do not
name your baby "Becky," right?
Why? What?
Becky. My new co-anchor?
Don't you guys ever watch the show?
- I really try.
- Our DVR won't recognize it
as a television program.
I watched.
Robin insisted I confirm
how "awful" Becky is,
so last night I checked it out.
Peace talks in the region
have been described as "productive."
Becky?
Last night, in Staten Island,
a taco cart owner
was robbed at gunpoint.
That's so sad.
Becky, we're journalists.
We can't get emotional
about the news, we...
They stole all his money and then
pelted him with his own taco meat!
Who would do that?
If you read the story,
we might find out.
Can I do this one, about the horse?
I love horseys.
The horse died.
Guys!
This news is all really sad.
Okay, no holds barred...
What'd you think of Becky?
- I thought she was charming.
- You, too?
Can somebody please explain to me
why the little girl act works on men?
Long or short version?
Short version.
Who's your daddy?
You know, when you think about that,
that phrase is really creepy.
No, it's not. It's fun.
Here, watch this.
Who's your daddy?
Let me get this straight.
So, in this scenario,
because you make such
sweet love to Lily,
she is now your daughter.
No, she is not my daughter.
I'm just...
her daddy.
- That is disgusting.
- Exactly. And it's not like
the opposite would work. There's no way
a guy could pick up a girl, going around
- talking like a little boy.
- Challenge accepted.
I, Barney Stinson,
will pick up a girl
whilst talking like a little boy.
Here's my list of baby names.
What about "Tara"?
Not "Tara." Tara was
the hottest girl in my high school.
We were all, like,
obsessed with her.
We didn't just talk about her
and fantasize about her...
We wrote songs about her.
Tara
Your booty is so smooth
And I hope this isn't rude
But I want to get up on it.
Not "Tara."
What about "Esther"?
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Coming up on the main stage,
give it up for Esther!
That prime rib was surprisingly good,
but it's 10:30 in the morning.
I don't need to see a lady
get naked and dance.
Esther gets naked.
But she doesn't dance.
Then what does she do?
Sweet mother nature!
That was my card!
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Give it up for Esther!
Not "Esther."
I need a drink. Ted? Ted?
Your list is entirely boy names.
You do realize there's roughly a 50%
chance of you having a daughter, right?
Honestly, I've never thought
about having a girl.
I don't wannna think
Tara, Esther...
can you imagine being one
of those girls' dads?
Marshall's daughter
Your booty
Your booty's so smooth.
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
On the main stage,
give it up for Marshall's daughter.
He screwed up my childhood.
That's why I do this.
I have no idea how
to raise a daughter!
What if she makes bad choices? I mean,
what if she winds up dating some...
Papa, I want you to meet
my new boyfriend.
Hey, bro.
Thanks for making such a hottie.
Who's your daddy?
You are,
'cause of all the sex we have.
I don't want a girl.
I just want a little boy.
It's not what it sounds like, folks.
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
Is that you?
You're a little too close
to the camera. Can you back up a bit?
How's this?
Every time.
Can you just sit
in front of the computer
like normal human beings?
Perfect! Perfect.
What's up, shooter?
To be honest, I'm getting a freaked out
about the idea of having a daughter.
You two probably aren't the right people
to talk to about this. You had all boys.
Well, that was just dumb luck.
Hey, honey,
would you get me a brewski
from out of the shed?
Sure. You want anything, Marshall?
I'm in a computer, Mom.
Yeah, all boys.
Total co-winky-dink.
It was no co-winky-dink.
Since the Viking age, the Eriksen men
have passed down ancient secrets
for conceiving boys.
Number one, avoid lemons.
They're baby girl fertilizer.
No offense, Dad, but I doubt there's
any scientific data to support...
"I doubt there's any
scientific data to support..."
I had all sons.
Your grandfather had all sons.
Your great-grandfather had all sons.
Scoreboard!
Who you gonna listen to?
Me? Or "scientific data"?
Members of the G-8
convened today in Vienna
to discuss plans to fight
climate change by re... What?
Ask me what I did yesterday.
Tthis is our news segment, okay?
Nobody cares what you did yesterday.
Lighten up, Robin.
What'd you do, sweetheart?
Well, I'm new in town and
don't know many people.
But yesterday,
I met the sweetest man,
who took me on a tour of the city.
Guys, New York is kind of cool.
Okay, back to the G-8 conference.
Hello?
Mike, can I get in the shot?
Fantastic.
Then this cutie patootie took me
to this bar called MacLaren's,
- right underneath his apartment.
- Wait...
Did you go out with Ted Mosby?
Guys, I went out with
Robin's roommate.
I saw her bedroom.
She's a messy Bessie.
In other news, later today,
a Manhattan architect
gets punched in the throat.
Of all the women in New York,
you had to go out
with an eight-year-old girl?
Not what it sounds like.
You know that I hate her.
How could you go out with this girl?
It wasn't a date.
She came over to the apartment
looking for you.
I made Robin my famous
chocolate chip cookies.
But instead of chocolate chips,
I used gummie bears.
A spider!
Let me guess: she acted
like a helpless little girl,
and you stepped in as the big,
strong man.
I don't know if that's totally true.
It's okay, darlin'.
Poor spider.
Spiders gotta die,
so trees can grow.
Then I held her tight
and told her
it was all gonna be okay.
By the way, I think
I only wounded the spider.
It crawled off into my bedroom.
Is that why you slept
on the couch last night?
I slept.
I'm dying out here.
Talking like a little boy
is not working with the ladies.
Wow, lady.
You got some tig ol'bitties!
Gosh!
Your body's a perfect...
this many.
Do you want to wrestle
with our special bathing suit places?
Come on!
I need two seconds, baby.
I know you think that's a compliment,
but I'd rather you took your time.
I'll be right back.
Ancient Norse wisdom tells us that,
to sire a son,
you must do three things right
before you lay with your maiden.
First, eat pickled herring.
Eat it!
This is ridiculous.
Gentlemen, on the main stage,
throwing her life away,
give it up for Marshall's daughter!
Who's your granddaddy?
That guy.
Want to have a three-way
with me and my imaginary friend?
His name's Otis.
Want to come to my house
and play telephone?
I got the string, you got the cans.
I wet myself!
Will you change me?
Can't blame her on that one.
Guys...
I have some terrible news.
I,
Barney Stinson,
can't pick up a girl whilst
talking like a little boy.
Challenge forfeited.
- We don't care about this.
- No one challenged you,
I'm sorry.
Gerard, what's with that shirt?
Nobody could pick up
a chick wearing that thing.
Challenge accept...
I'm glad that's over.
It was creepy watching Barney
talk like a little kid.
But you find it irresistible
when Becky does?
I don't get it.
The Ted that I went out with was
attracted to the kind of woman
who could use a steak knife
without supervision.
For your information, Becky doesn't like
steak, she likes "spasghetti".
Spaghetti.
And more importantly,
she makes me feel needed.
Needed?
She makes training
wheels feel needed.
It's nice to feel needed.
And you know what?
It's not a feeling guys
get when they're with you.
Son...
Viking lore tells us that
to ensure the continuation
of your noble male lineage...
get a big bowl of ice
and dunk your man
sack right in there!
You two and your football.
Now get in there,
point Lily due north
and make me a grandson!
When we were dating,
I didn't make you feel needed?
Come on! You always took
charge of everything.
I got this.
- This okay? Am I hurting y...
- I got this.
Someone's trying to break in.
Call the cops.
I got this.
Did that bother you?
Yeah. It's nice to be needed.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
It's Becky.
She's trapped in a revolving door.
I got this.
Let's make a baby!
You're packing snowballs,
and your breath smells like a fart.
You know what's hotter?
If we face this way.
Ooh, we're bad.
Baby, why are you facing me north?
You're trying to make us have a boy.
I can ex...
How do you know?
What are you doing with lemons?
Baby girl fertilizer!
You're trying to have a girl!
You are trying to have a girl.
All my least favorite students
have been boys.
So I Googled "how to make a girl",
some really weird stuff came up,
but I found this conception website
that said you should...
point south
at the moment of conception...
eat a lemon...
and heat up your lady parts
to a balmy 105 degrees.
That's not bad.
How could you do...
exactly the same thing I did?
You're supposed to be the sane one.
See that?
Another boy expecting a woman
to clean up his mistakes.
That's why girls
are better than boys.
Why creepy kids in a horror movie
are always little girls?
Or twin girls, who speak...
in unison.
What about Chucky?
A) He was a doll;
B) He was possessed
by an adult serial killer;
and C) How could you bring
up Chucky right before bed?
When we were dating,
did I make you feel needed?
No, I didn't feel
like you needed me at all.
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
Wwhere are you...
That's a compliment.
You are the least needy woman
I've ever met, that's awesome.
No guy's gonna say
"Who's your daddy?" to you.
You're your own daddy.
And mommy.
And weird survivalist uncle
who lives in a cabin with a gun
blaming the government.
That is what makes you the most...
amazing, strong...
independent woman I've ever banged.
There's something
I wanted to ask you,
and I don't really know
how to say it so... here goes.
Who's the crazy chick in the apron?
Someone naughty
left his toys on the floor
and needs to be spanked
on his tushy-tush.
I'm in "twubble."
You did it?
How?
Last night, after admitting defeat,
I just let myself go.
That looks so good.
Can I have some?
It's my ice cream,
you can't have any.
Someone needs to teach you
how to share.
Who's your mommy?
Challenge completed!
Can you get her out?
I'm scared.
I got this.
So you finally agreed on a name?
The other night she ran
a really high fever.
We rushed her to the ER
at 3:00 in the morning,
but they wouldn't admit her
without a name.
Right then,
we realized
how stupid we were being.
We looked at each other
and we just knew.
Our baby's name is...
Esther.
Beautiful.
We're idiots.
Names and gender, it's like...
it's some way of giving ourselves
the illusion that we have any control.
I just want a healthy,
happy, 12-pound...
Ten-pound?
- Eight-pound?
- I guess,
but you're writing checks
my vagina can't cash.
I love you.
And I'm gonna love the crap
out of whatever baby we have.
Me, too.
You know what?
We should just think of a name
that's good for either a girl or a boy.
Like...
Jamie.
We just named our baby.
Not Jamie.
Shoe's untied. I got it.
This is over.
www.tvsubtitles.net