Kids, there are two big days
in any love story:
the day you meet
the girl of your dreams,
and the day you marry her.
Nice. Where'd you get this?
Stashed a cooler behind the pulpit.
- Beer be with you.
- And also with you.
Man, this is what church
has been missing.
- Dude, you fixed church.
- You're welcome, God.
Nervous?
No. I'm just hoping it doesn't rain.
Why? Do I look nervous?
Look at your beer.
You do that when you're nervous.
It's a sad day in New York, Ted.
A sad day, indeed.
Do you know what I saw
on my way in here?
A girl...
in a sweater.
And you know what that means.
The season of exposed skin is over.
Exactly.
Gone are the tank tops.
Gone are the cute little skirts.
Gone are the sun dresses.
The sun dresses!
I don't think
I can make it another eight months
with no sun dresses.
- I have to grade these papers.
- I'm sorry. I'll let you work.
But first, a riddle:
What piece of women's attire
most stokes a man's desire?
A sun dress.
Correct.
What lightweight outfit,
pink or white,
makes the front of my slacks
abnormally tight?
- I really have to get this done.
- Of course.
"Sun dress," by the way.
What are you nervous about?
Tell me...
- What flowing cotton frock...
- I'll tell you. Just...
There's a girl sitting at the bar.
- Don't look!
- I want to see a pretty girl.
Okay, you can look.
Just be cool for once.
I'll be cool.
You got your beer label
in a bunch over nothing.
Listen to your Uncle Barney.
You have no reason to be nervous.
None whatsoever.
And I'm going to tell you why
in one word.
- And what's that word?
- Dibs!
Who's this fucking mother Team
Synchronisation :
JoJo, Karim, Kyros, MiniBen314
Adaptation :
Dark_Chii, H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture : MiniBen314, Titou
6x01 - Big Days (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
You can't call dibs
on a girl I've been sitting here
thinking about maybe talking
to eventually at some point.
You never called dibs.
Dibs were implied.
Implied dibs?
You are spitting
on the grave of Sir Walter Dibs,
inventor of the dib.
It was 1652...
The SS Dibs was lost...
I don't have time
for a fake history lesson,
so I'll keep this simple.
You go over there and talk to that girl,
I will see you in court.
And who's gonna represent you?
Dibs on Marshall!
- Damn it.
- Where is Marshall anyway?
Uncle Marshall
and Aunt Lily had recently decided
to take a swing
at starting a family.
Tonight was their first at-bat.
I'm almost ready to leave.
Let's see the checklist. Candles?
- Check.
- Music to set the mood?
Check.
Music for when
we're actually doing it?
You know what?
To hell with your dibs.
I'm going over there and talking to her.
Be my guest.
Fall in love with her. Get married.
Just know this:
When I step up to make my toast
as your best man...
- Marshall would probably be...
- As your best man...
Ladies and Gentlemen...
I...
had dibs.
Tell me this isn't true.
I had implied dibs.
You've humiliated me!
I had no idea.
You have to know that.
You're the victim here.
We both are.
Let's get out.
Or, we could just do it right here.
Fine.
Have at it.
Exercise your dibs.
She's got her shields up.
She's reading a book.
At a bar.
That book might as well be called:
Are You There, Barney?
It's Me, Horny.
That is not
what "shields up" looks like.
That is what "shields up"
looks like.
Move.
'Sup, dudes?
Fries?
Good God, woman.
You're a disgrace.
No fries for this guy.
Seriously, I love you, but it's like
you have squiggly cartoon odor lines
coming off of you right now.
Just cut her some slack, okay?
She just went through a breakup.
With hygiene?
No, with Don.
A few months earlier...
- Here, have some tea.
- Thanks.
Robin, I am here for you.
Whatever you need.
Okay, about that.
Ted, listen.
I know myself pretty well.
Some time over the next few months,
I'm going to want to sleep with you.
And when that happens,
you have to try to say no.
Try?
I will absolutely say no.
Our friendship is too important.
Maybe I wasn't clear enough.
I will come at you
with everything I've got.
I will stalk you
like the lioness stalks the gazelle,
careful, patient,
deadly.
And if you let your guard down
for so much as a second,
as sure as you were born,
I will hump your brains out.
I'm ready to have sex now.
It was a tough summer, but I think
our girl's been a real trooper.
She's...
Is this a Cheeto?
No, we ran out of Cheetos last week.
Yeah, it's a Cheeto.
Dibs.
You're exquisite.
You must let me paint you.
What do you think?
The girl sitting at the bar, shields up?
Totes, toots.
She's here on a date.
She brought the book
because she got here early,
and she also wants to impress
the guy she's meeting.
Girls like to come across all
classy and smart, you know?
This?
What you're doing right now?
I'm getting a "de-rection."
How'd it go?
You pregnant yet?
Nope!
So, here's what happened.
I was at home, waiting for Marshall.
How was your day?
Don't answer. No time.
Bedroom. No time.
Floor. No time.
- Against this wall!
- Marshall. Wait.
A big package just arrived.
- Yeah, it did.
- No.
It's a real package from your dad.
That's a little weird,
but yeah, it is.
Look!
A bassinet?
Oh, my...
He must've made it in his wood shop.
Wasn't that sweet of him?
Isn't that sweet?
You told your dad we're trying
to have a baby?
Of course I did.
I tell my dad everything.
My dad is my best friend.
We have been looking forward
to this magical, special night
for two weeks now.
And, sweetie, during that time,
I have been...
How do I put this delicately?
Saving all my love for you.
I have read 11 books on conception.
I have cut out
alcohol, caffeine and sugar.
I take my temperature every hour.
But good for you
for not playing with yourself.
- I feel you, buddy.
- Don't even touch me, dude.
It's been two weeks.
I'm, like, a light breeze away
from having a big problem.
Seriously.
Okay, I'm better now.
- What's this going to cost me?
- Excuse me?
I want to buy your dibs.
Two... hundred...
and fifty thousand dollars.
20 bucks.
But I...
- Can I go smell her first?
- No.
All right.
Wish me luck.
Now kids, remember how I told you
about a girl named Cindy?
How I went on one date
and it ended...
- Get out.
- badly?
- How are you?
- Good.
- What the hell are you doing?
- That girl she's talking to?
I dated her.
That sucks!
And dibs.
So you went on one date
with one of her friends.
It's not necessarily a big deal.
Did it end on bad terms?
Hi Cindy!
Well, I guess
you just got to move on.
It's not like you have a shot
with Ready McGee over there, right?
Then I remembered.
Cindy had a roommate.
A roommate
I only caught a glimpse of...
But a roommate who,
by every indication,
was something very special.
Was it possible?
Could this be the girl
attached to that ankle?
I got to see her ankles.
You're one of those?
God, I swear, one in five guys...
We kind of had a plan tonight,
remember?
Candles? Banjo?
Who else did you tell?
Did you tell anyone at the office?
Start the music.
Can you dig it?
Take it to the hole, Eriksen!
Sink that putt, big fuzz!
Put a pillow under her lower back.
It helps facilitate conception, bro!
I may have mentioned it in passing
to a couple of colleagues at work.
I'm sorry about that,
but you know what?
I gottaa be able to tell my dad.
Your dad is the last person
you should tell!
The man is too involved
in our lives!
It's like,
every time the phone rings...
Lily, Marvin Eriksen.
I noticed you hadn't changed
your last name yet.
- No, I'm gonna...
- So, don't worry. I called the DMV,
I called your Amex, I got
that process started for you.
Lily, Marvin Eriksen.
I understand
you and Marshall have been fighting.
Well, let me tell you what works
for me and the missus.
Frilly French undies
and a box of wine.
You might wanna try pickles
on that sandwich.
Pickles would have helped
that sandwich!
The man has no boundaries.
And I just can't procreate
under these conditions!
Well, you know what? I've already
told him, so the damage is done.
So, call him and tell him
we decided not to have a baby.
Okay, so you just...
You want me to give my dad a stroke?
Only if you wanna give
this a stroke.
That's ridiculous. Lily,
there is no way that I would ever...
Okay, everyone needs
to shut up so that I can think!
- They're talking to a guy now.
- What kinda guy?
- A cheesy guy or a cool guy?
- A cheesy guy. Don't worry.
That guy is cool.
His hair's all cool,
he's got a cool belt.
That guy is cheesy,
and if you think he's not cheesy,
then you're cheesy, too,
and now I want something cheesy.
Who's feeling nachos?
Look at you, Robin.
You're jealous.
- Jealous?
- Yeah, jealous,
because she's got it,
and you've lost it.
I have not lost it.
You lost it.
I still have it.
I know exactly where it is,
and I can go get it
whenever I want.
Robin, girls are
like cartons of milk.
Each one has a hotness
expiration date,
and you've hit yours.
I'm not saying the occasional
guy won't still open the fridge,
pick you up, give a sniff,
shrug and take a sip anyway.
But it's all downhill from here.
I don't have to take this.
But I do have to take this.
So you just want me to call my dad
- and tell him we're not having a baby?
- That's about the size of it.
Out of curiosity,
when do we tell him about the baby?
We'll tell him about the baby
when there's a baby to tell him about.
So, he just gets no notice?
He just walks
into his boss's office, and says,
"I just had a grandson.
I'm gonna be out for three months."
Out for three months?
He and my mom are coming
to live with us when the baby's born.
- We talked about this.
- No, we didn't.
I meant, me and my dad.
You know what, Marshall? Why
don't you have a baby with your dad?
Why don't you have a baby
with your butt?
What?
I can't think straight!
Why do you have to wear that shirt?
This is not how I thought
this night was gonna go!
God, this sucks!
Do you think she saw me?
Hi, Ted!
Yeah, she definitely saw you.
Can I see you for a minute...
in private?
Yeah, sure. I mean,
how could that not be fun?
If I don't come back,
tell my mom I love her.
Will do. And dibs.
Barney, am I crazy?
Marshall talks to his dad
way too much, right?
You don't want my opinion on that.
Why not?
If I had my dad's number,
I would never not be
on the phone with him.
That was really...
A hottie with a body!
- Brief.
- No. Lily, look.
You saucy little minx.
You sundressed up.
14 seconds!
14 seconds, and already
some dingdong is stepping up,
thinking he can get
some of this broke off.
I... still... got... it.
All right, buddy,
you proved my point. Now scram.
Nice belt, by the way.
Robin, you do look super hot.
- Do I?
- Yeah, you do.
Thanks.
I braced myself for what was next:
rage, fury, a savage bitting.
Thank you.
After things didn't
work out with us,
I got really sad for a while.
Then I realized,
you're not what I wanted,
and I'm not what you wanted.
I'm sorry I was such a jerk.
I feel like I should
make it up to you somehow.
Buy you a beer
or Yankees tickets, or...
Or set me up with
one of your friends.
No, I'm kidding.
That would be weird.
No, it wouldn't. would it?
Any one of those three.
Whichever's easiest and right nearby.
And not the beer.
- I should get back.
- Totally.
Come say good-bye before you leave.
- Say good-bye before you leave?
- Her words exactly.
Dude, you are so in.
That is so awesome.
A high five doesn't cut.
High six!
She didn't see this.
- Good. That was lame.
- Let's never do that again.
What? Lily what?
Are there more members of my family
that you want to crap all over?
- Here's the thing.
- Sorry. Hold on.
Just...
It's my dad.
Lily, it's my dad, okay?
I love him, and if he calls me,
I'm gonna answer the phone!
I know it's late,
but I just had to call.
- How'd it go?
- This is...
Did you do everything the books say?
Put the pillow under her back?
- I'm in the middle of something.
- Did it feel like a boy?
Huh? You can tell.
He's insane.
My dad is insane.
I'm so sorry.
He's just...
He's so...
enthusiastic.
It's ridiculous, you know?
Who's like that?
You.
You're like that.
You and your dad both care so much.
It's why women fall in love
with the Eriksen men to begin with.
But right now,
it's a lot of pressure.
- I'm not trying to pressure you...
- What if I can't have a baby?
That could happen.
I could totally let you down.
Has that thought
not occurred to you?
Not even for one second.
Not having a baby would suck,
but the idea of you letting me down,
that's impossible.
That would be like aliens landing.
That's a bad example,
because that could happen.
It probably already has.
I saw this episode...
All right.
I'm doing this.
I am going over there.
Wish me luck.
Nothing in this life
quite compares to the sweet,
terrifying exhilaration
of making your move.
When you just put it all
on the line and go for it.
And that night, by golly,
Cindy went for it.
So no, kids,
that girl wasn't your mother.
She ended up being
someone else's mother.
In fact, they both did.
Like I said, she's here on a date.
So that was not the day
I met your mother.
The day I met your mother
was the day of a wedding.
Maybe I'm a little nervous.
- Dude, it's just a wedding toast.
- I know. I want it to be great.
- I want this whole day to be great.
- It will be.
Best man?
You're being summoned.
Geez, what now?
Ted, seriously, relax.
Everything's...
- Okay, and it's raining.
- Yeah. You were saying?
You didn't happen to bring
an umbrella, did you?
I didn't bring an umbrella.
Everyone told us that
it might take a while, but...
we thought we might be
the exception to the rule.
Anyways, we're getting back
on that horse. I mean,
feeling good about the future.
Obviously, this goes without saying but,
you won't tell Lily about any of this?
www.tvsubtitles.net