Kids, in the fall of 2010,
I was hosting my first Thanksgiving.
And I wanted it to be unforgettable.
Instead of stuffing,
I'm going to fill the turkey with...
a slightly smaller turkey.
It's called a Turturkeykey!
A Turturkeykey?
Yeah, I was there for the "insertion."
He used shoehorns.
I'll be having sides.
Your loss.
It's dead in here.
I'm gonna call it a little early.
No! You can't go now.
It's the night before Thanksgiving.
College chicks are back in town.
Their moms made a snide comment
about the weight they gained.
They called her a bitch,
but deep down, they know she's right.
They're about to walk through that door,
where we will be waiting
with some light beer
and some rock hard approval.
What up?
You don't want to bail early, man.
You could become "The Blitz".
Blitz was a guy we knew in college.
Sadly, he was cursed.
Well, I'm calling it a little early.
You sure?
We got big plans.
Remember how last week
we fired up a sandwich,
and we listened to Pink Floyd
while watching The Wizard of Oz?
Tonight,
we're doing the same thing,
only with "Weird Al" Yankovic's
Greatest Hits
and Apocalypse Now.
We'll see what happens.
Nah, it's "Kraft/Croft night",
mac and cheese and Tomb Raider.
Biz-zow!
Every time Blitz left a place,
something amazing happened.
I'm sorry.
I thought this was my room.
Completely naked!
And the movie was awesome.
When Brando first appeared,
"Weird Al" launched
right into Eat It.
And over the years,
"The Curse of The Blitz" continued.
Well, I'm gonna call it.
I just got Madden 2K1
and I can't stop thinking about it.
See you later!
Okay, later!
Tap's broke! Can't turn 'em off!
Free beer for everyone!
You know what?
Go ahead.
Leave early to do something lame.
Just don't blame us
if you become "The Blitz".
First of all,
there's nothing lame
about brining a Turturkeykey,
copyright pending.
And secondly,
I don't believe
"The Curse of The Blitz" is real.
Kids, I'd bet to regret those words.
The "Curse of Blitz" could be passed
from one person to the next,
at any moment.
Blitz had gotten the curse from Jerry
Windheim, back in freshman year,
who got it years before that
from Davey Beaterman.
The original "Blitz", Matt Blitz,
was a guy who went to Wesleyan
back in the '60s.
He dropped out
right before the school went co-ed.
And then, Thanksgiving morning...
What the hell happened here?
Morning, "Blitz"!
Let's get one thing straight, okay?
I am not "The Blitz".
My Blitzy lies over the ocean
My Blitzy lies over the sea
So bring back my Blitzy...
Please stop.
Okay, fine.
to me.
The Gentleman!
Wait!
What's that?
You had to be there, Blitz.
I'm not "The Blitz"!
Morning, Blitz!
Team Who's this fucking mother ?
Synchronisation :
Kyros, MiniBen314, Strex
Adaptation :
Dark_Chii, H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture : MiniBen314, Titou
6x10 - Blitzgiving (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
Kids, you remember Zoey.
For the last two months,
she'd been making my life hell.
Thanks, guys!
Last night was amazing!
The Gentleman!
The Gentle...
How could you?
My best friends in the world,
hang out with my mortal enemy,
then let her sleep in the tub
where I clean myself!
Sorry, Ted. We can explain.
- After you Blitzed out last night...
- I'm not "The Blitz"!
My God.
That's Zoey!
That's Ted's enemy.
Which means she's our enemy.
Let's take this bitch down.
Who's got your back?
Now let's have dinner!
Finish the story, Red.
Okay, well,
we all started brainstorming
ways to mess with her.
There were a lot of different ideas.
And then I'm just
gonna leave her there...
butt-naked, covered in candle wax,
tied to the bed.
I know that Ted
doesn't like that girl, but,
that's a little extreme.
Wait, Ted doesn't like that girl?
I got it.
You see that silk scarf?
I'm gonna steal it.
Can I help you?
My name is Lily Aldrin.
I'm a friend of Ted Mosby's,
so you better...
You're Lily Aldrin? The painter?!
You're amazing! I bought
a bunch of your paintings online.
That was you?!
None of us meant
for it to happen, but, well,
we had an awesome night with her.
The Gentleman!
And then,
the craziest thing happened.
I missed a skateboarding dog?
Yeah,
but that wasn't the crazy part.
It wasn't?
Truth or dare?
Awesome.
Well, Lily doesn't let me do truths.
So, dare.
I dare you
to send a picture of your junk
to a complete stranger.
Best idea ever!
Worst idea ever!
My junk ended up
in some stranger's pocket.
If there phone was on vibrate,
I basically dry-humped them.
Everybody shout out random numbers.
4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42!
And... send!
Wait. Blitz was there, too?
The Gentleman!
I was there for the whole thing.
Something inside me just said
Grand Theft Auto can wait a night.
It was legen...
Wait for Ted to leave,
cause he's now The Blitz...
... dary. Legendary!
I'm not The Blitz!
I'm afraid you are, Ted.
You see, when you left last night,
you changed the course of Blitztory.
Blitz...
I'm finally free!
I mean, you have no idea
what I've missed all these years:
The university president's toupee being
snatched by a hawk at graduation,
Zeppelin reuniting
at my cousin Ira's bar mitzvah,
countless nip-slips, crotch shots,
shooting stars and double rainbows.
I've missed them all!
Not anymore, Blitz.
My name's not Blitz.
My name is Steve!
Colors seem so bright now.
- Thank you, Blitz.
- What?
I'm not The Blitz! The only thing
I missed last night was my best friends
stabbing me in the back by
hanging out with my worst enemy.
Guys!
I hate Zoey!
That means you're supposed to
hate her, too! That's your rule, Lily!
I tried.
Tried?!
Lily, do you have any idea
how many people
I've blindly hated for you?
I hated Renée Zellweger
with a burning passion
for eight years,
only to discover
you meant Reese Witherspoon!
I will hate her until I get my money
back for You, Me and Dupree!
That's Kate Hudson!
Yeah. That's who I hate.
Guys, we hate Kate Hudson.
We hate Zoey!
I'm so furious at you all
right now, but,
it's Thanksgiving,
and I have a Turturkeykey to make.
And not that I'm The Blitz,
but could everyone please
come with me into the kitchen?
Okay, I'm...
just gonna preheat the oven.
The oven.
You should dance on the oven.
Make out with Zoey!
Did they tell you
about the skateboarding dog?
It was awesome!
Great.
So not only did you guys betray me,
but you broke my oven
on Thanksgiving?
Full disclosure.
We also used all your butter,
greasing up Lily so we could see how far
we could slide her down the hall.
But if it helps, I reached 4G.
It doesn't help. 4G?
What are we supposed to do now?
This is awesome!
I'm part of this!
I don't know if the oven
is deep enough. Plus,
it's a display made of cardboard.
I should probably
disconnect the gas.
Just so you guys know,
there was a tiny explosion
at the sewage treatment plant
across the street from our apartment,
but, I'm sure it's fine by now.
- This is awesome!
- It's not awesome!
I think the smaller turkey
just tried to crawl further inside
the bigger turkey.
I'm have...
I'm having trouble breathing!
Mom keeps
an extra litter box in here.
There you go.
Good as new.
Hey, Ginger.
Ted, you're not gonna like this,
but we do have one other option.
Hey, you guys should come
to my house for Thanksgiving.
My husband always spends it with his
daughter, so I'm gonna be alone anyway.
Could we bring Ted?
It's Thanksgiving.
What the hell?
Absolutely not.
Come on. Give her a chance.
You violated a dead turkey
with another dead turkey.
Don't let that be in vain.
Guys? Wait a minute.
Where's Barney?
And here's the twist, Babaka.
Because Ted left early,
he's now The Blitz!
But Barney, now you left the group.
Wouldn't that put you in danger
of becoming The Blitz yourself?
No. I c...
Because...
Step on it.
You missed it.
Our cab took a wrong turn.
We were
in the Thanksgiving Day parade!
Tony Bennett passed Ted the mike
and he sang "Twist and Shout!"
But he's The Blitz.
I'm not The Blitz.
I'm The Bueller.
You know what this means.
You're The Blitz.
Blitz...
Life moves pretty fast, Barney.
If you don't stop and look around
once in a while, you might miss it.
Chicka-chicka!
Happy Thanksgiving!
Best friend alert!
The Turturkeykey
is officially cooking.
God, that is disgusting!
Guys, that's starting to hurt.
Random number guy just
sent me his wang back.
You sent a wang out,
and you got a wang back.
- It's a boom-a-wang.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
- No, I meant the wang.
- Could you get me some more ice?
- Sure. But...
No one move while I'm gone.
I'm scared.
You're safe.
It's okay to leave the room.
You have to leave the building
for something cool to happen.
Thanks.
You're the only one who's
nice to me about this.
I gotta test this.
What happened?
You missed it!
Dude, you walked out of the room,
the laws of physics stopped
and the laws of awesome tripled.
Man!
You said I could leave the room!
I just wanted
to see something cool happen.
I'm sorry. But I was on that island
for what seems like eternity.
I'm gonna enjoy things
on the other side.
I will pay you to be The Blitz.
$100!
No... $10,000.
No, 60 bucks. That's a lot of money
for someone like you.
Dude, The Blitz isn't something
that can be bought or sold.
Yeah, it's not like Ted's integrity.
What was that?
I was distracted by the 4-caret diamond
your 53-year-old husband bought you.
Facial!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a turturkeykey to baste.
I'm coming with you.
I baste alone.
I'm sure you're a master baster.
Word play. Loving it.
But relax. I've got a ton of sides
to heat up since my plans fell through.
Who canceled? Your coven?
Coven. Group of witches. Boom.
They were worn out from
putting that spell on your hair.
Serve returned.
Are you happy?
You're ruining Thanksgiving.
You're not exactly who I thought I'd be
spending Thanksgiving with, either.
God, I'm so happy to be here.
My face hurts from smiling.
I'm sorry, Lily. I'm just
never gonna like that woman.
- Ted, give her a chance.
- Enemies can't become friends.
Yes, they can.
Right, guys?
You guys can't be objective.
You still feel guilty about last night.
Let's get an outside opinion.
- Who are we gonna...
- "Dear Wang Guy..."
"Can enemies ever be friends?
Just wondering."
Really? Wang Guy?
We're asking Wang Guy?
He's bold and uninhibited,
so why not?
And guys, you know what? For fun,
why don't we ask him
what he does for a living?
Wouldn't that be fun?
You've got a little crush
on Wang Guy, don't you?
What? No.
Shut up. I hate him.
Look.
We got an answer. Here it is.
"Yes, enemies can become friends.
"Remember what Gandhi said.
'Be the change you want
to see in the world.'"
Did Wang Guy just quote Gandhi?
That is amazing.
And I was here for it.
Now Zoey is The Blitz.
Burn on her.
Come on, man.
Don't be that Blitz.
I'm not any Blitz!
You're The Blitz!
You're all The Blitz!
I slept with that cute
Indian girl who cuts my hair!
What does that have to do
with anything?
Nothing! I just forgot
to brag about it before!
Guys, despite the wit
and wisdom of Wang Guy,
Zoey and I
are never going to be friends.
We're just here for her oven
and that's it.
- Did you do that on purpose?
- What? No. It was an accident.
Yeah. Well, like this is.
- Great. Real mature.
- Yeah, well, you started it.
Just stop it!
Can't you two just
stop fighting for one day?
Like, when the Roadrunner
and the Coyote
clocked out and had a beer together?
Or Tom and Jerry
shared a cup of coffee.
Those are cartoon characters, and I'm
pretty sure you're making up episodes.
And if Zoey is a cartoon character,
she's Cinderella's evil stepmother!
Get out.
All of you, out!
But it's Thanksgiving.
And I'm a part of it.
Out!
Wait...
Where's Barney?
Guys, the most amazing thing
just happened to me in that other roo...
Man.
I don't get it.
Why'd she just
kick us out like that?
And then the cab driver said
the last thing any of us wanted to hear.
Where to?
I guess we're going home.
Yeah. I don't know where that is.
Lily, where'd you get that?
When Zoey booted us, it made me
wanna steal something of hers again.
Apartment full of designer labels,
and what do I grab?
"Happy Turkey Day, Hannah.
Love, Zoey."
I wonder who Hannah is.
You guys should come
to my house for Thanksgiving.
My husband always spends it with his
daughter, so I'm gonna be alone, anyway.
You're not exactly who I thought I'd be
spending Thanksgiving with, either.
And if Zoey is a cartoon character,
she's Cinderella's evil stepmother!
Get out!
All of you, out!
We have to go back to Zoey's.
You gotta throw me
some addresses, buddy.
What are you doing here?
Barney let us in.
Barney was here?
I was walking around half-naked.
Man!
Wait. Which half?
I'm sorry your stepdaughter didn't wanna
spend Thanksgiving with you.
How do you know that?
I just do.
It must be tough.
It was the first Thanksgiving
Hannah agreed to spend with me,
and then at the last minute,
she changed her mind.
She hates my guts.
I get that.
You should hang on to this.
You can give it to her next year.
Right.
Next year.
You never know.
People don't stay enemies forever.
And that's the story of how
Zoey and I became friends.
- Cheers.
Before we eat, we should take
a group picture and send it to Wang Guy.
- Great idea.
- All right.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
That is the best-looking turturkeykey
I have ever seen.
Thank you. Let's just hope
it tastes as good as it looks.
It didn't.
It tasted wrong.
We forgot to light the candles.
And just as Barney looked away,
it happened.
The Gentleman!
What happened?
I saw it!
Come on, Blitz. Now it's just sad.
Man.
Go ahead.
I forgot my jacket.
Hold the door!
Thank you, God!
Man!
Blitz.
www.tvsubtitles.net