I cannot stop
staring at that girl's face.
Face.
That's your weirdest nickname
for boobs yet.
I'm really looking at her face.
That's actually really sweet.
Puffy cheeks,
smudged mascara,
slightly red nose...
That girl was just crying.
She's so sad
and defenseless.
Anyone have a condom?
That's it! You know what?
Five-minute time-out! Corner booth! Now.
Get this. You know
my friend Max from law school?
He's
at Gregor's Steakhouse downtown,
and Woody Allen
is sitting two tables over.
He wants us to come check it out.
I don't know, it could be cool.
I've never seen Woody Allen.
What?! How can you be a New Yorker
and never have seen Woody Allen?
I have seen plenty
of other famous people.
Last week I saw...
Maury Povich.
Kids, you know talk
show host Maury Povich.
It was uncanny
how often we saw this guy.
- Dude, everyone sees Maury Povich.
- Maury Povich is everywhere.
I'm sorry, Robin, but you're not a real
New Yorker till you've seen Woody Allen.
I am, too, a real New Yorker.
That's adorable.
You're from Canada.
I've been here for almost six years.
It's not like I just got off a boat.
A boat!
Wait, that is how you say it.
I'd say you're not a real New Yorker
till you've stolen a cab from someone
who needs it more than you.
You're not a real New Yorker
till you've cried on the subway
and not given a damn
what anyone thinks.
You're not a real New Yorker till you've
killed a cockroach with your bare hands.
Those rules are all stupid, okay?
I've never done any of those things.
By the end of this day, Robin
would have done all of those things.
Okay, time's up.
What are we talking about?
Woody Allen is eating at Gregor's,
and Robin thinks we should go see him.
Why would I do that?
I'll see him at poker on Tuesday.
Come on, if we jump in a cab,
we'll be there in 15 minutes.
A real New Yorker knows
the subway's faster.
Take the 1, and transfer to the 2-3.
The bus runs more often on weekends.
Take the M-7 to the M-5.
The bus? Every time I take the bus,
there is one crazy person
no one wants to sit near.
That's why
I have never taken the bus.
Plus...
I can run faster than a bus.
Dude, that's, like, seven miles.
You can't do that.
- You can't beat the bus!
- I can beat
a bus or a cab or a train!
Is anyone else suddenly
craving green eggs and ham?
Machines are overrated, and someone
needs to take them down a peg.
You're all wrong... I got a way to get
there so fast, I could beat all of you,
even if I sat down and ordered
- a big, juicy steak first.
- How?
Medium rare.
But that's not important right now.
I know the city better
than any of you guys.
All right, all right,
hold on, hold on!
Let's just forget about it.
Who cares? I mean, there's no way
to find out who's right anyway.
- First person there wins!
- Doesn't matter how you get there!
Stay sad! I'll be back!
Synchronisation :
Kyros, MiniBen314, Strex
Adaptation :
H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture : MiniBen314, Titou
6x04 - Subway Wars (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
Can I see a menu, please?
No rush.
Kids, I should tell you,
Lily really needed a win that day.
When Marshall and Lily
decided to have a baby,
they assumed
it would happen right away.
It's gonna be positive.
Eriksen man are hella fertile.
When Uncle Morris was 16,
he got his girlfriend pregnant
just by holding her hand too
tight in the backseat of a car.
Now I'm thinking
my parents lied to me.
It's negative.
As the weeks went by,
Marshall's confidence never wavered.
And it started to mess
with Lily's head.
Negative?
We know it's not me.
Everything's fine.
These things take time.
Not with an Eriksen.
Something must be wrong with you.
Also, my mom hates you.
You know what?
Just to make sure,
I'm gonna pee on this again.
What?
No, you wouldn't.
Somebody help me!
Lily was so fed up
with not getting anywhere,
maybe winning this race
was just what she needed.
Idiot!
I'll show them.
My body can outrun
any motorized vehicle.
I'm like John Henry
when he beat the steam engine.
All I need is a great folk song.
Gather round, ye children
To hear the tale so sweet
Of a man who dared to race machines
With nothing but his feet
Suck it, grand-butt!
Marshall
Versus the machines
Taxi!
Excuse me, I got a thing.
Track maintenance?
20-minute delay?
- How do you do that?
- I grew up here, I speak conductor.
Damn it!
Kids, I also needed a win that day.
A couple nights earlier,
your Uncle Marshall
had offhandedly mentioned
a Web site called...
Grademyteacher.net?
It's this site where students can go say
what they think about their professors.
You're probably on there.
I just had to see what my students
had written about me.
And it was...
majestic.
Until...
Now, kids, I knew
I was a good professor.
That's why I didn't let it bother me.
I had nothing to prove.
Absolutely nothing.
Here's a fun fact.
See the Alberta Building over there?
The brown one or the gray one?
That's the gray one.
Did you know that in 18...
Come on!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Excuse me, I've got a thing.
- That's my cab!
- Gregor's Steakhouse, downtown.
This is my cab!
Downtown hospital, please.
It's right by Gregor's Steakhouse.
Take the FDR, and maybe
crank up some smooth jazz.
We're required by law to take you
to the nearest hospital,
which is St. Luke's-Roosevelt.
Uptown.
It's Barney.
Help me.
Robin also needed a win that day.
It had been a rough year for Robin.
First her boyfriend
and former cohost, Don,
left her for another job.
Then Robin met
her new cohost, Becky.
Hi! I'm Becky!
I am so excited to be your coanchor!
Hi, Becky.
My, you're perky.
Don't worry, I am not here
to step on your toesies.
You're still the star.
I made chocolate chip cookies
for everybody!
And just like that,
Becky started to eclipse Robin.
I mean, literally eclipse her.
This is my cab!
Keep it.
Ranjit, take me to Gregor's.
Taking you to Gregor's.
As Marshall ran with all his might
and passed his friend Christine
He thought of all the times
that he had beaten the machine
He triumphed over "Pitfall"
He vanquished the alarm
He brought the jukebox
back to life with his Fonzarelli arm
Marshall
Versus the machines
Last seat.
Thank God.
I just had the worst cab ride
of my life.
Well, you're in luck.
See that gothic church over there?
Those Corinthian columns were
designed by Giuseppe Pegatto
in 1896.
Ranjit, pull over.
Pulling over.
Hey, toots!
How about a ride?
Hey, Robin, it's you.
Move along!
See that over there?
That's the old Arcadian Hotel.
Fun fact...
While today its neoclassical
fenestration is considered to be...
So, is this ride your way
of apologizing for this morning?
I'm sorry.
I never apologize.
- And why would I?
- Are you kidding me?
- Can I talk to you?
- Sure.
Stand a little more this way.
I'm scouting some talent.
Pretend we're talking
about something important.
Well, this is something important.
I'm having
a really rough time at work,
the whole Becky thing...
That's just getting distracting.
Say "carrots and peas."
Guys, I can't stop staring
at that girl's face.
What, you really had something
to talk about?
I've spent the last
six years in this city,
focusing on my career,
all for nothing.
Some lady almost got me killed.
Maury Povich stole my cab.
I swear, this city is starting to
reject me like a bad organ transplant.
Everyone keeps saying
that I'm not a real New Yorker.
Maybe I should just stop trying.
Robin, I had no idea.
It's my fault for thinking
that you might care.
- Ranjit, stop the car.
- Stopping the car.
- Don't stop the car.
- Not stopping the car.
- Seriously, stop the car.
- Seriously stopping the car.
Look, you...
Wait, Robin, hold on.
If you want to talk, I'm right here.
Carrots and peas.
Don't...
I'll crank up the smooth jazz.
Our hero's strength
was fading fast
Just as the light turns...
Green
He then thought back
to all the times
He'd lost to a machine
Come on, Playboy Channel.
The cable box is fearsome
But the stapler's mighty sting
Come on, Spice Channel.
The cable box's bite again
Getting too tired
To sing
Kids, that day, I had
a horrible realization.
If you can't spot the crazy
person on the bus...
it's you.
The good news is, I was halfway there
and nothing could stop me.
- This is crazy.
- I can't believe it.
This is clearly a sign.
Let's just call it a tie.
Forget about the race.
Head back to the bar.
Just like that,
the race was back on.
Idiot.
Meanwhile, one subway car over...
Bite me!
Faster.
Mush! Mush!
I need this win.
And firing half my department
freed up the money to double my salary.
And this chick from Boston
was wicked hot in bed last night,
and I'm getting more muscular
even though I've stopped working out,
and I've got
this amazing poker group.
Actually, Barney did not need a win.
And I smell incredible.
Smell me.
Seriously, smell me.
He did smell incredible.
Too slow.
Switch.
Sweetie?
Are you okay?
I am done with this city.
It wins.
I just want to move somewhere new
and start over.
You've had a rough year.
But you're tough.
And I love you like crazy.
If you left, I'd have to follow you.
And Marshall would follow me.
And Ted would follow him.
The only upside
is that we might get rid of Barney.
Bring it in.
What did he say?
No clue.
Is that Maury Povich?
Sorry, I swear I'll be a great friend
at the finish line,
but the conductor just said
you're going express to Borough Hall,
which means you're screwed.
So long, sucker.
Bring it in.
Damn it.
It's Lily.
Help me.
And not a single passenger
would listen to me.
Am I a bad teacher?
Do I just put people to sleep?
Buddy?
Hey, buddy?
Need a hand?
The machines have won!
The machines have won.
Dude, mellow.
I can't do it.
I can't run that far.
I can't outrace anything.
I can't...
I can't get my wife pregnant!
Wait. Is that what this whole
stupid running thing has been about?
My body has been letting me down,
and I just wanted to prove
it could still do something,
but it can't.
You've been trying for two months,
not two years, that's nothing.
You should talk.
You're the one who's freaking out
because you have one mediocre review
and, like, 50 great ones.
64, but whatever.
And you're designing
a fricking building.
Come on, dude.
Sounds like you guys
need to clear everything,
subtract the negativity,
and add some perspective.
Get in!
- There it is.
- Where are Marshall and Lily?
Who cares?
I won?
I won!
I can't believe it!
How did that even happen?
Here's how it happened.
- He's in. Go. Go. Gun it.
- Ted's in the way.
- Run him over.
- Running him over.
What the hell
is the matter with you?
Nothing.
I just want to win this really badly.
So badly that I just ditched Robin
when she needed me.
You were also gonna run over Ted.
Why did I get so crazy about this?
Maybe for the same reason
I kept saying I could run seven miles.
I'm trying to be really
confident and positive about this, but,
I'm really scared
we're not pregnant yet.
I keep thinking
there's something wrong with me.
I keep thinking the same.
- It's only been two months.
- We are crazy.
- We're totally crazy.
- This is the last time
it's ever gonna be just the two of us.
Shouldn't we be enjoying that?
- We gotta go back to Paris.
- And take ballroom dancing.
And really learn how to ski, not just
go up and get faced in the lodge.
And see Coney Island.
I've still never been.
We have a whole bucket list
of things to do before having kids.
A cradle list.
I'm...
so glad we're trying,
and I'm gonna be really excited
for when it happens,
but this isn't a race.
This isn't a race.
Ranjit, screw Gregor's.
Let's go to Coney Island.
Screwing Gregor's.
Going to Coney Island.
As for how Robin beat me and Barney,
to this day,
your uncle Barney won't admit it...
But here's what I saw:
I saw Barney notice Robin's face...
and maybe realize something.
Barney says he tripped,
but it sure felt
like he tackled me on purpose.
And when Robin won,
I could have sworn I saw him smiled.
I know what you did back there.
Check it.
I just drove a pedicab 26 blocks,
and I still smell incredible.
Smell me.
- I'm not...
- Smell me.
He did smell incredible.
Wait a minute.
So, where's Woody Allen?
Right there.
Damn it, Max.
That's Maury Povich.
I always get those two confuse.
Technically, there was only
one winner that day.
But in that race, everyone
found exactly what they needed.
It's true, she wouldn't see Woody Allen
for another couple months,
but that's how Robin became,
by just about any definition
of the term...
... a real New Yorker.
www.tvsubtitles.net