Kids, in the winter of 2010,
we had a new addition
to our little group-- Zoey.
Zoey was married to...
The Captain.
Boys! Great to see you!
Looking smart.
Have a wonderful time
tonight, okay?
Okay.
That man is terrifying.
Everything he said was nice,
but I am profoundly scared.
Keep smiling.
He can still see us.
(all murmuring)
NARRATOR: There was
just something about him.
We couldn't put
our finger on it until...
I figured it out!
I know what's so creepy
about The Captain.
Okay.
(all scream)
Yeah.
I snapped this
photo of him
last time he dropped off Zoey.
Observe.
The bottom half
of his face... is smiling.
LILY: Oh. Look,
he seems happy.
Seems like a nice guy.
(all murmur happily)
But the top half of his face...
(all gasp)
...wants to murder you!
Cheerful.
(all screaming)
Wants to murder you.
No. Cheerful.
(all scream)
Wants to murder you.
Now, hold on.
Let me ask him a question.
Captain,
what do you think of ice cream?
Oh, he loves it!
Captain, what do you
think of rainy days?
(gasps) Whoa, he hates them.
Captain, quick question:
How do you feel about
the Jonas Brothers? Ooh.
Ooh.
What-What is that?
I don't get it.
He hates that he loves them.
(all murmur):
Ah!
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION,
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Great. Okay.
Hey, guys, Zoey just told me
about this great Frank Lloyd
Wright retrospective tonight.
Who's in?
Sorry, I'm, uh, I...
I- I don't know,
washing my hair.
Running the water.
Holding the towel.
And I'll be home
trying to get over the fact
that no one invited me
to the big hair washing party.
All right, fine.
Guess it'll just be me and Zoey.
Oh, wait.
Just the two of you?
Tread lightly, Mosby.
Any time
a single guy hangs out
with a married woman,
there are rules
that must be followed.
Rule number one...
Don't use
the husband's condoms.
That's just rude.
Rule number one:
don't go anywhere
that has candles.
Excuse me, Captain,
how do you feel
about Ted and Zoey having
an intimate chat by candlelight?
Mm-hmm...
(yelling)
It'll be the last dinner
they ever have.
Rule number two:
No sharing food.
Hmm.
In fact, anything involving
saliva is off-limits.
Toothbrushes,
thermometers, lipstick.
Well, if I can't share
her lipstick,
there's really no point
in even going.
And the most
important rule of all...
Lubricant is public
property. (Robin groans)
Please.
No lying to the spouse
about anything you do.
Why would anyone lie?
Look, Zoey and I
are just friends.
If there was anything more
than that,
I wouldn't hang out with her.
Lily's right, Ted.
Once you're married,
it's very hard to be friends
with a single person of the
opposite sex. ROBIN: Yeah.
Unless you're old friends,
which is why
I can hang out
with Marshall whenever I want.
Right, Marsh Madness?
No doubt, Robo Cop.
You two never hang out alone.
You just made up those nicknames
right now.
I guess it's true.
You and I never really
hang out alone.
Well, let's. Let's have dinner
together, just the two of us.
Oh! Sweet.
No candles.
BOTH:
Lily, I guess that leaves
just you and me. Want to hang?
NARRATOR: And then Lily
said something to Barney
that insulted every fiber
of his being.
Nah.
(gasps)
NARRATOR: Wait. No. It had
to be more than just, "Nah."
Oh, I think she said...
You're a big...
stupid octopus head!
(gasps)
NARRATOR:
No, that doesn't make sense.
Okay, hang on.
What did she say?
She said, um, uh...
To be honest kids, I'm having
a little trouble remembering
exactly what their fight
was about.
Hey, it was 20 years ago!
I'll remember.
Anyway, the next night...
Well, Lily,
you were right.
Something weird happened
with Zoey last night.
(phone plays "Anchors Aweigh")
Oh, that's the Captain.
Yes, I call my husband
The Captain,
but that is the only concession
I make to his seafaring ways.
Hang on.
Ahoy.
I'm just out with friends.
Friends. Plural.
Like-Like there was more
than one of me.
Ew! Ew!
She lied
to her husband? Uh-oh.
So, what did you do?
Uh, Zoey, um, did you just say
you were out with friends?
Yeah. The Captain's
on his way home from Milan.
He can get a little jealous
sometimes,
so I didn't want
to make him worry.
Is that okay?
It's totally okay.
It's not okay! I didn't
really think it was okay!
Pur-leez! You lie to
your husband all the time.
"Uh, uh, that shirt
looks great on you""
"I love your mom""
"I never fantasize about
Barney when we're doing it""
Sound familiar, Pinocchio?
(scoffs)
What's wrong
with this shirt?
TED:
Lily, ruling.
Do I have to stop
hanging out with Zoey?
No, you just need
to spend time
with her
and The Captain together.
If you're friends
with the both of them,
then there's not a problem.
Actually, I do have a standing
invitation from The Captain
to go for a ride with them
on his boat.
Great. So go make nice
with Captain Creepy,
and problem solved.
NARRATOR:
The next night,
Marshall and Robin went
to dinner,
just the two of them.
Now historically,
they had three solid
conversation topics:
cold weather...
December chill-- so great.
Totally.
NARRATOR:
...sports...
Did you catch
the game last night?
Yeah. Nail-biter.
NARRATOR:
...and cold weather sports.
You know what's fun?
Mm.
Is cold weather sports.
They are fun.
NARRATOR: They blew through
them all in the first 16 seconds.
ROBIN:
Man, this is awkward.
MARSHALL:
She's giving me nothing!
He's just staring at me!
She's just staring at me!
It's making me nervous.
Great, now my left eye
is twitching.
Marshall, it's cool.
She doesn't see it.
What the hell's going on
with his eye?
Am I supposed to not talk
about that?
Great, now
my right eye is doing it.
Can I get you two some drinks?
Lots of drinks.
Oh, so many drinks.
NARRATOR: That same night, Barney
and Lily were still fighting
about, um... something.
Or was it that other thing?
Barney.
Save it, Lily.
I am still mad at you for...
something, and for
that other thing.
Look, I'm sorry
I hurt your feelings.
But let's be honest.
You've been super
sensitive lately.
(crying):
No, I haven't!
God, how can you say that?!
Watch out!
(yells)
NARRATOR:
Wait. They were on the street.
Watch out!
Oh!
Wow. Thanks, Lily.
You saved me.
You saved us.
Look, I know
you didn't mean
whatever it was
you said that made me so mad.
I think I probably didn't.
NARRATOR: And just like
that, the fight was over.
You know, kids,
friendship is funny sometimes.
Wait.
I still can't resist
getting one last shot in.
(gasps)
NARRATOR: Like I said, the
fight was just getting started.
Hi, Captain.
The Captain.
Captain.
Ahoy, Ted!
Excellent to see you.
Ah, you, too.
Uh, where's Zoey?
Well, I'm afraid
she's feeling a little
under the weather.
Looks like it's just
you, me
and six hours
in frigid international waters.
Or we could stay on dry land,
hang out with some... witnesses.
(laughs)
You're a hoot.
I've been looking
forward to this.
For a very long time.
Well, anchors aweigh!
NARRATOR: Kids, here's
one thing I do remember.
I was pretty sure
I was going to die that night.
Mmm.
You know, I had this really
boring poetry class in college.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You were just thinking that
this dinner is really boring.
That's what made you think of
your boring class in college.
What?! What? No! No!
No, no, no.
Marshall, no. No. I...
I just saw that board
of specials, and I thought,
you know what sucks?
Being bored.
Which I am not.
So that clears that... right up.
Robin, I'm an attorney.
(sighs)
Fine. This night's
a little awkward.
I guess it's 'cause we never
hang out alone together.
Why is that?
It's 'cause
of The Mermaid Theory.
Two years ago, I had just hired
a new assistant at GNB.
So, who's the eye broccoli?
Okay, that's Iris,
my new assistant.
And yes, she's a little plain,
but I'm married, so that's good.
Mark my words, Marshall.
Someday you will find Iris
so excruciatingly attractive,
you won't be able to look her
directly in the boobs.
I don't think
that's gonna be a problem.
Marshall, do you know how
the myth of mermaids came to be?
I'm sorry. Myth?
It was 300 years ago.
Sailors stuck at sea
would get desperate
for female companionship.
It got so bad
that, eventually,
the manatees out in the water
started to look like...
beautiful women.
Mermaids.
Let's go get some tail!
Oh.
You see, every woman, no matter
how initially repugnant,
has a mermaid clock--
the time it takes
for you to realize
you want to bone her.
Sure, today you see Iris
as a manatee.
But she ain't gonna
stay that way.
Marshall, your secretary's
mermaid clock starts right now.
(clock ticking)
MARSHALL: And it took one year,
three months, and 16 days,
but eventually...
(alarm bell dings)
(panting)
D'oh!
Told you.
The Mermaid Theory.
It's a thing.
You owe me 500 bucks.
Did we bet on this?
Let's say yes.
And that's why we never
hang out alone? Yes.
As Lily's best friend, you are
the last person on the planet
o's allowed
to turn into a mermaid.
Wait, does that mean
that I'm a manatee right now?
Big-time manatee.
What were those
sailors thinking?
Huh. I don't know.
Being out at sea can do
crazy things to a man.
Vast, the sea.
Deep.
Endless.
Going around for miles.
You could scream and scream,
and not a soul would hear you.
Listen to this.
(screams)
Help!
Somebody help me!
I'm trapped on a boat
with a madman!
Help!
See? Nothing.
(laughing)
(both laughing)
(anxious laugh)
He's gonna kill me.
Okay, calm down, Teddy.
He's not jealous.
He hasn't even mentioned Zoey.
So, Ted,
I noticed you've been spending
a lot of time with Zoey.
(terrified scream)
NARRATOR:
Okay, back to Barney and Lily
and whatever the hell
they were fighting about.
Seriously? I step away for
five seconds, and you eat
all my onion rings?
No surprise there.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you calling me fat?
If there is one thing
you never do,
it is call a woman fat
right to her face!
Wait. Barney's not a woman.
That's right--
Barney wasn't hurt by Lily,
Lily was hurt by Barney.
Want to hang?
Nah.
(gasps)
Watch out!
(panting)
Wow... thanks, Barney.
You saved me.
You saved us.
If there's one thing
you never do,
it's call a woman fat
right to her face!
Okay, now I'm on track.
The rest of this story
should make perfect sense.
Oh, Lily, I'm sorry.
Hey, you want
to see a magic trick?
(eerie whirring)
You're a jerk.
Okay, that makes no sense.
Kids, I'm officially
admitting defeat.
I will never
remember this story.
I'm sorry
for wasting your time.
Ted, let me show you
my harpoon collection.
Just gonna make a quick call.
Hey, silly question.
What are our exact
nautical coordinates?
How now?
Oh, bother.
(sighs) Well...
she's a goner.
By now, the icy tide
has already dropped
its core temperature
to near freezing.
And down it goes.
Now it's at 50 meters.
Complete crushing blackness.
100 meters.
The pressure is so intense,
the keys are popping
right out of its head.
Head?
200 meters.
No one will ever find
its mangled remains,
save for the crustacea
that feed off
its lifeless husk.
Can you hear me now?
No. Because you're
on the bottom of the sea.
Well, I got a big
morning, so...
Dry cleaners, bank, you
know, so... Ted, it's time.
(whimpers)
I have something
for you.
Wait here.
Okay, you got to swim
for it, Mosby.
Man versus sea.
You can do this.
You didn't get
a "Good Effort" ribbon
from the Shaker Heights
JCC Swim Camp
because you don't
have what it takes.
Found it.
Zoey told me
you're a scotch drinker.
I bought this special
for tonight.
And just as I started
to realize that maybe
I wasn't in danger after all,
we hit a bump.
Whoa!
(splash)
Ted?
that if you spend
too much time alone with me,
I'll turn into a mermaid?
Yes. I mean, sure, right now,
you're bald and leathery
ancovered in
a thick layer of blubber...
Am I blushing or...?
...but at some point, my stupid
male brain will transform you
into a foxy fish-babe singin'
"Part of Your World"
to my pants.
Okay, even if that happens, is
there any way to un-mermaid me?
I asked Barney the same thing.
Once mermaid-ified,
there's only one way
a woman can go back to being
unattractive again,
but it's pretty gruesome.
Death?
Worse. Pregnancy.
If a baby's on board that train,
it is headed straight back
to Manatee City...
where the grass ain't green
and the girls ain't pretty.
Pregnancy?
Mm-hmm.
Once a mermaid gets pregnant,
she becomes a manatee again.
Never thought
I'd say that sentence.
Wait! That's it!
That's what Barney and Lily were
fighting about!
The Mermaid Theory!
But their argument didn't happen
at the same time
as all this other stuff.
I'm literally in the wrong year!
It happened much, much later
when Lily was...
pregnant.
Well, Lily, I guess it's
just you and me.
You wanna hang?
Nah.
(gasps)
Whenever we're alone, you spend
the whole time undressing me
with your eyes.
You even take off my shoes.
High heels chafe my shoulders.
But you don't have to worry
about that anymore.
Ever since you got pregnant,
you're just a big fat manatee.
(gasps)
Well, you're a big...
stupid octopus face!
That was it! I remember now!
Wow. Thanks, Barney.
You saved me.
You saved us.
If there's one thing
you never do,
it's call a woman "fat"
right to her face!
I'm sorry, Lily.
Hey, you want to see
a magic trick?
Oh...
You're a jerk.
(Barney chuckles)
Hey. Hey, wait.
Come on. I was kid...
Wait, wait, wait!
There's another addendum
to The Mermaid Theory.
A pregnant woman who's become
a manatee can become
a mermaid again
through one simple act.
What's that?
Breast-feeding. Hot.
Really?
Really.
When those things swell up to
three times their normal size...
so do I.
That's so sweet!
See kids?
Told you I'd get it!
Okay, now we're even!
Yeah, that's the ending
to a whole other story.
We'll get there.
So you really thought
I was gonna kill you?
Well... ish.
Oh, Ted, that's ridiculous.
If I wanted to kill you, I'd
invite you to my hunting lodge.
It's far more remote,
and I wouldn't have
to worry about you turning up in
some nosy fisherman's net.
See? It's stuff like that.
Why-why do you talk that way?
Oh, I'm just jesting for sport.
See, sometimes I don't
bond as well
with Zoey's younger friends.
But I know she really likes you.
I was hoping that maybe
we could be buddies.
We can.
We can be buddies.
Just not on a boat.
Fair enough.
The hunting lodge it is.
Ho-ho-ho!
(slurring): You know, once we
stopped trying to have a conversation
and just focused on
the drinking...
I had fun.
Yeah, me, too.
And then a terrible thing
happened.
Marshall's beer goggles
kicked in
and his very drunk mind started
to see...
No... No, no!
No! No,
don't turn!
Uh-oh.
I don't feel so good.
(vomits)
Oh, my God! Oh, my God,
I am, I am so sorry!
Oh! You must think
I'm totally disgusting.
I really do.
And from that moment on
Marshall never worried
about Robin becoming
a mermaid again,
and the two of them were
closer than ever.
There you go.
Hey, Ted.
Hey. You feeling
better?
I have a confession
to make.
I wasn't really sick.
You weren't?
I'm sorry.
I was just feeling guilty
that I lied
to The Captain and...
I don't know, I just thought it
would be good
if you two spent some time
together.
I get it.
And you were right.
He's a nice guy.
I mean, he can be
a little scary.
Yeah, he gets a little murder-y
when he's nervous.
Yeah, he's a creepy dude.
But I like him.
And I just want to make sure
you and I hanging out
doesn't, you know,
cross any lines.
Me, too.
I mean, if either one of us had
even the slightest hint
of feelings for the other,
we shouldn't hang out.
You don't, do you?
No. Do you?
No.
(clock ticking)
Still no sign
of land.
It's been 243 days
since we've seen
another living soul.
What are you looking at?
Dude, we need
to find land.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net