Kids, when Lily and Marshall
started trying to have a baby,
they went a little crazy.
We've been trying and trying,
and still nothing's happened.
I'm just worried
we can't have children.
- And how long have you been trying?
- Six days.
But then, months went by,
and still nothing happened.
Something must be wrong.
We're doing it a lot.
And everywhere...
the kitchen, the bathroom,
the living room,
outside in your wait... the kitchen.
Seriously, Doc,
why isn't this happening?
Look, if you're really worried,
here is a number for a reproductive
endocrinologist... Dr. Stangel.
He's the best in the city.
I don't know, baby,
do we really need a specialist?
What's your plan, Marshall,
just have unprotected sex
day after day after day
in every position imaginable
until...?
Wait, it sounded worse in my head.
Guys, we've got a problem.
This is the application
for the regional doubles
laser tag tournament
in Poughkeepsie.
Problem is,
only one of you can be my partner.
So it looks like
we've got a bake-off.
- You may now present your arguments.
- I'm not playing laser tag.
- I'm absolutely not playing.
- Damn it.
And Marshall's the winner.
Well, I'm gonna call Dr. Stangel.
It can't hurt.
So Aunt Lily went
to see Dr. John Stangel,
the man who knew more about human
reproduction than anyone in New York.
So, I understand
you want to get pregnant.
Team Who's this fucking mother?
Synchronisation:
Kyros, MiniBen314
Adaptation: Dark_Chii, H3AV3N,
Luoleilina, tactactac
Relecture:
Olaola, Titou et son pseudo variable
6x13 - Bad News (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
Yeah, and it cuts in and out.
How did you do it?
God, you found one of the cameras.
I swear that's the only one.
Wait, which one did you find?
- What are you talking about?
My visit to a certain Dr. Stangel.
We'll look at all the factors
that contribute to fertility:
dietary, environmental, genetic.
But first, Ms. Aldrin,
do you have any questions for me?
Just one, "Dr. Stangel."
Where'd you get the beard?
Well...
My mother's Armenian.
I've been with Barney
since 9:00 a.m.
Between the sexual harassment
seminar all morning
and the secretary beauty
pageant all afternoon,
he hasn't left my sight.
So you weren't wearing a fake beard
and examining girl parts all day?
Not today I wasn't.
We finally found Barney's doppelganger.
I guess we can tell you now, Lily.
That hot dog guy
did not look like Barney.
I know, we made our little deal
with the universe...
No, we've made a binding covenant
with the universe.
We said we weren't
gonna try to have kids
until we saw Barney's doppelganger.
This is bad news.
This is like a black cat
walked through my uterus.
Okay, that's it.
I am going back to Dr. Stangel
and getting thoroughly checked out.
Or cost-saving alternative:
you could get checked out
by someone who looks just like him.
I'm gonna go scrub up,
I'll meet you in stall 3.
- I still kind of think it's Barney.
- There's no way it's Barney.
Hello, you must be Mr. Eriksen.
I am Dr. Stangel.
It's Barney.
Really, dude, bravo.
You almost got a peek.
But seriously,
what second-rate community
theater did you get...?
Would you...?
So my wife and I
are trying to get pregnant.
Put your feet up in the stirrups.
We can begin.
- No, can't do it.
- No, but, baby,
I yanked on his beard.
He checks out.
I don't have time for this.
Wait, please... It's...
Can you just give us
a couple minutes?
How can I convince you
that this is not Barney?
It is like looking into
a poorly dressed mirror.
Okay, you have to go.
Leave the model of the vagina.
Convinced.
Great. All right,
you're a little low on the table.
- Please scoot up.
- "Suit up"... not convinced.
This whole thing
stinks to high heaven.
Baby, you just saw Barney.
He could have pulled
some crazy switch.
Remember when his Swedish
cousin came to visit?
Yeah... Bjorney.
I'm sorry, but unless I see
Barney at the same time,
I'll never be sure
that Dr. Stangel isn't him.
How you doing?!
Should I have a boner?!
We're all done. I'll call you
in a few days with the results.
You don't mind
if I take pictures, do you?!
Can we leave him in here
for a while?
I'm done for the day.
You can leave him in here all night.
Smile for the birdie, Lil!
Gyno-mite!
Now, while all this was going on,
your Aunt Robin was starting
her new job at World Wide News,
aka the big leagues.
She was excited.
This job was a new start,
a clean slate.
So, first day of work?
Everyone, say hello to your new
research associate Robin Scherbatsky.
- Hi, guys.
- Welcome.
Here comes our new Hardfire host.
Robin, this is Sandy Rivers.
Robin's old cohost
and my old nemesis.
We should have sex.
- I hate that guy.
- It gets worse.
Sandy, this is...
- You two know each other?
- Know each other?
We've had sex.
You had sex with Sandy Rivers?
And I can't believe
it's my first day,
and already I'm the girl
who slept with the host of the show.
Already? Were you planning on
eventually sleeping with the host?
Now that I know it's Sandy, I'm not.
There's a couple messages
on the machine. Your dad called.
He wants to know if
you have any sixes.
We got a game of "Go Fish"
going on the phone.
P.S., Pops, go fish.
Who's the second message from?
Dr. Stangel's office.
- I'm extremely fertile.
- You're extremely fertile! My God!
I told you there was
nothing to worry about.
I gotta call my dad
and tell him the good news.
If you're fertile,
then that means I'm the problem.
Okay, now you're being ridiculous.
An hour ago, you didn't even think
there was a problem.
I was just putting on a brave face.
Okay, think about it:
we've had unprotected sex
203 times in the past four months.
Obviously I'm the problem.
Problem?!
You can't get a girl pregnant.
That's the dream.
I'd give my firstborn
to not be able to have children.
So, second day of work?
What's wrong?
You didn't hear?
She's the office slut.
Already? Honey...
I wish I was the office slut.
And we can explore how
those policy changes will affect Iraq.
We definitely had sex.
We did not have sex.
Then why do I remember you?
I don't know, maybe because I'm
a smart, talented, professional.
No, none of those.
I remember.
We didn't have sex.
Thank you.
You're the girl who did the report
on the carriage driver
and slipped
and fell in horse poop...
We did have sex.
I remember now.
Do me a favor.
But this reporter takes pride in...
And now everyone
calls me Scherpoopie.
It's not funny.
A word of advice: play along.
Okay, the more you fight it,
the worse it's going to get.
It's like when your car slides on ice,
you steer into the skid.
Exactly!
Or when your... I don't know...
friend invites you to a laser tag
tournament, you don't fight it.
You just strap on the vinyl holster
and race into that abandoned JCPenney
guns a-blazin'.
I'm just agreeing with Ted.
It's my dad.
Aren't you gonna get it?
No, you know what? I'm gonna get
my stuff checked out first.
I'll call my dad after Dr. Stangel
gives me the thumbs up.
He has to do that?
But I thought you talk
to your dad about everything.
I only like to call
my dad with good news.
I mean, telling him good news
is what makes it feel real to me.
I'm getting married!
- I passed the bar!
- All right!
I found an amazing Viking lamp
that fits right on the coffee table,
as long as we don't mind
stepping over the cord.
- That's what I'm talking about!
- Right?!
I found someone who can
fix the Viking lamp!
But the news that I might not be able
to give him a grandchild?
You know, like, I don't even know
how to have that conversation.
I'll show you.
Dad, there's, there's something
I need to tell you,
and it's going to come
as a bit of a shock to you,
but here goes.
You are speaking
to the 2011 Tri-County
Laser Tag Co-Champion.
- I've already told...
- And my sperm don't work.
The laser tag thing is awesome.
So, third day of work?
And the fertilizer is seeping
into the ground water, causing...
Is Scherpoopie pitching
a story about manure?
Genius.
Yes, I fell into some manure.
It's hilarious, fine.
In a five-year career
of on-air reports,
there are bound to be a
few embarrassing moments.
A few?
But in my case, it was just the one,
and you found it, so...
Just the one.
Oh, God.
What did they find?
Everything.
Everybody, come and play
I'm a dirty, dirty girl.
VENTILATEUR GEANT !
The Federal Reserve Board
voted to leave interest...
They even found the video of me
getting attacked by an owl.
You got attacked by an owl?
I did not get attacked by an owl.
Robin, here's what you need to do...
Don't you dare tell me
to steer into the skid, okay?
It's too late. I'm already
wrapped around a hydro pole.
It's a Canadian telephone pole.
I never should have taken this job.
Kids, at that moment,
I knew what I had to do
for my friend Robin.
But first I had to do
something for me.
Show me...
"owl attack."
I am freaking out.
Is there a chance
that I can't have kids?
I've been hit in the nuts a lot.
We won't know anything
until we run some tests.
We'll need a sample of your sperm.
No, there's a room
at the end of the hall.
If you find yourself in the elevator,
you've gone too far.
You'd think I wouldn't have to say that,
but you'd be surprised.
All yours, buddy.
The thing you're
about to do in here...
I did that in here, too.
Three minutes ago.
I was here eight minutes ago.
14 minutes ago.
I'm here every Thursday.
I can't do it, Doc.
Is there another option?
Could I take this home?
Sure, you could,
but we close in an hour
and I'm not back till Tuesday.
So, clock is ticking. Make it fast.
Only way I know how, Doc.
Only way I know how.
Surprise!
Mom. Dad.
What are you doing here?
We hadn't heard from you in two days.
We were worried about you.
For God's sake.
Do you have any sixes?
Go fish.
Excuse me.
Can I just talk to you in
here for a minute?
Isn't it great?
They just showed up.
Your mom's already
rearranged my kitchen,
organized my closet
and she asked me if I lost height.
Not weight. Height.
I'm very excited
that they're here, too.
But right now, I have to get excited
about something else.
Okay.
Well, I'll go handle your parents.
And you handle your, well...
Wait, Marshall.
Thank you, baby. You're the best.
I just got my new bathing suit
for the beach this summer.
It's a two-piece.
I mean, can you imagine?
Me in a two-piece
bathing suit at my age?
Just picture it!
Picture it!
That's why Fred Cox
is the greatest kicker
the Vikings ever had.
Seriously, Marshall, picture it.
Just picture it.
Give me a C. Give me an O.
Give me an X.
What's that spell?
Cox! Cox!
Okay, I did a bad thing last night.
- I looked up his address.
- Who?
Sorry. You said "who."
It reminded me of the owl footage.
Genius.
Sandy.
How dare he laugh at you.
Who does he think...
Sorry. "Who."
Anyway. I looked up his address
in your contact list.
God. Tell me you
didn't go over there.
I just thought...
he needed to listen to common sense
and reasonable discourse.
God. Tell me those aren't
the names of your fists.
They're my feet.
I'm more of a kicker.
So I went to his apartment.
You're not the pizza guy.
Oh, my God. This is...
This is how you make sure Sandy
never makes fun of you again.
I told you to steer into the skid.
That was bad advice.
So new advice.
Steer into Sandy, and run him down.
If people found out
Sandy wears a toupee...
Really? That's your take-away?
Nothing on the bear in the bra?
No. He's very open about that.
That's Gregory.
Nice guy.
And the top is so low-cut.
Your father says he has
front-row seats
to the Minnesota Twins.
By the way, Marshall,
we do need to know
if you're coming to Florida this summer.
Are you coming?
Marshall, are you coming?
This isn't working.
- Where you going, son?
- I'm going to...
I'm going to...
Kids, to this day,
your uncle Marshall is thankful
for what Lily said next.
He's going to masturbate.
Marshall, tell them what's going on.
And so Marshall told his parents
everything.
Now, I'm scared that we won't be able
to give you a grandchild.
We don't care about that one bit.
And if you guys want kids,
there are other ways.
Adoption.
Maybe you have a good friend
who could loan you some sperm?
Maybe adoption.
What I'm saying is,
we love you no matter what.
Why don't you pretend
you're in high school,
get back in that bathroom,
and "blow dry your hair."
Wait, you knew?
We didn't have a hair dryer, dear.
So?
Possibly last day of work?
Actually, it was a good day.
And I need more numbers
on how the holiday season
impacted the economy.
Sparkles, got anything on malls?
Actually, Sandy,
I have something I think
you're all gonna want to see.
Yes! Put him in a body bag!
- I didn't do it.
- What?
I didn't want to just attack someone
out of the blue like some kind of...
Owl?
Exactly.
So, instead of taking your advice,
I took your advice.
That day, Robin decided
to steer into the skid.
And though she never quite
shook the nickname,
Sparkles went on to do very well
at World Wide News.
Especially after this happened.
After his parents had gone
back to Minnesota,
Marshall got the results.
I'm afraid I have
some very bad news, Marshall.
Judging from the results
of your test, it is...
it is very unlikely that you'll be able
to father a child.
- Oh, God.
- I know, I know.
It's just...
Now...
in some rare cases,
a regimen change
can fix the problem,
so I'm recommending
a spirited cardio routine.
Preferably with a partner,
involving any light-based
firearm activity
in the Tri-State area.
Poughkeepsie, for example.
Have you heard of the gentlemen's sport
known as laser tag?
Surprise!
Damn it, Barney!
What are you doing in here?
Think about it, Marshall. All entrants
get 20% off at the snack bar!
BT-dub, the receptionist.
What's her situation?
Go!
Well, Marshall.
I've got your results.
And?
Your sperm is fine.
My sperm is fine!
Count, motility...
everything's off the charts.
You, sir, have got
some strong swimmers.
Bro, that is awesome.
Motility five!
Can I borrow your phone?
I want to call my dad.
Go ahead.
Man, this is great.
I was expecting bad news.
I really was.
You're here!
Oh, my God!
I love you so much!
Can you believe it?
Something's happened.
Your father, he had a heart attack.
He didn't make it.
My dad's dead?
I'm not ready for this.
www.tvsubtitles.net