Kids, in the spring of 2011,
Zoey and I broke up.
But the good news...
Goliath National Bank was finally ready
to demolish The Arcadian
and build the new headquarters
I'd designed for them.
The only problem was
I kept butting heads
with my project supervisor
on one very important issue.
I want to press the button
to blow up The Arcadian!
- I want to press it!
- No, I want!
I want to press it!
I dated you both and neither of you
is good at pressing
or even finding the button.
After some awkward pawing around,
that building
is going to fake an implosion,
say, "Baby, that was great",
and go to sleep.
She means you.
I want to press it.
I'm gonna press it!
It's just a button, okay?
Can we just talk
about something else, please?
I ran into Zoey yesterday.
That's the first time
since the breakup.
How's she doing?
I'm still unemployed,
so I had to get a couple roommates.
Saving money.
Making new friends.
No downside.
They're all 22 and sell drugs.
Which means they're not taking them.
So, that's a win.
I can tell you're really busy
so I should...
I'll let you go.
You want to get coffee sometime?
You know "coffee" is code
for "I want to get back together"?
At first I wasn't sure, but then,
she said something that got me thinking.
I want to get back together.
Don't worry, we're not.
I just, I feel bad Zoey's
having such a hard time.
You know what might
make you feel better, buddy?
- I'm not letting you press the button.
- I want to press it!
Sadly, that's all you need
to know about my summer.
Around this time, Uncle Marshall was
still having a tough time finding a job.
He's out printing out a whole
new batch of résumés
because he misspelled the phrase
"detail-oriented."
And when he gets back home,
he is going to find his favorite soup
there waiting for him.
That's sweet, Lily,
but didn't you guys get
food poisoning here one time?
Three times.
But they're really nice about it.
Their policy is,
"Get sick, get a free gallon of soup".
And so, Lily dropped off Marshall's
surprise soup and headed back to work
to introduce the new class pet.
This is Mr. Buttons 2.
Now, after what happened
to Mr. Buttons 1,
we have to be very gentle with...
Don't eat the soup!
Thank God.
This was about to be my third bowl.
Why shouldn't I eat the soup?
Team Who's this fucking mother ?
Synchronisation :
Kyros, MiniBen314, Strex
Adaptation :
H3AV3N, tactactac, Titou
Relecture :
Titou le Lapinou
6x24 - Challenge Accepted (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
Mr. Architect,
big day for you tomorrow, huh?
Yeah, getting to stand next to me
while I press the button.
That is going to be legend...
wait for it...
dary adjacent.
Legendary adjacent!
You okay?
This morning I was talking
to the foreman.
Hey, hotshot.
You know, Rod,
I'm loving that nickname,
and I can tell
it's totally affectionate,
but I'd prefer Ted.
Yeah, but you're such a hotshot,
I figured I'd just call you hotshot.
Pick one.
And make sure you like it.
There's going to be 50,000 of these
in your big, hotshot building,
hotshot.
50,000 lightbulbs!
What if this one's too bright?
What if this one flickers
and gives everyone a weird headache?
Do you know how many people
it takes to change 50,000 lightbulbs?
Are these people Irish, Polish, blondes?
What are we dealing with here?
There's so many decisions to be made.
What if I make all the wrong ones
and my building just sucks?
Not possible.
Your building is new.
And I have one rule.
New is always better.
You can't keep saying you have one rule
if they're always different.
But "new is always better"
is my oldest rule,
which makes it the best.
Everything okay?
Lily got food poisoning
from some soup.
And then I ate the soup,
exactly three hours later.
Which means I can see exactly
three hours into my future,
and it doesn't...
look...
good.
I tried to be supportive.
Oh, baby,
can you just hold me, please?
Of course, baby.
But when Lily gets going
she sounds like a velociraptor
from Jurassic Park.
But then I realized...
a man can do a lot of living
in three hours.
So, I'm out experiencing this beautiful,
crazy dance called life.
My last meal.
MacClaren's famous jalapeño poppers.
My doctor says
I need to eat healthier,
so I figured the round-trip flight
these babies are about to take
will land them permanently
on the no-fry list.
Good-bye, my friend.
It's been a hell of a ride.
I have to...
Hey, babe.
The gang says feel better.
Thanks.
Wait!
You didn't tell them
I had food poisoning, did you?
Marshall, when it's stomach stuff,
you just say "under the weather",
or people start picturing you
doing unspeakable things.
I know.
I just said
that you had the sniffles.
No one is picturing anything
but little red-nosed you
under a blankie with some hot tea.
I wonder what end
it's coming out of Lily right now.
I bet it's her tushie.
I bet it's both.
Speaking of explosions...
Enough already, Ted!
That button's mine!
Yeah, fine, okay.
I got you this job, so I...
Say what?
Whatever.
It's yours.
I gotta run.
Yes.
It's Bloom, Greenberg and Associates.
They want me to come interview.
I know it's risky to go,
but this is the best environmental
law firm in New York, my dream job.
Great idea, babe.
I'll ask them.
Is it at all possible,
could I come in on Monday?
Okay, I'll, I'll see you at 5:00.
Thank you.
I love and believe in you too, baby.
Why would Ted
just give up the button like that?
He forgot his phone.
"See you in an hour."
- Who's that from?
- Zoey.
They're meeting for coffee.
Ted's getting back together with her!
Why would Ted get back together
with Zoey? He's doing great.
After a breakup,
we all think we're doing great.
Sometimes the tiniest trigger
can unravel you
and send you crawling right back.
Ted isn't getting back with Zoey
because of lightbulbs.
Ted's gone back for less.
Hi, Natalie.
You want to get coffee sometime?
CARTON
Bro.
Ted, I only have one rule.
But I can't reach the worst part.
Hi, Karen.
Want to get coffee sometime?
CARTON
Coming up next, our two local pandas,
Ming Ming and Bao Bao,
are expecting a baby.
You want to get coffee sometime...?
Get it together, bro.
According to my calculations,
at 6:00 PM,
my body is gonna pay out
like the most disgusting
slot machine in the world.
That gives me two hours
to go do the interview
and still get back in time.
What if you hit the jackpot early?
Don't worry.
I'll be prepared.
I'm talking your ear off, sorry.
Is there anything
I can do for you, sweetie?
Can... I... borrow...
an adult diaper?
Let's stop Ted.
Where are they meeting?
Zoey wrote, "Meet me
at 6:00, where it all began,
where you gave me the orchid
at the intersection."
That's good.
All we have to do is think back
to the time Ted told us
about his first date with Zoey.
Amazing first date with Zoey!
We met at the intersection.
That's sweet.
You weren't listening either?
I was in a coma.
I mean, who pays attention
to that sappy romantic crap?
Yeah, I wasn't listening, either.
Ted really can go on about a bitch.
Great.
He could be anywhere.
We're flat out of clues.
Wait. Ted left a message.
I could hear it
'cause I was in the bathroom...
blowing my nose.
I have the sniffles.
Hey, Lily,
hope you're feeling better.
Marshall told us you're exploding from
both ends like a busted fire hydrant.
Damn it.
Anyway, listen, I was going
to get back together with Zoey today,
but I came to my senses
on the way out here, so...
False alarm.
Oh, crap.
Just stepped in some gum.
I'm getting back together with Zoey!
We're never gonna find him.
Wait.
That's was a subway announcement
in the background.
I speak conductor.
Got it.
Ted's at...
- Ted's at Smith and Ninth Street.
- That's the intersection.
That's in Brooklyn. How are we
ever gonna get there in time?
Way ahead of ya.
Jake Bloom. Great to meet you.
I'm sorry about the stench.
We're suing a factory
that's been dumping raw sewage
into a marshland.
Ten minutes ago,
I was knee-deep
in liquefied human feces.
And that was just on the F train.
I can't believe Ted's getting
back together with Zoey.
- They're a total train wreck.
- Unmitigated disaster.
Worst couple ever.
Yeah, almost as bad as us.
We were a mess.
Do you remember how awful
I looked by the end?
My hair was falling out,
my skin was gray,
my back was hunched.
What about me?
I got so fat,
at the end of a date,
you'd unhook my bra.
You were the only boyfriend
I ever motorboated.
Thank God we're not sentimental saps
who panic and get back together.
Seriously,
why would people do that?
I guess I get it.
What do you mean?
Well, no matter how bad things got...
Ted really did love Zoey
for a minute there.
Didn't he?
He did.
She loved him, too.
Didn't she?
Yeah, she did.
Smith and Ninth Street.
Let me show you some of the
gut-wrenching environmental atrocities
that we were working to stop, okay?
Here, pop quiz.
What is that?
That's a seal.
A bloated seal corpse
rotting in industrial waste.
Now, wait till you see what we found
when we cut him open.
- Okay, where the hell are they?
- Maybe this isn't the intersection.
Maybe it is and we're too late. Man,
I wish we'd gone to Brooklyn sooner.
I know, right?
Ever since the Trader Joe's
opened up,
Brooklyn is so... whatever.
Wait. Where'd you get that?
Across the street
at the Intersection.
So...
You guys...
wanna buy some weed or...?
She's alone! There's still time!
But where the hell is Ted?
Wait a minute. On their first date,
he brought her an orchid.
How much do you want to bet
he's gonna do it again?
Brilliant. But wait,
he had a huge head start on us.
No way he's still in there unless
he spent an hour choosing an orchid.
Thanks, Julia!
You know what?
Let me see
the pink lady slipper again.
Now, do you know what that is?
A pile of rotting seagull carcasses
covered in toxic sludge.
Being eaten by rats. Exactly.
Now this next slide...
I'm sorry.
That's my wife's water birth.
I don't know how that got in there.
Anyway, that's all my questions.
Oh, my God, I made it!
Now just shake his hand,
clench your very soul
and run like hell!
I like to take 20 minutes at the end
of every interview for your questions.
So don't hold back.
Whatever you got inside there,
you just let her rip.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm just gonna tell him the truth.
When it's stomach stuff,
you just say "Under the weather"
or people start picturing you
doing unspeakable things.
I have food poisoning
and I'm about to start volcanoing
toxic sludge out of both ends!
Nailed it.
Thanks, Julia!
No, on second thought.
- Come on.
- What the hell?!
You can't get back with Zoey
over a lightbulb.
I'm not freaking out
over a lightbulb!
I'm freaking out over
50,000 lightbulbs!
I can't do this!
I only got this job because
you gave it to me, Barney.
I didn't earn it!
The future is scary.
But you can't just run back to the past
because it's familiar.
Yes, it's tempting.
But...
It's a mistake.
You're right.
Excuse me.
Can you give this to the blonde
sitting alone in there
and tell her Ted's really sorry?
Also...
Indirect sunlight. Don't overwater.
Half a cup a week is more than enough.
And kids...
that's how I met your mother.
Psych. It was just some chick.
Hey, baby, how'd it go?
Lily, this year,
this nasty schoolyard bully of a year
will not stop punching me
in the face.
How did we kick off 2011?
My dad died.
And now after five months
of unemployment,
I just blew my dream job.
The good news is, in a few seconds,
I'm gonna start heaving my guts out
because that's what life is
for me now,
just losing what's inside
until I'm just empty.
Baby, come here.
I just want to shut my eyes
for a few seconds before it starts.
And Marshall slept...
... all night.
Who's gonna do the honors?
He is.
You sure?
You earned it.
All clear!
New is always better, right?
Always.
Ten,
nine, eight...
It's a miracle.
I didn't get sick.
I know, baby.
I'm pregnant.
I'm proud of you
for giving Ted the button.
It meant a lot.
It's just a button.
Can we talk about
something else, please?
How you been?
Fine.
I don't know why you would possibly
say yes to this, but,
would you want to grab
a cup of coffee with me sometime?
20 minutes.
I was such a jerk to you.
You can spend the entire time calling
me every dirty name in the book.
I speak four languages.
I'm gonna need more than 20 minutes.
I'll call you.
You look beautiful, by the way.
And here I thought
it was too late for sundresses.
It's never too late, Barney.
Challenge accepted.
Best man?
You're being summoned.
Geez, what now?
I heard the groom needed me.
What do you think of this tie?
www.tvsubtitles.net