Kids, in the fall of 2010,
it seemed like Aunt Lily could only
talk about one thing,
babies.
God, I have been craving
this burger all day.
Do you know what plays a huge role
in helping a woman conceive?
Cervical mucus.
God, I can't wait to see this movie.
I hear it's really scary.
Change of plans.
I thought violent images
wouldn't be good for my future fetus,
so instead, I rented
this video of a live water birth.
They don't know what it is.
It just showed up on my mom's X-ray.
Look at this crib.
But all in all, it wasn't a problem.
That is, until the night
of Barney's boutonniere.
- You're wearing a flower.
- Thank you.
- Didn't compliment. Just observed.
- I know.
- Why are you wearing that?
- Why does Barney do anything ever?
Exactly. Science.
There is an 83% correlation
between the times men wear boutonnieres
and the times they get laid.
Think about it. Proms,
weddings,
grandmas' funerals,
thanks for the redhead, Nana.
The "everyday boutonniere"
by Stinson.
And nope.
I'm sorry, Barney,
but no girl is going home
with a guy with a flower
on his chest.
Unless he's a clown,
and she's in the trunk of his car.
Along with 50 other clowns.
It's a clown car.
Robin, did you know that boutonniere
is French for "bootie is near?"
True story.
Une histoire vraie.
Did you know that Barney is French
for "sad little guy who works
way too hard to get laid".
- Woman, you best check yourself.
- On the bright side,
I guess suits are pretty boring
without them, so...
Madam,
that is an insult
that cannot be borne!
I demand satisfaction!
What, are we gonna duel?
No. I'm gonna show everyone
this embarrassing video of you.
It's Robin Sparkles III, y'all!
Team Who's this fucking mother ?
Synchronisation :
Kyros, MiniBen314, Strex
Adaptation :
Dark_Chii, H3AV3N, Kenji, TTT
Relecture : MiniBen314, Titou
6x09 - Glitter (1.00)
.:: www.sous-titres.eu ::.
Kids, by this point, we knew Aunt Robin
had been a teen pop sensation
in Canada, known as Robin Sparkles.
And we also knew
that her Robin Sparkles character
came from a Canadian TV show,
which we'd never seen...
until now.
I cannot wait
to see what's on this DVD!
- You haven't watched it yet?
- Of course not.
I wanted my first time to be
with someone I cared about.
I get that a lot.
Well, once.
Robin, do you want to go get
a Korean massage on Saturday?
I'd love to. I've got this knot
in my neck that's so annoying.
I figured I should get one now
because once I get pregnant,
no more massages.
Just so annoying.
Space Teens?
Is this a porno?
- No, dude.
- Sweet!
It's a kids' show.
This does have
all the earmarks of porn.
Stripper pole, bad lighting,
delusional girl who thinks
it's a stepping stone to success.
Yeah, it's a big old bowl
of "pornflakes".
And who is this exquisite keytarist
I assume you're about
to make love to?
That's Jessica Glitter. She was my BFF
on the show and in real life.
BFFs.
Did you guys have sleepovers?
Get mad at each other and wrestle,
but then end up kissing
in a tender embrace?
Show us on Lily.
If you're gonna be disgusting,
we're not watching this.
Come on, Barney.
It's just a cute little story about...
What exactly is this about?
Two average Canadian teenagers
who solve crimes in space using math.
That sounds ridiculous.
So sue me.
Like the producers
of Milky Way Mathletes tried to.
Great job using long division
to catch that space burglar, eh?
What can I say?
He'll be in galactic jail
for the remainder of his life.
Sparkles, Glitter, we're about
to enter an asteroid belt, eh.
Brace for turbulence!
I have to say, as much as I hate
to agree with Barney,
this does seem to be
a veritable "pornucopia".
Guys, come on.
It's a kids' show!
Like Electric Company
or Sesame Street or...
- You can't do that on television.
- Exactly.
You can't do that on television!
This show is so dirty,
I don't know whether to hug you
or run a shower so you can sit there
alone, crying and clenching your knees.
It's just bad camera work, okay?
Wayne, our camera guy,
he wasn't that great.
I don't know. He did a pretty good job,
considering he was only using one hand.
You know what?
I feel bad for you Americans,
that you can look at this wondrous
and educational adventure through space,
and see something obscene.
Can you just,
please, try to look at this
with the innocence of a child?
- Innocence of a child.
- Coming up. Here we go.
Girls, if you want to get through
the asteroid belt, you've got
to use multiplication.
To the joystick!
Okay, Space Teens, let's multiply!
Five times six?
30.
Seven times four?
- 28!
- Keep going!
Eight times nine?
- 72!
- Don't stop now!
Almost there!
23 times three?
I'm sorry.
We got to ration this.
It's like we're on a desert island,
and this video is a really hot,
naked chick, and she's got, like,
seaweed on her and a seashell bra.
You all feel me?
If you and Jessica are BFFs,
how come we've never met her?
It was a long time ago, okay?
I get a Christmas card
from her every year, but,
we're not really friends anymore.
But BFFs are forever.
Come on, Lily. Nobody stays friends
with their high school friends.
- I'm still friends with Punchy.
- Dude, he lives in Cleveland.
You see him once a year,
at which point,
he punches you really
hard in the arm
and tells everyone
how you dookied your pants.
I know, on paper he sounds great,
but you guys aren't really friends.
Look, I may not see him a lot,
but it doesn't matter.
Observe.
- Schmosby!
- Punchy!
- Good talking to you.
- You, too.
- If you're ever in New York.
- Definitely.
We are just two peas.
I don't get it. How can you
and Glitter just stop being friends?
Best friends don't do that.
We did. And I haven't talked to her
in, like, five years, so just drop it.
I got to go.
What do you think came
between Robin and Jessica?
Much like our friends,
the Space Teens,
I think I can solve this crime
with math.
Here is a Christmas card
that Jessica sent Robin.
- How old would you say that kid is?
- Four years, three months.
Which means Jessica got pregnant
five years ago, right around the time
- she and Robin stopped being friends.
- Of course. Robin hates kids.
The last thing she would wanna do
is hang out with some little brat.
Thus, if I may...
When Glitter's womb
a fruit did bear,
Robin said,
"To hell with this, I'm outta hare."
Glitter got pregnant,
so Robin dumped her.
That's got to be it, right, Lil?
Robin's gonna dump me!
Sweetheart.
When a second uterus
plumped becomes...
Dude.
Feel the room.
We've been waiting all day!
Just watch it without me.
Two dudes on the couch together
watching porn? That's kind of weird.
It's not porn, it's a kids' show.
Two dudes watching a kids'
show might be worse.
Fine, I'll watch it with you.
But if either of you makes
even one peep about the show
being dirty, I'm turning it off.
I'm serious.
Jessica, how's your beaver?
Great.
How's your beaver?
Busy as ever!
Our characters had pet beavers.
Sure.
The beaver
is the official animal of Canada.
It's our national mascot.
It's a noble creature.
Okay, girls. Everyone knows
a beaver's favorite food is wood.
I just hope we brought along
enough of it
for our three-day
galactic space journey.
So let's do the math.
If Robin's beaver devours
six inches of wood every half hour,
and Jessica's beaver devours
eight inches of wood every 45 minutes,
how much wood will I need
to keep both of these beavers
well-fed all weekend long?
While you figure it out at home,
how about we sing you a song
about our beavers?
You don't get to hear the beaver song!
It is a sweet song about friendship,
and you guys are being disgusting,
and beavers are adorable!
No arguments here.
'Sup Shmosby!
Punchy, what are you doing here?
Yesterday you said
if I was ever in New York.
'Sup, turds?
Okay...
Where are you staying?
In your mom's pants.
Trick. She's old.
Don't worry about me.
I'm cool on the couch.
He's staying here?
You're staying here?
I know! It's so good, right?
Feel like you're dreaming?
But check your totem, brah.
Punchy's here in the flesh.
So, why don't we get
one of these, Ted?
Remember these?
High school? Junior high?
- Elementary school? Remember those?
- Look, look, Punchy's here.
Schmosby, remember when you dookied
in your pants down by the lake?
Unbelievable!
Schmosby, remember when
you dookied on our couch
in the form of your idiot
high school friend?
Unbelievable!
Come on. I worry about the guy.
He's had the same dead-end job
at a car rental place for 15 years.
- Don't care.
- He's been stuck in Cleveland
- his whole life.
- Get a hotel.
LeBron.
Okay, one night.
Gotta go.
- Where are you going? We just got here.
- A Korean massage.
- By yourself?
- Well, I figured you'd be busy,
reading What to Expect
When You're Expecting to Expect.
Guys, did you see that?
She's going
to a Korean massage without me.
That's our thing.
I'm telling you,
she's gonna dump me,
just like she dumped Glitter.
Lily, come on. We don't even
know that's what happened.
Hello, somebody already solved
that crime using math, remember?
Look, Lily.
Robin is clearly getting tired
of you constantly
talking about babies.
I don't.
- How old am I?
- 384 months.
Busted!
So before you Lily all over the place,
maybe you should
try hanging out with Robin
and not talking about babies.
So Lily did just that.
She tried not to talk about babies.
Lily, what brings you to the crib?
- Crib...
- What's the matter? You look rattled.
Rattled?
- I want to talk about babies.
- What?
Look, I know you don't
care about this stuff,
but I'm about to become a mother.
And as a future mother,
I'm gonna need the support...
Oh, my God!
You're not even pregnant yet.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that a fertilized egg
has not yet attached itself
to the lining of your uterine wall.
You see?
I read your Facebook updates.
It's like it's all you ever
talk about, Lily, and I'm sick of it!
Well, guess what?
I've got some good news.
When that baby comes,
you don't have to see it. In fact,
you don't have to see me.
This whole friendship thing?
Done.
- Great.
For crying out loud.
You broke up with Robin?
I had to.
We were growing apart, and,
we're better off without each other.
Lily, you sound about
as convincing as you did
the time you "accidentally" shredded
my Joey Buttafuoco pants.
Get on the phone, call Robin
- and fix this.
- I can't.
The damage is done.
Can you just hold me?
You know what? No.
I don't agree with what you did,
and so I refuse to comfort you,
despite how adorable you are
when you cry.
Okay. Maybe just one cuddle,
but then that is it.
Times Square's the bomb!
I got so many great pictures
of all the billboards.
You know, there's more to New York
than Times Square.
There's the Village,
the Lower East Side, Central Park...
They got better billboards
then the ones in Times Square?
Times Square's the bomb!
Here. You know what?
Hold this, okay?
I'm going to go pee in the jar
I got going in the alley.
Seriously, dude, he has got to go.
You need to be like,
"You are the weakest link.
Goodbye."
Punchy, the tribe has spoken.
Please pack up your knives and go.
Your work of art didn't work for us.
Your time's up.
I have to ask you
to leave the mansion.
You must leave the chateau.
Your tour ends here.
You've been chopped.
Yeah. I know.
You've been evicted
from the Big Brother house.
Your dessert just didn't measure up.
Sashay away.
Give me your jacket
and leave Hell's Kitchen.
I'm sorry, you did not get a rose.
You have been eliminated
from the race.
You are no longer in the running
to be America's Next Top Model.
You're fired.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Come look at this.
I found a little wounded
bird in the alley.
That's your scrotum.
You know what it is.
Come on, Ted.
You always fall for that.
Yeah, he's gotta go.
What are we doing
in Madison Square Garden?
You refused to talk to Robin so
I thought you might like to talk to...
the organist
for the New York Rangers.
Jessica Glitter?
- How did you find Glitter?
- Simple, really.
I used my powers of deduction.
I knew Glitter used to be a keytarist,
which is basically a piano, so
I made a list of all the keyboard-based
occupations and I cross-matched them...
His friend Barney looked me up,
hoping to buy my Space Teens costume.
Yo, Glitter...
be cool.
Is this the one who's best friend's
with Robin now?
More like ex-best friends.
Just like you.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I miss Robin.
Well, Marshall and I
are about to get pregnant,
and I know she stopped being friends
with you when you had a baby, so...
Robin didn't stop
being friends with me.
I stopped being friends with her.
What?
Why?
Because I had a baby.
Honey, when you have a baby,
all that best friend stuff...
hockey, bow hunting
for caribou, math,
that all goes out the window.
I tried to stay friends with her,
but it just didn't happen.
She took it pretty hard.
I even thought
she might try to kill herself.
Charge!
You dumped her
just because you had a baby?
That's cold.
Didn't you do the same thing?
Minus the baby?
I gotta go.
I gotta go apologize to Robin.
I need to tell her I love her,
and that she'll always be a priority.
Be careful, Lily.
I made those promises, too.
And now I haven't even
talked to her in five years.
Sure, I thought about
picking up the phone
and calling her a hundred times,
but I just never have
the courage to...
Go ahead.
Do you guys get Big Chuck
and Little John out here?
- Punchy, it's time to go back.
- Back to Times Square?
Back to Cleveland.
I don't know if I can do that, bro.
I mean, yeah, I've been jonesing for
a piece of Cleveland-style pizza, but,
I feel bad
about leaving you out here.
I worry about you, Ted.
You worry about me?
Yeah.
The other day when you called...
- Schmosby!
- Punchy!
- Good talking to you.
- You too.
- If you're ever in New York...
- Definitely.
- Sweetie, who was that?
- It was my friend Ted.
He sounded kind of depressed.
The Ted who got left at the altar?
He's not doing so good.
Poor guy lives
in a tiny apartment in New York,
nowhere near Times Square.
He's got no family around.
He's still single,
doesn't have a backyard.
It's just a bummer.
Maybe you should go visit him.
Cheer him up a little.
You know, buy him some shots,
do the whole wounded bird trick.
You think that'd work?
Worked on me.
She sounds pretty great, Punchy.
She's my angel.
In fact...
we're getting married.
That's...
I'm really happy for you.
Thanks, Ted. Thanks.
Actually, that's the other reason
why I came out here.
I wanted to see
if you'd be my best man.
Of course I will.
That's great!
No, you're stupid.
Dawg pound.
That's it...
That night, Lily went to the one place
she knew she could find Robin,
New York's premiere Canadian bar,
the Hoser Hut.
There you are.
Robin, I owe you a huge apology.
Me first.
I've been pulling away from you,
and I'm sorry. It's just...
The last time
my best friend had a baby...
I know.
I know all about it.
It's not gonna happen
with you and me.
And I'm sorry I've been crazy
with this baby stuff.
I know you hate babies.
Look, I hate most babies.
But your baby?
I'm gonna love that kid so much.
I'm gonna pick it up and everything.
I'm so happy you guys made up.
Me, too.
Where do I know this song from?
My God, it's the beaver song.
Which one of you put this on?
Hey, beaver, come on
When you feel alone
Just pick up that phone
And I'll be there to share my
Ice cream cone
We'll lick it side by side
- This is so dirty.
- Come on, Barney.
- It's a sweet song about friendship.
- Yeah, dude, come on.
Day is done
Two beavers are better than one
They're twice the fun
Ask anyone
A second beaver can be
Second to none
Two beavers are better than one.
You're my favorite beaver...
Two beavers are better than one
They're twice the fun
Ask anyone
A second beaver can be
Second to none
Two beavers are better than one.
www.tvsubtitles.net