NARRATOR: Kids, when Aunt Lily
went into labor,
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com to download
Marshall was somewhere
slightly inconvenient,
in Atlantic City
with Uncle Barney,
and drunk to the point of
talking like Yoda.
Baby come...
Papa gonna be am I...
Hospital must we get now...
Okay, there's like a four-hour
wait at the valet stand.
Plus, we're in no shape to
drive. So, a car's out...
Wait, don't worry. We'll take
a cab to the train station.
MAN: Yeah, good luck
getting a cab.
It's impossible because
of the big thing.
NARRATOR: Kids, for the life of
me, I can't remember
what the big thing was in
Atlantic City that weekend.
SON: Was it
a cheerleading convention?
NARRATOR: No, it was
a porn convention.
Sci-fi convention?
Eh, I can't remember.
We're stuck in Atlantic City!
City of Atlantic stuck in are we.
♪ How I Met Your Mother 7x23 ♪
The Magician's Code
Original Air Date on May 13, 2012
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com to download
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Okay, Lily,
it's going to be fine.
We are not freaking out.
We are not freaking out!
I feel calmer already.
Let's get you to the hospital.
Oh, I can't go yet.
I talked to Dr. Sonya.
They won't admit me
until my contractions
are four minutes apart.
Okay, well, if you
don't make it in time,
I have got you covered. When I
was 13, my father caught me
kissing a boy, so he sent me
to our family's ranch
for foaling season.
Once you see a baby horse
erupt through that birth canal,
you stop even touching yourself.
Anyway, I had skinny arms,
so I got up there elbow deep.
I lost this watch
birthing Blacky...
Okay, stop it. I am not
a farm animal. (mooing)
Oh, there we go.
Easy girl. Sugar cube? (moaning)
Oh, okay.
Ah, don't worry, Lil.
Some of us know what
a woman actually needs
at a time like this.
(panting) A kick-ass
labor announcement e-mail.
TED: A man,
a woman,
and their best friend,
embark on an
incredible journey.
Lily's cervix is dilating,
and we want you all
to be part of its
grand opening.
You are not sending that
to anyone, ever.
So what I need right now is
distraction from the pain.
Just tell me a story.
Uh, what story?
I don't care. Anything.
How about the worst
cab ride ever?
HOMELESS GUY:
Clean your window for you? - No!
Hey, get off my cab!
(grunting)
(blows landing)
Oh! Oh, God!
(loud thud)
Oh! Ah!
(Ted and Robin gasping)
(both screaming)
(screaming)
We are not panicking!
Get on all fours;
it widens your hind quarters.
Stop it! I am not
a farm animal!
But give me that sugar cube.
Okay, listen, I am going to
get you to that hospital
or die trying.
And if I succeed,
I ask only one thing in return.
Let me choose
your child's middle name.
Because I have thought up the
most awesome name of all time.
What's the middle name?
Wait for it...
I'm waiting.
I said I'm waiting.
Wait for it.
What's the middle name?
No, the middle name is
"Wait For It."
Let's say his first name is,
oh, I don't know, Barney.
He'd be Barney
"Wait For It" Eriksen.
How awesome is that?
That is...
the coolest...
middle name of all time.
I know!
Okay, listen.
I have a plan
to get us to New York.
All we have to do is get our
hands on that motorcycle.
And I know just the way
to do it.
(both sigh)
(phone rings)
Here.
Oh. Hi, Judy.
Oh, good.
You got the e-mail from Ted.
No, I am not worried my
city hips are too narrow,
and-and your grandson's
going to get stuck.
I got to go.
I thought you deleted
that stupid e-mail.
Okay, I sent it by accident.
She like it?
Yes!
Just keep telling me stories!
Okay, okay, I got one for you:
second base with Neil Young.
Um, (chuckles)
I don't normally go to, um,
second base and tell,
but I just spent
a magical night with Neil Young.
(whispers):
He's still in my room.
Seriously?
Oh, my God.
Be quiet, don't scare him off.
(clears throat)
He-Hey...
Robin...
Yeah.
That's not Neil Young.
Oh, God.
(both laughing)
Oh, we're busting apple bags?
I can bust apple bags.
Ted, remember when we were
dating and we threw that party
and one of those appetizers
just didn't sit right?
Ah... doesn't sound familiar.
I call this story "Ted and
the Cuban Sandwich Crisis."
(toilet flushes)
ROBIN: Ted came out of that
bathroom looking like
Joe Frazier after
the Thrilla in Manila.
Oh, what is that smell!?
Ugh!
So I, being a great girlfriend,
tried to help him out.
You guys are all crazy;
I don't smell anything.
Anyway, uh, who wants to
go up on the roof?
ROBIN: But then...
She, who denied it, supplied it.
Yeah, must have been that
Cuban sandwich, huh, babe?
(both chuckle)
That was not cool, Ted.
Contraction!
That wasn't cool, Ted?
(grunting): Just keep going
with the stories.
I don't even care
if I've heard it before.
Just tell me, uh,
"Where Does That Door Go?"
Okay.
Hey, I've never noticed
that door before.
I wonder where it goes.
Ted.
No, no, no, let him...
let him...
Wow...
Don't...
No...
Robi....
Oh...
Wow...
(cell phone rings)
Dad, oh, good.
Let me guess,
you got Ted's e-mail.
I'm on my way, Princess.
Dad, wait, no, not...
Damn it, Ted.
I was okay with you e-mailing
my aunt, my cousins,
and your cousins, and the guy
that Robin thought was Neil Young.
But my father is the absolute
worst person to have around
in any sort of
medical situation.
LILY:
When I was seven, I needed
to have my tonsils out.
Daddy, I'm scared.
Aw, Princess, I would be too.
I've researched this surgery.
Anything can happen.
You could bleed to death...
...you could have your jaw
removed due to infection,
and the anesthesia could
suddenly just stop working,
much like your mom's
and my marriage.
(laughing)
You do know that we're
getting a divor...
Don't worry about it. We'll talk
about it after the surgery.
Calm down, girl.
(panting)
Okay, for the last time,
I am not...
Actually, keep going.
Okay, I admit the whole "win a
motorcycle plan" was stupid.
Especially because we've been
playing on the wrong machine.
BARNEY: New plan:
Meet me at the entrance
in five minutes.
(engine revs)
Hop on, Marshall.
Tonight, we ride!
You won that?
Not exactly. You see, I...
Get off!
(grunting)
I hope Marshall's close.
Cube me.
I'm on my way, Lily Pad.
NARRATOR:
Kids, your Uncle Marshall
has faced many challenges
in his life.
But he still considers
getting up these two steps
when he was this drunk to be
the hardest one of all.
Tell me a Marshall story.
I miss him.
Got it.
"The Tale of the Cursed Pants."
Hey, guys. (chuckles)
So, I'm starting worry
about these pants.
Starting to?
No, ever since I got them,
terrible things
have been happening to me:
I stubbed my toe,
I missed my train...
You put on the pants.
(all chuckle) And then the lady at the thrift
store said that for years,
no one so much as tried them on.
Can you believe that?
Yes.
You know what this means?
These pants are cursed.
What's this in the pocket?
A clue.
TED: Marshall had
the writing translated.
It led him deep
into the heart of Chinatown.
(gasps) It is you.
The One has arrived.
Dry cleaning, $21.50.
I remember that suit.
He looked like
a little kid's imaginary friend.
(chuckles)
Where is he?!
NARRATOR: Now, Uncle Marshall
knew he had only one chance
of getting out
of Atlantic City:
bribing a cab driver.
Machine that gives money!
(chuckles)
NARRATOR: Now, Marshall
was pretty drunk,
but he swears the ATM
started to do this.
(video game sound effect)
(beeps)
(laughing)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Stop
hitting me. Just for that,
you're never getting home
for the birth of your son.
(shredding sounds)
No!!
What's up, bro?
Wait, how did you...
with the security?
I'll explain.
(grunts)
Tell me why we shouldn't
call the authorities...
right now?
Go ahead, call 'em.
But first, can you show me
the rule that says you can't
drive a motorcycle
on the casino floor?
(chuckles)
It's not in here.
NARRATOR: And, kids, that sign
is still there to this day.
When I came out,
I ran into this guy.
Two seats just opened up
on his bus to New York!
Barney, you're a genius!
Plus, here's the best part.
This Quinn thing is probably
done, so I'm basically single.
He said the bus is full of
hot college seniors.
Okay, maybe he didn't
say "college."
Or "hot."
I miss Quinn.
(groans)
What is taking Marshall so long?
Salt lick?
Just finish the door story!
Oh, wow.
I don't like this.
(groaning) Okay, okay, that's
four minutes!
We're going to
the hospital.
W-Wait, but Marshall's
not here yet.
I can't go to the hospital
without Marshall!
I'm on it.
Lily, spread your legs.
I'm gonna see if we can
see the hooves--
uh, the-the snout--
uh, the head.
Here we go.
Take me to the hospital now.
Okay. Come
on, come on.
Excuse me, sir.
My wife is in labor,
and I really need to
get to Saint Marcus Hospital.
So where exactly in New York
does this bus drop off?
Buffalo.
What do you mean
I can't have an epidural?
You're too far along.
Things are moving much faster
than expected.
Look, if your hands
are tied medically,
just leave the epidural
on the table and walk away.
Don't worry.
The baby slide right out, huh?
It's like a whoosh.
(chuckles)
Like a waterslide.
(screaming)
Slightly painful
waterslide.
(sobbing)
Tell me a story now!
Uh...
Oh! Remember the time Barney
tried to pick up girls
as the Terminator?
Yes.
♪ ♪
(à la Schwarzenegger): Come
with me if you want to bang.
Another.
Oh, uh, Ted and the
freakishly long arm hair!
No, I disagree,
because the filling--
It depends on
what you're eating, right?
If it's...
Whoa. What the...?
ROBIN and MARSHALL:
Whoa.
(groaning) The debunking of the
freakishly long arm hair.
Wait, it's-it's
just a thread.
I was jealous, okay?
Barney's getting all
the attention today
with this
Terminator thing.
Huh. Can't believe I'm not
getting laid in this thing.
Maybe I need to pick
a different part of the movie.
♪ ♪
(high-pitched screaming)
Tell me another story!
Oh, hey, we never finished
"Where does that door go""
Come on.
Let's check it out.
You know what, baby,
they're gone.
It's time for us
to move on.
L-Lil...
Oh, my God.
(screaming)
New story!
Uh, the time we tested
if banana peels are
really slippery.
Yes.
Ready?
There's no way
that's really slippery.
(grunts)
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Uh, the Halloween we decided
to go as The Breakfast Club,
but failed to coordinate
our costumes!
Uh...
Does...
Oh.
(groans)
(sighs)
Really?
I mean, you live with me, Lily.
Yeah, that was funny.
Keep going!
Oh, uh, uh...
the-the time Barney
saved a woman's life.
Ready?
There's no way
that's really slippery.
(grunts)
(screaming)
Uh, the time Lily
went into labor!
That's now!
Sorry, I'm running
out of stories.
Forget it!
They're not working anymore!
Okay, Lily, I know this
isn't how you imagined it,
but I want
you to know
that I am here for you
and I am rock solid!
Oh, I can see its head.
Oh, thank God,
Dr. Sonya!
You!
Get that thing
out of my delivery room!
Weak women
disgust me.
All right, Lily, legs up!
We push now, yes?!
I can't.
Marshall's not here yet.
Lily!
If you don't push,
I will shove that baby
up your throat
and pull it out of your mouth!
(screaming)
Where the hell is Marshall?!
I can't do this
without Marshall!
NARRATOR: Kids, sometimes the universe
sends exactly what you ask for.
Other times,
it sends Lily's dad.
(groaning):
Oh...
Remember the time
you had your tonsils out?
Yeah, yeah.
You scared the crap out of me.
Yes, I did, didn't I?
(laughs)
Oh, my.
But do you remember
what happened next?
And don't worry,
Princess,
if you permanently lose
the ability to speak,
we'll give you
a chalkboard.
You can hang it around your
neck on a little string.
Nurse, I don't know
who this strange man is.
Security!
What are you talking about?
I'm your daddy.
What do you mean...
Hey, fellas, come on!
I woke up in a Dumpster
of medical waste,
and I couldn't
have been prouder.
Because, much like
that Dumpster,
you had a lot of guts.
And you've used that bravery
every day of your life.
With or without
Marshall.
You're having
this baby.
Thanks, Dad.
That story actually helped.
Oh, good, I'm glad.
And, you know, few women have
vaginal tearing severe enough
to need surgical
reconstruction...
Security!
Oh, come on.
That's not necessary.
Sweetheart, please...
Oh, fellas, come on.
Please, sir,
all you have to do
is take the next exit
to Manhattan.
You'll be back
on the road in 20 minutes.
I already told you,
I'm not allowed to stop.
Sir, this man is
having a baby tonight.
And instead of going
to Saint Marcus Hospital,
we're going to Buffalo.
And I've seen women from there;
the city's aptly named.
Look, I'm a screwup.
I had something special
with this girl Quinn,
and I ruined it.
But this guy--
he's done everything right.
He's been loving and devoted
since he was 18 years old.
There are only a few truly great
people on this planet,
and he is one of them.
He deserves to be
at the birth of his son.
So... what do you say?
Unless there's an emergency,
I'm not allowed to stop,
so sit down, watch
Cocoon 2 and shut up.
I'm sorry,
buddy, I tried.
NARRATOR: And then, something
wonderful happened.
I'm having a heart attack!
I'm having a
heart attack!
I'm having a heart attack!
And my doctor is
at Saint Marcus Hospital!
MAN:
So is mine!
Mine, too.
And my son is head
of Cardiology.
ALL:
We know!
Push!
I wish Marshall were here!
(panting):
I'm here, baby.
Marshall!
I don't know why
I passed out.
I have delivered
12 perfectly healthy babies,
and one of them was even human.
Well, it's different
when it's someone you love.
When that head was coming
out of your best friend.
Oh, stop.
I'm feeling woozy again.
Don't.
Salt lick?
In return for him getting me
here, I may have promised Barney
that our son's middle name
will be Wait For It.
I can't wait, just--
what is the name?
The name is
Wait For It.
(screaming)
That is the coolest middle name
of all time!
Look, um,
I know things have been weird
between us the last few months,
but...
Marshall and Lily
are having a baby.
Yeah.
And, you know,
I want this baby to be born
into a world where we're okay.
So, friends?
I love you, Robin.
Kidding.
You...
Friends.
(both laugh)
Guys, great news
from down the hall.
One dollar,
two bags of gummy bears!
It's like, I don't even care
what happens
for the rest of the day.
I...
Hey.
Well, guys, uh...
(sighs)
I'm a dad.
(laughs):
Oh, my God!
(cheering)
Everybody,
this is Marvin.
We named him after my pop.
Tell them the
full name.
Marvin Wait For It Eriksen.
That is the coolest
middle name of all-time.
Totally.
♪ You were born into
a strange world ♪
♪ Like a candle, you were meant
to share the fire ♪
♪ I don't know where we come
from, I don't know where we go ♪
♪ But my arms were made
to hold you ♪
♪ So I will never let you go ♪
♪ 'Cause you were born ♪
♪ To change this life,
you were born. ♪
♪ How I Met Your Mother 7x24 ♪
The Magician's Code, pt2
Original Air Date on May 14, 2012
(exhales)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
ALL: Boo!
(screams)
NARRATOR:
Which brings us to the story
of a wedding day
that went horribly wrong.
Ted, the bride wants to see you.
Uncle Barney
was getting married.
How the hell did we get there?
I love the name Marvin.
Marv.
Sounds like a little
middle-aged man.
(chuckling)
Golf next
weekend, Marv?
How's that tax report
coming, Marv?
At your age,
erectile dysfunction
is nothing to be
ashamed of, Marv.
It was a beautiful moment.
But then a thought popped
into my head, kids.
The same thought that will pop
into your heads
the first time you see your
best friend holding their baby.
(staple gun clicks)
Wonder how much this would hurt.
(chuckles)
(staple gun clicks)
(screaming)
That guy's a dad.
(baby crying)
Oh, I think he's hungry.
Oh, we'll give
you some privacy.
Wow. Seeing them in there
all together like that,
they're a family,
you know?
That's what I want.
Oh, Ted, I'm glad
we're friends again.
Me, too.
Because as your friend,
I have to tell you:
You're full of crap!
You say you want a family,
you say
you want to meet "The One,"
but you are always chasing
the wrong women.
That is not true.
Look at the women you date,
starting with me:
I told you right away
I didn't want marriage or kids.
Stella had a child with another
man who she still loved.
Zoey was married and trying
to sabotage your career
and wore a lot of stupid hats.
If you really wanted a family,
you would stop pursuing women
you know that
there is no future with.
Okay, first of all,
hats were in that year, kind of.
Secondly, I don't
always choose women
there's no future with, kind of.
Name one exception.
Victoria.
TED: Victoria was great.
Exactly,
and you threw it all away
to chase after some hot piece
of ass. (scoffs)
You mean you?
Thank you!
Victoria is the only
woman you've dated
who could've been "The One."
You should call her.
Tiny thing, last time I saw her,
she was getting engaged.
That was eight months ago.
For all you know,
she's single again.
What if she's married?
What if she's not?
Then you would actually
have a chance
to get what you say you want,
and it terrifies you.
Why? Because if I stole a
scalpel and I cut you open,
all I would find inside is a
scared, trembling pile of crap.
See, I've missed these talks.
Oh, me, too.
Yeah.
Whoa.
What's wrong?
(sighs)
I ruined things with Quinn.
I insisted she stop stripping,
we got in a huge fight about it,
then I ran off to Atlantic City
for two days without calling.
What the hell
am I coming home to?
Let's have an eight-way with
my six hottest stripper friends.
Um, how is that a punishment?
Wait for it.
But I forbid you from filming it
with your overhead camera
that zooms in
on whoever's being the loudest.
Nooooo!
(shudders)
No, that's too cruel.
Or, you know,
maybe Quinn's moved out.
I didn't even think of that!
(sighs)
Hi.
Welcome home.
I decided the place was a bit
too "American Psycho" for me,
so while you were gone,
I hired a decorator
and I asked him,
"What would the inside
of Tinkerbell's vagina
look like?"
And the kid just ran with it!
So... what do you think?
Thank God you're still here!
Welcome home.
NARRATOR: Lily and Marshall asked Robin
to be the photographer
for Baby Marvin's
Birth Announcement card
instead of me.
Whatever.
The only problem?
(camera snapping)
These are terrible, Robin!
Hey, it is not easy
getting a good shot
cooped up in this apartment!
See, two different styles:
I make compositions,
Robin makes excuses.
Click!
Photo burn!
Okay. How about this?
Tomorrow, we go
to Central Park at sunset
and we get the perfect picture
in the perfect setting.
Oh, I like that.
It'll be Marvin's first
outing into the world.
You're gonna love
the park, buddy.
It's a great place
to meet chicks.
Or-or dudes.
Or both.
Oh, we love you
no matter what!
NARRATOR: And kids, as I watched your
Aunt Lily hold her baby boy,
another thought
popped into my head.
Even though you
didn't buy anything,
I want to thank you
for coming in.
Here's a free teddy bear.
What are you gonna
name the little guy?
Six Pack.
Gun it, bitches!
(engine revs)
NARRATOR: That girl's a mom!
(engine revving)
(phone chimes)
Okay, so I met this girl
on the train,
and I texted her, "What's up""
She texted,
"Hey," exclamation point.
Does that mean,
"Ask me out" or "Just..."
Ted, we are responsible for
a whole other human life now,
so new rule: You can't come
to us with any issue unless
it's an "8" or higher.
Got it.
So I'm thinking of texting
back a winky smiley face.
Eight or higher, bro.
Well, no, what should I--
No, yeah,
I'm just wondering if--
Eight or higher, bro.
Well, where do you rate this?
This is the same as what's in
little Marvin's pants right now:
a soft two.
Sorry, bro.
Stop texting the bimbo
and call Victoria.
That chapter's over.
W-We just weren't destined
to be together.
"Destined." Aren't you tired
of waiting for destiny, Ted?
Isn't it time
to make your own destiny?
Hey, false alarm.
What I was smelling was
the previous poop,
which, apparently, is
still somewhere on my
clothes and/or in my hair.
Hold him, would you?
Oh. Here.
Ooh.
Yeah, smart.
(shutter clicking)
Oh, sure, that one
turns out great. Ugh.
NARRATOR: And then another thought popped
into my head:
That guy's nowhere
near being a dad.
(line ringing)
VICTORIA: Hello?
Hey, Victoria, it's Ted.
Um, listen, I was just wondering
if you wanted to catch up
sometime; it's been a while.
That sounds nice.
I'm actually around
this afternoon.
Oh, wow, uh, great.
MacLaren's at 2:00?
Is 1:30 okay?
I might have a thing later.
Yeah. Yeah. See you then.
See you then.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile, Barney
and Quinn were off to Hawaii
for their first getaway
as a couple.
Ma'am, I need you
to open your suitcase.
(sighing):
It's mine.
Did you have
to replace my luggage, too?
Run away on me again, you'll
be wearing hot pink stilettos.
What's that?
Yeah, what is that?
It's a magic trick.
You see, I'm something
of a magician.
Open the box, sir.
(laughing):
Oh, I can't do that.
(barking)
Sir, are there drugs
in that box?
Oh, no. He's probably
just barking
because of the explosives.
(gasps)
Oh, my God!
Tell us what's
in the box right now!
I can't.
Magician's Code.
TED: Okay, I need to figure out
if Victoria ever got engaged.
I'll have to very subtly
check for an engagement ring.
Hmm, can't see the left hand.
Open the box now!
I can't.
Magician's Code.
What the hell is
the Magician's Code?!
"A magician never
reveals his tricks."
Mr. Flanagan, my magic mentor
from the hallowed
Staten Island Mall Magic Shop,
taught me the importance
of the Code
one fateful autumn
night in 1993.
Always good to tell
a long story while people
are aiming guns at you.
'Twas a night which
would changed my life...
(thudding)
Hello? Mr. Flanagan.
Wh-What are you doing here?
Um...
I'm checking up on you.
Just to make sure
you're practicing your craft
or whatever.
That is an honor, sir.
And yeah, I promise,
I'm practicing.
But wait.
Why were you, why were you
going in my mom's room?
Uh... your mom's actually
helping me with a new trick.
That is so cool!
What is this trick?
Is it sawing a lady in half?
(wry chuckle)
Well, not sawing.
But actually,
the Magician's Code forbids me
from telling you anything else
about the trick.
LORETTA:
Wayne, come back to bed!
Okay, it involves a bed.
W-W-Wait. Can
you at least
tell me the name of this trick?
Sure, kid.
It's called--
The Disappearing Salami.
Mr. Flanagan's wife shot him
before he could ever tell me
what the trick was.
Yeah, that guy was
banging your mom.
Yup.
Totally.
Mr. Flanagan was not ban--
Oh, my God, he was.
Wait, why are you bringing
a magic trick to Hawaii anyway?
I was hoping to shoot up
to Honolulu
for the Worldwide
Magic Convention.
Don't worry. You'll
notice I was gone.
It's only three
14-hour days.
So on our romantic getaway
to help me forget about
you skipping town on me,
you're skipping town on me?!
Look Quinn, you're
very important to me,
but you're sharing my heart
with an equally important Miss.
Miss...
Direction.
What?
H...
Shoot him.
So what did you order?
Oh, just black coffee.
I like it that way, too.
Yeah, it just tastes
better to me.
I find that if the coffee beans
are good enough,
you really don't need--
Why are you in a wedding dress?!
Well, I'm sort of supposed to...
get married today.
All your friends and family
are waiting for you
in some church right now?
Well, not all; we had
five last-minute no-shows.
Well... six.
Mazel tov, Ted.
I was starting to think
this would never happen.
Oh, no, Mrs. Matsen--
MRS. MATSEN: I told
you he wasn't gay.
Wait, what?
I was tempted to leave Klaus
for you last fall.
The only thing holding me back
was the Robin of it all.
I know, and you were right,
but... but that's all over now.
She moved out-- I mean, we're
still friends, but that's over.
All these years, I never stopped
thinking about you, Ted.
I've got a car outside
if you're ready to drive off
into the sunset together.
But if you don't feel
the same way,
if you've closed the door on us,
just say the word...
and I'll go.
Barney, tell them the trick.
The only person I could possibly
reveal the trick to
is another magician.
Well, I'm a magician.
Prove it.
Whoo-hoo!
(gasps)
NARRATOR:
That's Barney's version.
Quinn said it was
a simple card trick.
Who's to say which
version was true?
Quinn's.
Quinn's version was true.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
Oh, that's really cool.
So what's the trick?
I can't say.
Magician's Code.
(gasps):
Ta-da...
da-da-da-da-da-da.
(cell phone ringing)
Hello.
Why did you make me
call Victoria?
She's here in a wedding dress.
I'm the verge of
ruining a wedding!
And Mrs. Madsen's friend
thinks I'm gay,
but let's put a pin
in that till later.
Oh, my God.
Victoria's at the bar with Ted.
That's a seven.
And she's in a wedding dress.
That's a ten.
We got a ten!
What are you gonna do?
Where is she right now?
So this dress, what's the cut?
Are we talking princess,
ball gown, column?
Right, 'cause it's a federal
crime to love weddings.
She's in the bathroom,
which I guess
takes forever with that
giant poufy skirt thing.
Ball gown. Thank you.
Four shots of tequila.
Ted, calm down.
Or not. This is your chance
to get the one who got away.
You want her,
she wants you,
what's the problem?
The problem is Victoria's in
the middle of a giant freak-out.
What if she winds up
regretting this decision?
She's going after Ted Mosby.
That's the best decision
she's ever made.
There you go.
Whoa. What was that?
What?
You said you wanted a picture
of Baby Marvin's first outing.
Our baby's first outing
was to a bar.
(gasps)
I dribble Cuervo
on Marv's soft spot.
Here she comes! Quick!
Oh, yeah.
Eggshell or cream?
Is it eggshell or cream?
So.
You... me...
riding off into the sunset.
Any thoughts?
One question:
FDR or Westside Highway,
what's the quickest
way to the sunset?
Man, I wind up in
these rooms a lot.
If we miss Hawaii because of
this, guess who's not doing
The Disappearing Salami
anytime soon?
I need to ask you both
a few questions.
Let's start with you.
Name?
Quinn Garvey.
Occupation?
Unemployed.
Well, well, well.
Look who's keeping secrets now.
Sir, I'll tell you her
occupation: stripper.
She insists she's proud of it,
but apparently not
proud enough to tell you.
Barney, I was going to surprise
you with this on our trip,
but... I quit.
You... did that for me?
Yes.
And now that you know
what I did for you,
and how much I care for you,
would you please
show him the trick?
Sorry. Magician's Code.
Where should we go?
Your place?
My place?
We could go on my honeymoon.
(laughs)
Just kidding.
Although, it is paid for.
I know where we should go.
Where?
Your wedding.
I'm taking you back.
I don't understand.
I thought you wanted this.
I do want this.
I've thought about you
so many times.
What might have been...
But I got left at the altar,
and it nearly killed me.
You're someone's fiancé,
and I have to respect that.
So let's hit a motel,
jam in a quickie,
and get you back
to your wedding.
(giggles)
It's the right thing to do.
Some part of me
needed to hear you say
that running away together
wasn't an option.
And now that I know that...
it's like I'm sobering up.
Is there any way
that we can just pretend
this never happened?
This never happened.
Mr. Flanagan wasn't
banging my mom.
Well.
Your flight left.
We need to hold Mr. Stinson
for further questioning.
But you're free to go.
Maybe I should.
Wait!
I'll show you the trick.
Sir!
May I please have
the silk handkerchief
in your top left breast pocket?
Well... I don't have...
(chuckles)
(clears throat)
Sim salabi ma...
sim salabi ma...
(gasps)
Relax, relax,
it's part of the trick.
How did you get that
through the X-Ray machine?
No questions from
the audience, please!
(chanting nonsense syllables)
What is that?
Madam, may I please have
the key on your necklace?
Oh!
(giggles)
(beeping)
Is that gonna explode?
What?
(screams)
(coughing)
Ahem.
(mock gasps)
What?
(loudly):
Will you marry me?
Yes.
(laughing)
Come on, guys.
We're losing the light
for Baby's Second First Outing.
NARRATOR: I hate to say it,
but Robin nailed it.
(door closes)
Hey.
Guys, we've got something to tell you.
Eight or higher, bro.
We're engaged.
That's a... that's a ten.
We got another ten!
Oh...
Wow, big day!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
How did this happen?
Oh... magic.
Oh.
Uh, not to ruin the moment,
but apparently little Marvin
is quite stunned by the news.
Well...
Yeah. Wow.
Yeah.
Do you guys mind
recounting this romantic tale
next to a Diaper Genie?
Oh, Marvin, you're about to
hear your first love story!
QUINN:
Once up on a time,
this creepy magic dude
was boning Barney's mom...
It's our last chance
to run away together.
Door's right there.
Yes, we'll start a new life.
Head for the border!
Canada!
Eh, Mexico.
Canada sucks.
Okay, well,
you're one-quarter Canadian,
so by that logic
you one-quarter suck.
I'm 100% awesome
and you know it.
Yeah, I do.
(clears throat)
Look, I-I hope this isn't weird,
or anything, because...
Barney...
I'm... I'm really happy for you.
Really?
♪ I listen to the wind ♪
Really.
♪ To the wind of my soul ♪
♪ Where I'll end up
well I think ♪
♪ Only God really knows ♪
♪ I've sat upon ♪
♪ The setting sun ♪
♪ But never never never... ♪
You just drove
right by the church.
I know.
♪ I never wanted water once ♪
♪ No, never, never, never ♪
♪ I listen to my words ♪
♪ But they fall far below ♪
The road to this day has had
a few twists and
turns, hasn't it?
Yeah. Just a few.
♪ My heart wants to go ♪
In a weird way, it all makes
sense, though, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, it kind of does.
♪ ...the devil's lake ♪
♪ But never never ♪
♪ Never never ♪
The bride wants to see me?
♪ No, never, never, never. ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com to download
www.tvsubtitles.net