NARRATOR: Kids, Barney and Robin's
wedding turned out
to be a life-changing weekend
for all of us.
Well, not just us.
One ticket to Farhampton,
please.
NARRATOR:
But I'll get to that.
(horn honks)
Who are you honking at?
You.
You're going 40 in a 65.
Pick it up, Grandma!
Look, I'm happy to rock it up
into the 50s,
but I'm gonna need a hand...
or two.
Oh, no. Not the driving gloves.
In 99.9% of highway accidents,
the driver was not
wearing gloves.
Because they're stupid.
They don't help you
drive better.
That's why no one wears them.
Then why is it called...
the glove compartment?
I am not
having this argument again.
Now, as you know, a Mosby
road trip is not only safe,
but informative.
Chiggedy-check it.
Manhattan to Farhampton:
Lil' and Ted's
Excellent Adventure?
That baby's stuffed to the rings
with fun facts
about our unsung neighbor
to the east-- Long Island.
For instance, just up
ahead, the historic
childhood home of
Florian van Otterloop,
the Dutch bucklesmith
who revolutionized
the belt industry.
Uh, fun story
about that color-blind genius.
When he...
Please stop!
Well, I was just gonna
slow down for pictures,
but that level of enthusiasm
can't go unrewarded.
♪ How I Met Your Mother 9x01 ♪
The Locket
Original Air Date on September 23, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(phone chimes)
Hmm.
Oh, look at my
little cousins
in their flower
girl dresses.
Aw, they'll look so cute
next to the ring bear.
Yeah.
Wait, you said
ring bear-er, right?
Ring bear.
Ring bear-er.
Are you planning
some crazy stunt
with a dangerous wild animal
at our wedding?
(phone chirps)
Because...
Oh, oh, sorry,
sorry, sorry, sorry.
Oh, boy.
My brother wants to know
what time he "goes on"
at the reception.
What does that mean?
Every wedding he attends,
James insists on... performing.
♪ Islands in the stream
♪ That is what we are
♪ No one in between...
So? What do you got
against K-Rodge?
Everybody loves
The Gambler.
Wait for it.
♪ How can we be wrong?
♪ Sail away with me
to another world ♪
♪ And we rely
on each other, uh-huh! ♪
That is nothing.
I have invited Scherbatskys
from all over Canada,
and they are Canuckin' nuts.
Like my cousin Ruth
from the Yukon.
I don't like to encourage
Canadian stereotypes,
but that woman
practically rides a moose.
(laughs)
Does she actually ride a moose?
Yeah.
And, uh,
I'm worried she'll bring it
to the wedding.
She and the moose are...
very close.
Whoa.
Every wedding's got a wild card,
but we've invited a whole set.
(accordion playing
"Wedding March")
Someone is gonna
ruin this wedding.
It's just a question
of... who.
I'm gonna ruin this wedding!
My wife is
gonna kill me!
PILOT: Flight attendants
prepare for departure.
We were gonna move to
Italy for her dream job,
so I brought my son
here to Minnesota
to see my mom
before we left.
And then I got offered
a job as a judge
in New York City,
which is my dream.
But that'll totally
destroy her dream!
You are destroying
a lot of dreams right now.
(phone chimes)
(chuckles)
Wait.
If I got this...
(phone chimes)
(sighs)
Aren't you gonna
check that?
No.
It-It's just another
obnoxious update
from Marshall's mom.
She's been posting
these "cute" baby pics
of Marvin,
but it's all just propaganda.
First, it was
"Don't move to Italy."
Followed by an extremely subtle
guilt trip.
And then, randomly preachy.
Nah, not looking.
It's just gonna piss me off.
Why are we exiting again?
Well, if you turn in your binder
to the section labeled
"Mennonite Windmills..."
Get back on the expressway now.
(scoffs)
The expressway's
for gloveless amateurs.
I'm done.
There's a train station
coming up; just drop me off.
Okay, but some newfangled
train's not gonna stop
at the 40-foot-tall
butter churn in Ronkonkoma!
Yes, but unlike any of
your 18th-century stops,
at least the train will have
a 21st-century toilet!
You're a 21st-century toilet!
(gasps)
Train now!
Fine!
Okay, so far,
I've got 12 wild cards,
not counting the ring bear.
Ring bear-er.
Oh, oh, here's another one.
You know how I found out
that I'm one-quarter Canadian
but I've completely
blocked that out
because your nation's ridiculous
and I'm awesome?
Sure.
Well, turns out,
I have a crazy cousin Mitch
on that side of the family.
That's funny.
I have a crazy
cousin Mitch, too.
But I guarantee
he is crazier than yours.
He built his own house
from timber he chopped down
from other people's houses.
That's funny.
My cousin Mitch
is a lumberjack.
Except mine has six fingers.
On one hand or total?
Total.
Are truckers always
beating him up?
Yes, because he has to...
BOTH: ...hitchhike
with his middle finger.
Wait.
Is it possible that we're...
Could... c-could...
could we be...?
Shh...
Ranjit, could you be a dear
and pull over for a second?
Pulling over!
(both chuckle weakly)
(both retching)
All right, train.
Let's show your critics you're
not just a Dumpster on wheels
full of drunk idiots.
CONDUCTOR:
We're being held at this station
until further notice.
I got to sober up.
(phone ringing)
Eriksen residence,
Judy speaking.
Why did you post
that judge photo?
Because I'm guilty...
of being one proud mama!
Lily doesn't know
that I took the job,
so if she sees it,
I'm dead.
Just take it down, okay?
Fine.
Let me just get on the online
so I can Internet.
I love the lingo!
(modem screeching)
Look, Mom,
just-just...
click on the photo
on your wall,
and then under "menu""
click on "options""
Some kind of advertisement
popped on.
Oh, my.
That appears to be pornography.
Just click
on "options""
(whispering):
It's men with other men.
(whispering loudly):
Just click on "options"!
Excuse me!
Are there any other seats
left on this plane?
No.
Hell, I've been
going to Pilates.
I can just hang on
to the landing gear like this.
Sorry, ma'am.
I only signed up for Pilates,
I haven't actually
started going yet.
I didn't sign up.
LILY:
No, I'm not looking.
I don't need to see
my child used against me.
My sweet, beautiful child
who I haven't seen in a week...
whose head smells like love
and unicorn teardrops,
and why are trains
so lonely?!
Damn it, I'm looking!
WOMAN:
Hey, are you okay?
You look stressed.
Plus, you muttered
a few words out loud.
I heard "lonely" and "unicorn,"
which actually gave me
a great idea
for a children's book,
so thank you.
Are you okay?
No.
But there's nothing you can do.
Do you want a cookie?
(crying):
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Wow.
You just took a cookie
from a complete stranger
on a train.
I like how trusting you are.
There could be drugs
or poison in there.
But there's not, is there?
No idea,
I found them under my seat.
No!
Kidding! Sorry!
You looked stressed, so I
thought you could use a cookie,
then I thought
you could use a joke.
I should have stopped
at the cookie.
You know what?
I don't care
if these are poisoned.
There's chocolate
and peanut butter
and caramel in these sumbitches.
I call them "Sumbitches"!
(laughing)
NARRATOR:
And that's how Lily
met your mother.
Are Cousin Mitch and I
directly related?
No, Mom, I'm asking
is Cousin Mitch
a blood relative?
I'm not asking
about Cousin Pete,
I'm asking about Cousin Robin!
Mitch!
Cousin Mitch!
Well, just find out
from Uncle Frank
and call me back!
Well, then, go
visit Cousin Cecil
at his sky-diving school
and ask him!
Oh, God, he did?
Well, I guess that can happen
no matter
how experienced you are.
I'm so sorry.
(exhales)
got fired.
(sighs):
Oh.
That's a relief.
Um... I'm so sorry
for your loss.
It may be our loss.
(both shudder)
Just click
on "options"!
All I see is a man
holding a bratwurst!
Oh.
No, the pornography's back.
I said, please turn off
all electronic devices.
Oh. (laughs)
This isn't an
electronic device.
This is actually a toy.
For my son.
We call it Phone-y.
(scoffs)
I call you phony.
We can't take off
till you hang up.
Okay, enough.
Give me that phone!
Just click
on "options""
I don't see it!
I said,
give me the phone!
Just click
on "options"!
Stop yelling at me!
Just click
on "options""
Give me the phone.
Click on "options"!
Click on...
I have a baby!
Please, I-I have to get
to New York.
Yeah, well, you should
have thought about that
before you attacked me.
All right, boys,
you got this?
Good.
Let's get this bird in the air.
Ah, you're both
banned from this flight.
So I was driving with my
friend, who thinks he's
"The Road Trip Master."
He has leather driving gloves.
Who wears those?
Huge dorks, that's who.
NARRATOR:
Your mother was lying.
She had her own pair.
And he always makes us stop
to see some weird
roadside attraction
no one except him
gives a crap about.
Nerd alert.
NARRATOR: Kids, you remember
the seven-hour detour
on our road trip
to Disney World
so your mother didn't miss
that goat in South Carolina
who could blow smoke rings.
And he won't go one mile an hour
over the speed limit.
That would drive me crazy.
I would give him
a humiliating nickname
until he stopped driving
like a little girl.
NARRATOR:
It was "Lady Tedwina Slowsby."
And it worked.
Okay, look, if it's
true, if we are...
(gags softly)
You know.
It's really not that big a deal.
Okay, we-we know
we won't have kids.
And even if we did,
King Joffrey's parents
were brother and sister,
and he was
a fair and wise leader.
Yeah. Look, no one
ever needs to know but us.
Exactly.
(both chuckle)
I know.
BARNEY:
We might have to...
ROBIN:
Take care of Ranjit.
Hey, you just finished my...
Creepy telepathic
murder thought.
Oh, it must be
a soul mate thing.
Unless...
it's a weird cousin thing.
(gags softly)
So we'll be good
either way, right?
Honey?
That's right... sweetie.
Now, get over here, you.
Gah, just try
and stop me.
Aw.
Ooh, ooh.
Ooh, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Well, I can't wait
till tonight.
I have got some
naughty-naughty-naughty
things planned.
Aw.
Oh, wow, you have certainly
piqued my incest.
Interest. Interest!
I still can't believe he dragged
me to the childhood home
of some stupid bucklesmith
no one's ever even heard of.
Yeah, who cares
about Florian van Otterloop?
I never told you his name.
Sumbitch?
I mean, why'd he have to
act that way?
He knows I hate
how he gets on road trips.
It almost seems like
he wanted you to storm off.
But we're going
to the same place.
There's no reason
why he'd want to ditch me.
NARRATOR: And suddenly Lily remembered
that a week ago,
I'd helped Robin look
for her long-lost locket.
But it was gone.
Then Lily told me
the locket actually got stashed
in my pencil box,
but when I opened it...
the locket wasn't there.
Good.
'Cause that locket's trouble.
How? It's-it's just a friendly,
innocent wedding gift.
It's not innocent.
Ted, you think
if you can get that locket
for Robin you'll win her back.
Lily, I've let it go.
I mean...
What?
There's, like,
a one percent chance
that Stella has the locket
from when we lived together.
Promise me you didn't call
the woman who left you
at the altar so that
you could find that locket.
Of course not.
I e-mailed her.
Ted.
But Stella's living
in L.A. now.
And even if she has it,
it's buried
in some storage unit.
She said I'd have
to fly out there
and look for it myself.
Promise me you aren't
about to do that.
I promise.
Sumbitch!
You better hope when Sweaty
finally gets off that phone,
he can get me on the next flight
to New York.
I got the password
from my mom.
I'm gonna take that
photo down myself.
You know, I don't give
a damn about your photo.
My daughter is giving
a big speech for the Model U.N.
at her school, and I'm
gonna miss it because of you.
(sighs)
Her father and I are separated.
She lives with her dad.
And if I don't make it...
she's never gonna
trust me again.
I'm so sorry.
Wow, that worked on you?
Let's hope Pit Stains is
as dumb as you are.
What? Why is this
so hard for my mom?
All you do
is you click the photo,
and then you click on the...
I don't see...
I don't see "options."
Just click on "options."
But where is it?
Is it up on the toolbar?
Just click on "options."
It's not there!
Just click on "options"!
(phone ringing)
Hi, Grandma.
You-you can explain how
Cousin Mitch is related to us?
Explain, Grandma, explain!
Okay, he married
Barney's dad's cousin Renee,
who he met selling Vachon cakes
outside a curling bonspiel
in Chicoutimi.
English, Grandma, English!
And on our side of the family,
he was adopted
because his real parents
were eaten alive
by their sled dogs?
That's awesome!
Thanks, Grandma.
(both sigh)
So...
So you and I share
no DNA whatsoever.
Let's change that.
(both moaning)
RANJIT:
Don't hold back.
This divider is
totally soundproof.
Go all the way.
Wait till the hotel?
Totally.
Hey, you know what?
I'm not worried about a wild
card at our wedding anymore.
Whether it's Uncle Vic
or Aunt Shelly
or the ring bear.
Ring bear-er. Er.
Whether any
of those mammals go rogue,
our wedding is
gonna be legendary.
No "wait for it"?
I've got you.
I don't have to
wait for it anymore.
(phone ringing)
(line ringing)
It's a long story,
but if we don't beat my friend
out to that wedding,
it's gonna be bad.
This is too stressful.
I-I need to see Marvin!
No! You made me promise
not to let you look,
because it's
only gonna upset you.
Here, have another sum... bitch.
No more sumbitches?!
Give me the damn phone!
(both scream)
(clamoring) Just go to "edi""
on the toolbar!
No, "account settings"!
Just click
on "options""
Stop!
It can't be done.
That photo is etched
in eternity.
Long after humanity's
reign has ended,
the only traces
of our civilization found
by Earth's new ape masters
will be
the top
of the Statue of Liberty
and this photo of me
pretending to be
a judge with a banana gavel.
Well, they'll probably like
the banana thing.
The ape masters?
Sorry.
Lily's gonna see it,
and we're gonna have
the biggest fight of our lives.
(chuckles) Oh, I wish I could
see your wife kick your ass.
I don't mean a physical fight.
She's not an animal.
I'm sorry I tried
to bite you.
I'm sorry that I swatted you
on the nose
with a rolled-up magazine.
It's the only way I'll learn.
Look, I haven't seen
my baby in a week.
You know what?
Go for it.
It's gone!
(all cheering)
You did it!
You did it! (laughs)
No new insulting Marvin photo.
Hmm.
(voice breaks):
No new insulting Marvin photo.
I know I'm just a stranger
on a train
who you tried to bite, but...
do you want a hug?
(Lily yells)
Lily! What the hell?!
Ted and I had some
road trip issues.
Did he put on the gloves?
Mm-hmm.
That tackle was justified.
What's this?
It's for you.
Don't open it.
TED: With all
the big changes coming up,
I just wanted Robin
to remember her friends.
We all want nothing but
happiness for you and Barney.
Right, Lily?
Right.
Oh, wow.
That was, what, eight years ago?
Yeah.
Eight years.
Thanks, Ted.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get checked in.
Marshall's flight just took off.
My boys will be here soon.
Oh, yay.
NARRATOR: Actually, Lily's boys were
just learning there was
only one more flight out
to New York with one seat left,
and it was all the way
across the airport.
You're not gonna
tackle me again, are you?
I'm the maid of honor.
There's a good chance
that won't be
my only tackle of the weekend.
NARRATOR:
It wasn't.
Look, I'm sorry.
I just got it in my head
that you somehow managed
to track down that locket
in Los Angeles,
and now you were gonna
blow up the wedding.
You really think I'm that crazy?
(sighs)
I guess that's fair.
Look, even though I was wrong,
tell me you aren't thinking
about doing anything
insane this weekend.
Of course not.
NARRATOR:
And all I can say, kids,
is at that moment,
I really thought I meant it.
But the truth is...
you never know
who's gonna be the wild card
at a wedding.
Hi. One ticket
to Los Angeles, please.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
NARRATOR: That afternoon
at the Farhampton Inn,
Aunt Lily and I
tried to check in.
Are you chewing gum?
You never chew gum.
You shouldn't chew gum
in here.
Nobody cares if
I chew gum, Ted.
Are you chewing gum?
Yes, she is.
She's chewing gum.
Ooh, can I have a piece?
Of course!
Great.
Thank you.
Okay, let's chew some gum
and get you guys
all checked in.
Ms. Aldrin, how many
keys will you need?
Two, please.
My husband's
getting in later.
Excellent, and Mr. Mosby?
Uh, just one, please.
Oh, oh, I-I see.
Oh.
Well, hang in there.
You'll find somebody.
Thank you,
front desk stranger.
I'm sorry, we just... we just
don't get a lot of singles here.
I mean,
look at this place.
It's so romantic.
Countless babies conceived
within these walls.
And one... grisly murder.
Now, are you sure
that you wouldn't
feel more comfortable
staying at a motel?
What? No, look.
I'm not some miserable,
lonely person.
Tell him, Lily.
It's a tough
weekend for him.
Bro.
We're here for a wedding.
Ouch.
And he used to date the bride.
Ooh, mama.
And he's the best man.
Devastating.
Could you please
just check us in?
Oh, your rooms aren't
gonna be ready for hours.
But in the meantime,
Ms. Aldrin, I definitely think
you and your husband should
check out the lighthouse.
It's a beautiful view
of the bay-- so romantic.
Oh, wow.
Here's the channel guide
for the TV.
Don't listen
to him, Ted.
(phone ringing)
You are not alone.
In fact, this
whole weekend,
it is going to be
nothing but me and...
Marshall!
Oh, thank God,
you're on your way.
If I had to be here alone,
I would kill myself.
How are you doing?
I'm fine... Curtis.
I mean, let's do
the math here.
One "best man" plus one
"no girlfriend" equals...
"Mothers of Farhampton,
lock up your daughters!"
Double guns!
(imitating gunshots)
Wow, you're in bad shape.
Marshall missed
his flight.
He might not get
here tonight.
He might not
get here at all.
We...
only have a few
of these left.
♪ How I Met Your Mother 9x02 ♪
Coming Back
Original Air Date on September 23, 2013
Hi...
Linus.
Here's how this goes down.
If I'm going to make it through
this weekend without my husband,
I need you to hook a lady up.
Any time you see me
without a drink in my hand,
you put a drink in my hand.
Are you my guy, Linus?
So you want the Kennedy Package?
Bingo.
(phone rings)
Go for Barney.
Ah.
Thank you Linus.
Barney,
before you get too upset,
there's another flight
that leaves in five minutes.
You're getting on it.
I'm gonna try.
There is no try!
You're getting on that plane.
Hey, growth spurt.
If there is only one seat
left on this plane,
I will fight you for it.
And I'm a biter.
Marshall, whoever that is,
grab her carry-on
and throw it
into a restricted area.
I'm serious. Do it.
Do it now.
What? No.
Barney, are you...?
No, I'm not gonna...
That's... No.
There is no
"What, no, Barney, are you,
no I'm not gonna, that's no!"
This is a holiday weekend.
You're not gonna get
to New York by being nice.
So you're gonna have
to lose the whole Midwestern
aw-shucksy-doodles thing...
Shucksy doodles?
...and act like a New Yorker.
A pushy, obnoxious,
knock-the-other-guy-down-
and-take-his-hot-dog resident
of the greatest city on earth!
No can do, Barney.
I'm from Minnesota,
where there's plenty of hot dogs
for everyone.
Perhaps even too many.
But listen,
I'm gonna get to New York
without being a jerk.
Just get to New York!
I'll get to New York!
Nobody's getting to New York.
Not this weekend anyway.
There's a big storm
rolling up the East Coast.
All the airports
are closing.
My advice is
rent a car and drive.
But you better hurry.
They're gonna
run out of cars soon.
(groans)
Okay, listen.
If we're both
going to New York,
why don't we rent a car,
split the drive?
That seems like
a reasonable plan.
Can I help you with
that diaper bag?
Sure. Thank you.
Oh, it's...
Have a nice bus ride,
pumpkin head!
(panting)
Hey, lady.
Yeah, you just threw away
your ticket
to a really great road trip.
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
You're all the way back there,
and I'm all the way
up here.
(laughing)
Oh, you can hear me.
Get ready to be driving
the jealous-mobile
because our car is
gonna have games,
snacks, a James Patterson
audio book
my mother describes as
"cluttering her glove box."
Your car? I'll be in Pittsburgh
before you get your car.
We'll see about that.
And if you're going to New York,
you're not gonna want
to go through Pittsburgh.
94 backs up around Allentown,
so you're gonna want
to stick on 80.
Jerk face!
Come on, universe.
I'm a nice guy.
Send me a miracle.
NARRATOR: And then the universe sent
your Uncle Marshall...
Herm.
Okay, people, let's move
it along. What do you want?
You want a car? You got a car.
Beat it.
What kind of car
do you want?
Too slow, you get a minivan.
Next. Ah, midsize sedan.
Incoming. Next.
Yes!
You want a gas option?
Nobody wants a gas option.
Get out of here.
Next.
Hello. I need a car.
You've got it.
That's all of them.
We're all out of cars,
everybody.
Wait, no!
You let this guy beat you?
Ma'am, it's not a race.
That right there
is why you lost.
Maybe this is your fault.
Did you ever think of that?
Maybe if you
had just been
a little bit nicer,
then you would be
the one driving this lovely...
What kind of car is it?
NARRATOR: Now, kids, I don't remember
the actual name of this car,
but to an environmentalist
like Marshall,
this car was a monstrosity.
2006 Monstrosity.
♪ Monstrosity
♪ 'Cause global warming's
not real. ♪
Oh, no, not a Monstrosity.
I'll take it.
I can't drive that.
I can. Give me the Monstrosity.
Do you have anything else?
I'll take the Monstrosity.
There's nothing else.
Give me the keys, old man!
It's just so freaking huge!
Well, actually it's
a Monstrosity Sport,
so it's a little smaller.
♪ Monstrosity Sport
♪ It's still freaking huge.
Fine. I'll take it.
But I'm also gonna need
a baby seat.
We're all out of baby seats.
Get out of here.
Oh, my God--
what am I gonna do?
I don't care.
(groans)
Can I make a suggestion?
I rent the car,
then I go buy the car seat,
come back here,
pick you guys up,
and then the three of us
drive to New York together.
(laughs quietly)
Let me get this straight.
So, you're gonna
rent the car,
go and get a baby seat
for my son,
and then drive all the way
back here to pick me up.
That's right.
Well, then you're
gonna need some cash. Here.
Hundred bucks ought to cover it.
So, we'll see
you soon.
You got it, Michael!
Marshall.
Doesn't matter now, does it?
Remember this day, Marvin.
Not only is this the day
that we either saw Prince
or a... a really flamboyantly
dressed greyhound,
it's also the day that your dad
chose not to be a jerk...
and put his trust in humanity.
Just watch where it gets us.
Shucksy-doodles!
NARRATOR: Uncle Marshall
was just about ready
to abandon
his faith in humanity.
But let's back up a little bit.
And now the true tale
of the Stinson Curse.
BARNEY:
Moscow, 1807.
(Russian accent): What a wonderful night
at the opera.
Wouldn't you agree,
Comrade Barnovski?
(Russian accent): I would indeed,
Comrade Jamesokoff.
But you know what made it
truly wonderful?
Being here with my wife...
the beet in my borscht,
the fur on my hat,
the only person I've ever
been attracted to, ever.
I feel the same way
about Kyle...
my plutonic friend
from work.
(clattering)
Is it just me, or did that feel
like we hit an old Gypsy woman?
Yep. Old Gypsy woman.
Good call, Barnovski.
Oh, well, she's just a peasant.
Home, Smirnoff.
Wait, she's
saying somethink!
(low, deep moan)
Hornier.
Hornier?
Sonobovich!
Did she just put a curse on us?
Eh, nonsense, brother.
Okay, let's go, Smirnoff.
Smirnoff?
Homina, hominovich. Mmm,
Smirnoff, I would climb you
like the Kremlin Wall.
What's happening to me?
Don't you see?
You're getting hornier, brother,
just like
the old Gypsy woman said!
Oh, hello there.
(chuckles) Ever had
a White Russian?
BARNEY:
For the next 200 years,
every male member
of the Stinson family
was afflicted
by the Gypsy's curse,
an unquenchable thirst
for booty
that no committed relationship
could ever satisfy.
That is, until my brother James
met his husband Tom.
The day they got married,
they lifted the curse forever,
freeing me from the shackles
of having sex
with lots of different women.
Although, sometimes
Robin and I still use
the shackles.
Bondage five!
Whoa.
I can't, I can't,
I can't.
(phone rings)
Go for Barney!
Ah.
Thank you, Linus.
This is worse
than I thought.
I know.
Showtime, no HBO?
JAMES:
No.
Tom and I are getting divorced.
What?
TED: What?
That's why you look
extra handsome.
I do get extra hot
when I'm single.
Your skin looks amazing.
Looks amazing.
I know.
So... so what happened?
Why-why'd you guys break up?
Well, the thing to remember
is that when something
like this happens,
it's nobody's fault.
You cheated on him.
Repeatedly.
I thought about
keeping it quiet,
but then I realized,
wouldn't my family want me
to be honest with them
about news this big?
Oh, can I just say five things?
What is the matter with--
sorry, six-- you?!
Ooh! What?!
I'm-I'm sorry
about you and Tom,
but you can't just drop
a bombshell like this
so close to
someone's wedding.
You broke the curse.
You and Tom
are the only couple
that makes Barney
believe in marriage.
(chuckles) Really?
The only couple?
I mean, no one else
comes to mind?
Been together 17 years?
She's a spunky redhead,
he's got calves
that launched a thousand
lady boners?
BARNEY:
Hey, sorry about that.
Hey, did you guys know
that Sunday is James' and Tom's
anniversary?
How cool is that?
We're anniversary bros!
Every year, we should go out
and celebrate...
just the two of us.
Listen, bro, you...
I know, I know, "Please, Barney,
you don't have to get us
an anniversary gift this year."
You get them an
anniversary gift?
Why shouldn't I?
They're the one couple
that makes me believe marriage
is possible.
I mean, I'm sitting right here.
Thank you, Linus.
JAMES:
Barney, the thing is...
Cover your ears and hum "The
Battle Hymn of the Republic""
Why?
It's for the bride.
Oh, it's for... (humming)
Okay, listen, James,
my cousin Vince
is a Mountie.
His girlfriend is back home,
but he gets gay at weddings.
He's yours.
I am giving you Vince.
Just please,
don't tell Barney.
If he finds out
that the only
successful marriage
in his life is over...
I hate everyone
at this table.
...it'll spook him.
I don't want him
getting spooked.
Robin, have some faith.
Do you really think what you
and Barney have is that fragile?
I don't want to find out.
Fine.
Thanks, baby.
No sweat.
Mmm...
So, James, seriously,
where's Tom?
He can't make the wedding.
He had his wisdom teeth out.
Ugh! On top of a divorce?
That is rough.
Uh-oh.
What is she talking about?
Tom and I are getting a divorce.
Excuse me.
Vince... off the table.
What was that?
I don't know.
It just came out.
That's it.
It's barely even noon.
You're cut off.
Thank you, Linus.
Okay, but after that one,
you're cut off!
No! No, you are not doing this.
Step away from the desk.
What are you talking about?
You just found out
about James and Tom,
and it totally freaked you out,
and now you're asking this guy
to point you in the direction
of the nearest,
dirtiest strip club.
Oh, well,
that-that's a tough one.
Uh, the nearest one
that's-that's kind of dirty
is The Sand Box,
but the, uh...
the dirtiest one that's nearby
is The Crab Shed.
Dude.
Sorry. Uh, but hey,
if-if you do go,
maybe you could take Ted.
I'm really worried
about that kid.
No, Robin, I am not
going to a strip club.
Especially right now.
Could you imagine
the day shift at The Crab Shed?
Robin...
I came to the desk to get this.
Is that the key to our room?
It's the key to James's room.
Oh, my.
What is that?
It's an erotic cake.
I wanted to surprise them
for their anniversary.
Is that... is that
James and Tom?
Mmm, caramel marzipan,
chocolate marzipan.
I love chocolate
marzipan.
So does Tom.
Used to anyway.
This is, uh, absolutely the,
uh... the weirdest thing
anyone has ever done
for their sibling.
I love you so much.
You thought I was
gonna freak out.
Well, I mean, a Gypsy
cursed your family
to become hornier and do
awesome guitar solos.
Can you blame me?
Look, am I bummed about James
and Tom getting a divorce?
Obviously.
But I don't need them
to make me believe
in true love anymore.
I've got you for that now.
Mmm.
Oh, man, now I gotta figure out
what to do with all this stuff.
Well, before we do that...
um, would it be all
right if I nibbled
on your brother's
Ding Dong?
How about we nibble
on my brother's
Ding Dong together?
I'd like that.
NARRATOR: So, they cleaned all that stuff
out of there
and had a talk with James.
And Barney didn't freak out,
because here's the thing, kids.
When you believe in people,
people come through.
Just so we're clear,
I pick the music.
Of course.
Say it.
Say, "Daphne picks the music."
Daphne picks the music.
And you pay for gas.
Are you kidding?
Do you have any idea
how much gas this thing takes?
(engine revs)
No, no, okay!
Okay, I pay for gas.
Good. Now, get in.
It's a long ride to Phoenix.
Say what?
(laughs)
I'm just kidding.
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
This must be the singles table.
(chuckles)
Guess it is.
Well, it's kind of nice
to be asking this question
instead of answering it
for a change:
How are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm trying to be happy
for my brother,
but, uh... I guess a person
has a different
perspective on weddings
when he knows what's down there
at the end of the aisle.
It's not all
champagne and frosting.
Mr. Stinson, your room is ready.
And, Ted...
she's right around the corner.
Thank you, Curtis.
I feel it, too.
No, no, no, the-the housekeeper.
She's in the room that's right
around the corner from yours.
Oh.
So another hour, tops.
Sure.
Okay, see you later, Ted.
You're not
giving up, James.
And neither am I.
(footsteps approach)
TED:
Hey, beautiful.
Hi.
God, you look great.
What? Come on.
You do!
I've been in a car all morning.
I just ate a croissant crumb
that I found in my bra.
I'm disgusting.
Yeah, I saw you do that.
And it was super hot. Come here.
(chuckles) You come here.
Come here.
No, you come here.
Hey, you want to hear
something funny?
Mm-hmm.
One year ago today,
almost to the minute,
I was sitting
at this very table
right in that seat.
Oh, yeah. I can see it.
Nursing your gin and tonic
with three extra limes,
doing the crossword,
probably being
all showboat-y about it.
I wasn't being
showboat-y about it.
"Vesuvius""
Boo-yah!
Oh, wait, that doesn't fit.
The point is,
one year ago today,
I made a promise to myself
right at this table.
THE MOTHER:
What was the promise?
BOTH TEDS: I'm coming back,
and I'm bringing you.
Wait a second.
Hold it.
One year ago today,
you hadn't even met me.
I know, but I knew I would.
And now it's a year later.
And here I am.
Here you are.
Love in your eyes,
baked goods
in your undergarments.
Yeah.
You picked a real winner, Mosby.
I did.
Okay, seriously, what the crap
is taking so long
with these rooms?
It was like this
last year.
I'll be right back.
I'll be right here.
Sorry that took so long.
Please...
try to enjoy your stay.
I will.
Try to.
I will enjoy my stay.
Try.
Not gonna try.
Just... just gonna do it.
Good for you.
Not good for me.
No, just-just neutral for me.
Attaboy.
No, at not a boy.
It gets better.
I am fine, Curtis. Okay?
I enjoy and appreciate
the happiness of other people
whether I am in a relationship
or not. Okay? Curtis?
So just-just...
just go ahead
and give me my one key
because I am fine.
Oh, come on!
I need another drink.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net