So?
No.
No. You-You were in.
I said, "Have you met Ted"
and everything.
How could that not work?
I don't know,
we introduced ourselves,
I bought her a drink,
told her I loved her...
What?
I'm kidding.
Hold on, Roxanne-- if that
really is your name.
It's not. It's Robin.
You played "Have You Met Ted"
without me?
In my bar with my Ted?
Maybe stealing a bro's wingman
is okay back in...
I'm sorry, what's the name of
this third world banana republic
you claim to be from?
Canada.
I have literally
never heard of that place.
When'd you move
here, anyway?
Two months ago.
How do you like it?
Honestly,
it-it's been
a little tough.
I moved here for this on-air
reporter job at Metro News 1
thinking it was gonna
be my big break,
only to find out
that our viewership
mostly consists
of DMV waiting rooms
and people plugging in their
TV for the first time.
To top it all off,
I have no friends.
Um... wrong.
You have four friends
right here.
Right, guys?
Uh, yeah.
You're totally in our gang,
now. And once you're in,
you're in for life, right?
She's in.
Oh. All right.
Welcome.
Well, if I'm in, I should
get the next round.
Whoa, whoa,
Ooh,
I like this girl.
ho, ho.
I'm serious, I
like this girl.
And we need some estrogen
up in this bitch.
All we ever talk about
is Scotch and sports.
Five Glen McKennas,
21 years, neat.
And switch it
to the hockey game, 'cause
my Canucks are gonna
bury the Bruins, yo.
So here's the deal
with the deal.
Robin's my new
best friend--
nobody bangs her.
Hey, hey,
hey, she only rejected me
three times,
she's still very much in play.
I'm serious.
There's only one way I'd let
either of you have sex with her.
Not that. It's never that.
I really want this girl
to stay a part
of our lives.
So the only way you're allowed
to hook up with her...
is if you marry her.
Too rich for my blood.
That son of a bitch did it.
He really did.
So you're moving
to Chicago tomorrow, huh?
How do you feel?
Uh, I'm looking forward to it.
The job's amazing.
I got a great apartment
lined up.
You know, it's...
It's exciting.
Onwards and upwar...
♪ How I Met Your Mother 9x23 ♪
Last Forever, Part 1
Original Air Date on March 31, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey! Bass player.
It's me. The guy from
the drug store with the diapers
that hit on you,
then we went outside
and had a deep, emotional
talk on a bus bench.
I ...I-I'm gonna be really
surprised if I have to be
more specific than that.
Remember when you
told me to stop
messing around
and go get the girl?
Well, check it. I got her.
What about you?
You still dating that guy?
Grape Scotch
Ted, Ted, Ted, Ted.
Right here, right here,
Yeah,
I-I see you, Barney.
right here, right here.
Good, great. Then it's
time to play a little game
I like to call Have...
Yeah,
Barney, I...
No, no.
You are not getting out
of Have You Met Ted.
There's a girl
that you have to meet.
She is perfect for you.
And has...
she met you?
No, she has... not.
Think of all the sex
you're gonna ha..
Barney.
I ha... I have to go.
What, now?
Yeah.
Y...
W-We have to do this outside.
Robin.
It's been a major pleasure.
Major Pleasure.
Come here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Oh, God, no, this is too real.
I can't handle this,
Marshall's next.
Marshall.
Good luck out there
in Chicago.
I'm gonna be kind of jealous
of you, getting to have
Gazzola's pizza
whenever you want.
You're gonna be in Rome.
Yeah. I guess.
I just...
I feel like a hug isn't enough.
E.T. good-bye?
I'll be right...
here.
Okay, it helped,
but that was really creepy.
I don't want to see you for awhile.
Barney.
Mm.
We licked the Liberty Bell.
We did?
Yeah, you...
You don't remember that?
Uh, I've done
a lot of cool stuff, Ted.
Oh, my God.
I just... I just realized:
Who am I gonna high five now?
Come on, dude.
No, no,
I'm being serious.
What if I see...
a pack of lions
fighting a tyrannosaurus?
Or, better yet,
what if I see boobs?
Who am I...
who am I gonna high five then?
You can high
five Marshall.
Yeah, yeah. But Marshall
only likes to high five
about Lily boobs.
Oh, always.
Okay, Barney.
I have an idea.
One last high five.
A high five to echo
throughout eternity.
Yes.
And within
that high five will be
all the high fives
we've ever high fived.
And all the high fives we
could ever possibly high five.
A high infinity.
A high infinity, exactly.
Let's do this.
All right,
everybody back up.
Oh, boy.
I'll see you
on the other side, Ray.
Nice working with you,
Dr. Venkman.
Aah!
Ow!
Oh. Oh.
Oh!
Worth it.
So worth it.
So I rushed out
to make the train,
which is now 45 minutes late.
This lady
with the bass guitar--
was she pretty?
Yeah.
She was beautiful.
Go back and meet her.
No.
But what if it was destiny?
Lady, it's been
a really long weekend.
I'm moving to Chicago tomorrow.
I can't really
talk destiny right now.
Okay.
Yes?
What if the universe
sent you a gigantic sign
that this woman
was your destiny?
Then would you talk to her?
Yeah, sure. I mean,
I-I guess I would have to.
Okay.
Where is that train?
Can I ask one more question?
What?
This girl with the bass guitar--
is that her?
That is her, isn't it?
This is so exciting.
G-Go talk to her.
All right. Just be cool,
lady. Damn.
Why are you still
sitting here?
Because I'm moving to
Chicago tomorrow, remember?
And 24 hours
from now,
my life is gonna be
completely different.
This is so strange,
you know, now that Ted's
gone, it's just a...
a different vibe.
You can just f-feel
his absence.
Are you kidding me?!
Oh, hey.
Ted, what are
you doing here?
Just having a drink.
What are you doing
in New York?
Aren't you
supposed to be in Chicago?
No... Oh.
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
What?
I'm not moving to Chicago.
Why?
I met a girl.
You...
son of a bitch!
What is the matter with you?
How could you put us
through that?
That good-bye was
emotionally devastating.
A certain delicate flower
cried all night in the shower.
And I was pretty
bummed, too.
And now you're
staying because of some girl?
I mean, who is
this person?
The bass player
from the wedding band.
Oh, yeah, she's great.
Love her.
Right,
right?
What are you... What are you doing?
Calling her.
Don't do this.
Don't call her the next day.
You're blowing this.
Huh?
Three days.
You wait three days,
Ted.
Oh, the
three day rule
is-is a childish,
manipulative
mind game.
But yeah, you
wait three days.
H-Hey, it's Ted. Hi. Um,
listen, do you ... do you want
to have dinner tomorrow night?
Great.
It was clear I meant
with me, right?
Same answer. Solid.
Why does he keep
doing this?
He meets 'em,
he likes 'em way too much,
he goes way too big, too soon,
and he ends up blowing it.
I can't take this anymore.
He's fallen in love
so many times now.
Not like this.
This is different.
Come on, go talk to her.
Oh, and it'll all be
because of me.
And I'll sing
at your wedding.
Y-You are gonna have
a big wedding, right?
What? No.
Just be cool, lady. Damn.
And aren't big weddings
kind of a young man's game?
You don't have a big wedding
in your 30s.
If I do ever get married,
I'm keeping it simple.
A hot air balloon?
Well, yeah. I mean,
when you're getting married
in a 17th-century castle in
France and making your entrance
on a stagecoach
with six white horses,
you kind of got to make
a big exit.
How much are you
spending on this?
Oh, like, a lot of money.
Mm.
All of my money.
Look, I know you guys
have been traveling a lot,
but you're coming, right?
Oh course. What...
Duh.
I'll get the next round.
Thanks.
I'd offer, but...
Castle.
Yeah.
So, how you guys doing?
I mean, Robin's really
taking off at work, huh?
It's like, "Robin Scherbatsky,
World Wide News, Caracas."
"Robin Scherbatsky, World Wide
News, St. Petersburg."
"Robin Scherbatsky,
World Wide News,
anywhere but New York,
apparently."
But it's great.
Uh, it's makes things
super difficult for us,
but it's great. It's great.
It's great. It's great.
One more and I'll believe you.
It's great.
Sounds great.
Hey.
Hi, hi. Sorry I'm late.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure. Did you wire the
down payment to the castle guy?
I got a castle guy.
I've got, like,
three castle guys.
And a moat guy, so...
I didn't wire the
payment because
I don't think we can get
married in September.
What-What, why?
Because,
when I do get married,
I kind of want to fit
in... my dress.
Why wouldn't you f...
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Whoa.
What's going on?
She's getting a boob job.
We just peeked in on Penny
asleep in the baby room.
It's adorable.
The whole place
looks great, guys.
But I can't believe you let Ted
hang his jousting lance
from the renaissance fair
on your bedroom wall.
Yeah.
That's Ted's.
So, Marshall, how's your job going?
Mm.
My chair...
is reasonably comfortable.
For short periods of time.
Marshall has decided to say
only positive things about
being back in corporate law.
So you hate it?
Much of what I do does not
make me cry.
But the job's only temporary.
Marshall was offered
the judgeship once,
and he turned it down for me.
So, karmically, that phone
has to ring again.
And even if it doesn't,
today, when my boss
threw his egg salad sandwich
at my face,
some of it got into my mouth.
And it was tasty.
Hey, what
about you guys?
How was Argentina?
Great. It was great.
It was great.
One more and I'll
believe you.
This is so not great.
I'm sorry that I have
to work while I'm here.
It's called being on assignment.
Well, what about me? There's
no Wi-Fi in this hotel.
How am I supposed to
run a business, Robin,
with no Wi-Fi?
It's not a business,
Barney, it's a blog, okay?
It is a lifestyle blog.
For the upscale, sophisticated
urban gentleman, and it's
never gonna take off if I can't
post today's boner joke.
I know I'm always traveling.
We both hate it when
I'm gone, we both hate it
when I drag you with me.
Neither of us is happy.
Is this just not
working anymore?
Wait, w... What "this"?
This-this?
If I gave you an out,
right now--
if there was
an exit ramp right here
at the three-year mark--
would you take it?
Before I answer that,
real quick:
you want to get super drunk
and have sex right now?
Of course.
And then, one thing
led to another.
And then another.
And then another
after that.
Oh.
And we kept drinking, and
may have had
a little... too much.
Arigato.
Wow, these rooms
all look the same,
even when you're sober.
You're sober?
So, um...
about what we discussed
last night.
How do you feel?
I love you, Robin.
And when we got married,
I made a vow that I would always
tell you the truth.
We got divorced.
I can't believe you got
divorced without telling us.
This is my mom and
dad all over again.
Barney, if you start
brewing your own beer now
and nail my prom
date, so help me...
Years too late on
one of those, Teddy.
Guys, it's okay.
This isn't
a failed marriage.
It's a very
successful marriage
that happened to
only last three years.
You both want this?
For real?
We do.
For real.
Lily, you okay?
Of course
I'm not okay.
This ruins
everything.
Now we have to choose sides,
and obviously
we're gonna choose Robin,
but Barney has his moments.
I really liked
the boner joke of the day.
Look, you guys do not need
to pick sides.
Nothing has to change.
No. We've already
broken up before
and we've stayed friends,
remember?
As long as you promise me this
won't mean we stop hanging out.
Okay.
I'm serious.
I know, but, I mean,
we hardly hang out anymore
anyway.
They live in the suburbs now,
and you two are about
to have baby number three.
Please. You're so obvious.
Your gals are back up
to a full C-cup,
and you've been sipping
her drink all night long.
We didn't want
to announce anything
till we knew for sure.
Oh, my gosh, Lily!
That's amazing!
Oh, congratulations!
Oh, my God.
Wait, see?
This, right here,
this is why we can't fall
out of each other's lives.
We have to be here
for the big moments.
Just promise me,
no matter what,
we will always be there
for the big moments.
I-I promise. We'll-we'll always
be there for the big moments.
Mm.
See?
It's like this whole divorce
thing never happened.
I...
Hey.
Hi, sweetie.
How was work?
My-my boss only called me
three words
that meant "vagina" today.
How are the kids?
Asleep.
Good. This is working, right?
Marvin and Daisy sharing a room
together? It's not too cramped?
And then when the
next one arrives,
we'll just put her
crib... in the shower.
It's the perfect size.
It'll save time on cleanups...
Let's move
somewhere bigger.
Yes. Oh, thank God.
I mean... You know,
don't get me wrong.
I love this apartment.
How do you say good-bye
to so many special memories?
Cock-a-mouse!
We have to move!
Hey, Marshall.
Robin!
Hey, I'm so glad you're here.
It's-it's been forever.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Where's your...
where's your costume?
Oh, uh, it's been
a crazy week at work
so no time to go shopping.
Uh, well, who are
you supposed to be?
Okay, I want to make it clear
this is not my idea.
I'm Captain Ahab.
Why is it bad
if it was your idea?
Robin, you made it!
A white whale. Got it.
Aw. Hi.
Hi.
Yeah, I figured,
people are thinkin' it. Might as
well steer into the skid, right?
Where's your costume?
Oh, you know,
I've just been so...
Oh, my God, Marshall!
Guess whose digits
I just scored?
The slutty
police officer's...
tax attorney.
Hey, Robin!
Hey.
Didn't see you there.
Saved it.
Sorry, I got to pee.
I-I'll be back
in... an hour.
Oh, man.
Is Ted still wearing
his hanging chad costume?
How old is that thing?
It's gone
from played out to
charmingly retro and back
six or seven times now.
Kind of
like Ted himself.
Tonight it's working
for him though.
How do you do this, Ted?
How do you
sit out here all night
on the roof in the cold
and still have faith
your pumpkin's gonna show up?
Look, I know that odds are
the love of my life
isn't gonna magically walk
through that door
in a pumpkin costume at...
2:43 in the morning, but...
this seems as nice a spot
as any to just, you know...
sit and wait.
Um...
uh, c-can you tell Lily
I-I had to go?
I got to split.
Speaking of splits, do you think
I can do a split in midair
like my boy
David Lee Roth?
I know you can't.
Challenge accepted.
Oh, my scrotum!
I can't get out
of this thing.
I'm holding it.
Wait, are you leaving?
Yeah,
I got a big day tomorrow.
I got to get some sleep.
No, you can't leave.
This is a big moment.
We're saying good-bye
to the apartment.
The whole gang has to be here.
The gang?
Do you know who the gang is
to me, Lily?
Here's what the gang is:
the gang is a married couple
who I never see anymore,
about to have their third kid;
it's my ex-husband,
hitting on slutty cops
right in front of me;
and it's the guy I probably
should have ended up with
with the beautiful mother
of his child.
I mean, who in their right mind
would call
that group of people "the gang"?
Oh...
Oh, oh, so... so what?
This is all
just over then?
Our whole friendship
is just over?
No. No, of course not.
Look, we'll...
we'll always be friends.
It's just...
never gonna be how it was.
It can't be.
And that doesn't
have to be a sad thing.
There-There's so much
wonderful stuff happening
in all of our
lives right now.
Look, more than enough
to be grateful for.
But the five of us
hanging out at MacLaren's,
being young and stupid...
that's just not one
of those things.
That part's over.
I got to go.
Good night, Lily.
Good night.
Marshall's almost here.
Yes! Look at us,
hanging out again.
This is amazing.
This is awesome!
This is...
Okay.
Just settle down, buddy.
No!
Settling down is for losers with
kids who never go out anymore.
I am in
charge tonight,
and the earliest
I am allowing anyone
to go home is...
2:00 a.m.
10:00 p.m.
9:45.
3:00 a.m.
Guys, tonight
is gonna be legen--
wait for it...
If I leave now,
I could put
the kids to bed.
I'll get the check.
..dary!
Legendary!
Guys, the gang is back!
We're back!
All of us except for Robin.
We never see her anymore.
Okay, in addition
to you guys not going home
before 4:00 a.m.--
yes, it's up to 4:00 now--
new rule: anytime anyone talks
about something sad,
we stay out an extra hour.
We said we'd always be there
for the big moments.
5:00 a.m.
To be fair,
tonight's just
us hanging out
until 10:00 p.m., tops.
It's not a big moment.
Um,
yes, it is.
Um, no, it's not.
Um, yes, it is.
Um... no, it's not.
I got a phone call today.
A judge in Queens is retiring,
so...
I'm gonna be a judge.
Yes! Yes!
Judge Eriksen!
Yeah!
One more.
I told you the phone would
ring. You deserve this.
Thanks, Lily.
- I love you, Marshmallow.
- Oh.
1:45 a.m.
Well, you were right, Barney,
this night was, in fact,
legendary, but...
I know what you're gonna say
and I agree.
We're going to Vegas!
I will be awakened
by screaming children
in less than...
four-and-a-half hours.
You're staying.
I'm going.
Judge Fudge,
your very first ruling?
He stays.
Hey! See?
Tonight is about
celebrating our enduring bond
as friends.
Nay, family. Because
that's what we are, Ted.
We are fa...
Okay, fun night,
guys. Keep in touch.
Damn it, Barney.
Crushing... windpipe.
You're lucky that's
the only pipe I'm crushing.
Aah!
That woman is half your age.
Haven't you changed,
even a little?
No. I haven't.
Look, I know
there was a time
when it seemed like I was
capable of going the distance,
but... if it wasn't gonna
happen with Robin,
then it's just not gonna
happen with anyone.
I am never
gonna be a guy
who meets a girl
and, from the first time
I see her, I'm just like,
"You are the
love of my life.
"Everything
I have
and everything I am
is yours forever."
Really?
No, I'm just making a point.
Move it along.
That's not me.
I'm the guy
who straightens his tie,
says something dirty,
high-fives himself
and then goes and talks
to that girl over there.
That's me.
Can I please... just be me?
Judge Fudge?
I'll allow it.
Then I'll a-plow it. Self-five.
Stinson out.
Oh!
Hey, so are you guys
ever gonna tie the knot
or are you...
are you just comfortable
living in sin?
Someone's gotten a bit...
judge-y.
Oh!
- Sustained.
- Yeah.
We'll get around to it.
It's just, you know,
with life and
jobs and kids.
Plus, this one's still
insisting on getting married
in a French castle.
I'd get married tomorrow
in a White Castle,
but this guy needs
more "wow factor."
You're all the wow factor
I need.
Aw!
Glad someone can be happy
on the day of a tragedy.
Aw, Barney,
you know this is
all fake, right?
That robot's
not really dead.
I'm not
talking about the robot, Lily.
Everyone,
stop having fun! I'm about
to tell a sad story!
Guys, remember back in 2010
when I achieved a perfect week?
Seven girls in
seven nights, sure.
Well, recently,
I decided to attempt...
a perfect month.
I put together
a brand-new playbook.
No, I can't hear this.
This is just too sad.
But I haven't gotten
to the sad part yet.
You're in your 40s and
you have a playbook.
That's
the sad part.
Lily... just...
Okay?
So I put together
a brand-new playbook,
filled with plays
I'd never tried before, like...
...where,
as in the '80s classic,
I magically come to life,
if you know what I mean.
...where I wait till a girl
mentions something she likes.
God, I love nachos.
Thank you.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Jim,
Jim Nacho.
Inventor of the nacho.
So... did you get
a perfect month?
Yes.
Then why are
you so upset?
That last girl, number 31...
Oh, that's a pretty name.
What is that, French?
...she's pregnant.
Wait, you're messing
with us, right?
You didn't really
get a girl pregnant?
It's real.
She's pregnant.
Kinda puts an asterisk,
on the whole perfect
month thing, huh?
Barney,
are you okay?
Ah, Jim Nantz.
Thank goodness. You're always
here for me in times of trouble.
What should I do?
You're on your own
this time, bro.
Congratulations, Papa.
Stop it. This is a disaster.
Why?
Why? Because I'm too old.
I was about
to enter my golden years,
my Clooney years,
my daddy issues years,
where I don't just remind
messed-up girls of their dads
because I'm emotionally distant.
I freaking look like
their dads. That's the dream.
My life
is over.
So where are you guys
registered?
Another fun fact about the
Goliath National Bank building,
the sleek but historical facade
has been described
by Architecture Vision Monthly
as "modern classicism."
I can see that.
Mm-hmm. Any questions
from the group?
I have a
question.
What happened to the building
that used to be here?
It was way nicer.
Robin!
Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in...
Greece, uh, Morocco, Moscow.
Yeah, World Wide News
keeps me pretty busy.
And pretty famous.
I mean, you're everywhere.
I am not everywhere. The...
Okay, I'm some places.
Hi, Penny.
Oh, my gosh, I haven't
seen you in forever.
I like you, bus lady.
Oh,
I like you, too.
Never call me that again.
And that was it.
Wow.
Hm.
A genuine Scherbatsky sighting
out in nature.
At this point, that's
like seeing Sasquatch.
No, Sasquatch is a warm
and affectionate creature.
At this point, Robin's
more like the yeti--
cold and aloof.
Hey, Ted.
Ask me if the Abominable
Snowman called.
Has the Abominable Snowman
called?
Not yeti.
Here we are again.
Another big moment for us,
and Robin's missing it.
I know, baby.
I mean, the birth of her
ex-husband's love child
is a bit of a stretch--
but I know, baby.
Well?
It was... crazy in there,
but...
I threw up,
and now I feel better.
Where were you?
In the can.
I knew I was gonna urp,
so I put this on over my suit.
Number 31 won't let me
in the delivery room.
We're gonna need a name
eventually.
Mr. Stinson?
Yes?
Congratulations.
Congratulations because
the blood test came back
and I'm not the father?!
Happy Not a Father's Day!
No. Congratulations.
It's a girl.
Would you like to meet her?
Nah, I'm good.
I don't...
Oh, just go meet your daughter!
This is Ellie.
I'll give you guys
a minute.
You are the love
of my life.
Everything I have...
and everything I am...
...is yours.
Forever.
What?
Do I have stuff in my teeth?
Give me your
engagement ring back.
Just because I have
stuff in my teeth?
We-we can work through this.
Just give it back.
If you don't get married in that
time, you have to re-propose.
Will you...
Yes. Yes, you silly man.
Let me finish.
Will you...
Yes! Sorry.
Yes.
Will y...
Will you marry me...
on Thursday?
I called your office--
you got nothing on Thursday.
Will you marry me on Thursday?
Yes.
Same ring.
I can't believe it.
It's Ted Mosby's wedding day!
Yes! After only seven
years and two kids.
Guys, am I rushing
into this?
Whoa.
Oh, buddy, are you okay?
So tired.
Baby no sleepy.
Barney dying.
Well, we're staying out till
3:00 a.m. tonight.
9:45!
Seriously, though,
I am so proud of you.
Not that
you're a dad.
It's like
you're a totally
different pers...
Whoa!
And... we're back.
Hey.
Hi.
What to join us for shots?
Shots?
Before lunch on a Thursday?
It's like you're trying
to make bad decisions.
You young ladies
need to go home,
put on some
decent clothes
and take a good hard look
at your lives. Get!
Call your parents--
they're probably worried sick.
I have officially
seen everything.
Not everything.
Hi.
I-I know I've...
missed a couple lately, but...
we said we'd always be there
for the big moments.
Aw, crap.
Mascara running.
Nobody let her
out of your sight.
Hi, Daddy.
Whoa.
Look, Robin,
I'm really happy to see you,
but I don't think of you
that way anymore.
, dummy,
you had a kid.
Congrats.
Right, yeah.
Thanks. A kid.
I'm tired.
Oh.
But, uh,
she's awesome.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Daddy's home.
Mm.
Judge Fudge? Hey?
Hey...
Actually, um, little
announcement for everybody.
I'm gonna be running
for State Supreme Court.
Yeah. So if
everything goes well,
in a couple of months,
you won't be calling me
Judge Fudge anymore.
You'll be calling me
Fudge Supreme.
The man of the hour.
Yeah.
You RSVP'd no.
I did.
But someone pretty persuasive
talked me into it.
Sorry. I know
it's bad luck
to see the bride
in her dress.
Worth it.
But I couldn't miss this.
I want to get
a picture.
Get in! I want to take
a picture of you guys.
Come on, get together.
Are you ready?
All right, get in.
All right. All right.
One, two,
three.
Hey. Hey, you kids.
Yeah, you didn't sound
a thousand there.
Do you have any idea
what happened right here
in this very bar?
No. What happened?
Just...
...just all kinds of stuff.
A toast.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, first off...
to everyone at
this table...
...I love you
guys so much,
I can't even...
Just move to the second part.
Okay, okay.
Secondly, to Ted...
Don't say it.
...Evelyn Mosby.
Thank you for that.
A man with...
more emotional endurance
than anyone I know.
It was a long,
difficult road.
Thank God we
finally got here.
Hear, hear.
Aunt Lily wasn't wrong.
It was at times
a long, difficult road.
But I'm glad it was
long and difficult,
because if I hadn't gone
through hell to get there,
the lesson might
not have been as clear.
You see, kids,
right from the moment
I met your mom, I knew...
I have to love this woman
as much as I can
for as long as I can, and
I can never stop loving her,
not even for a second.
I carried that lesson with me
through every
stupid fight we ever had,
every 5:00 a.m.
Christmas morning,
every sleepy Sunday afternoon,
through every speed bump.
Every pang of jealousy
or boredom or uncertainty
that came our way,
I carried that lesson with me.
And I carried it with me
when she got sick.
Even then, in what can only
be called the worst of times,
all I could do was look at her
and thank God,
thank every god there is,
or ever was, or will be,
and the whole universe,
and anyone else
I can possibly thank...
♪ Will I see you tonight?
...that I saw
that beautiful girl
on that train platform,
and that I had the guts
to stand up,
walk over to her,
tap her on the shoulder,
open my mouth,
and speak.
Excuse me. Hi.
Hi.
I'm the...
The best man. Yeah. Get in here,
get in here, get in here.
Oh, thanks. Here, let me.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Great show tonight. Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
You're Cindy's
ex-roommate, right?
Yeah. And you are the professor.
I took one of your classes.
Really? Which one?
Mm-hmm.
Econ 305.
I don't teach...
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me, I'm gonna jump
onto the tracks now. - No.
No, no, no, don't.
You were great, you were great.
Wait a second.
This is my umbrella.
I left this umbrella at Cindy's--
you totally stole my umbrella.
What? No, I didn't.
This is my umbrella.
I bought this.
Excuse me. It even
has my initials
on it right here: T.M.
Ted Mosby.
Yeah. Look again,
Those are my
T.M.
Tracy McConnell.
Um, no, Tracy McConnell,
it's T.M.--
Totally My umbrella.
Uh, your T.M.--
Terribly Mistaken,
because this umbrella has
always belonged T.M.:
To Me.
Although... I did lose it
for a few years there.
Um... so, I went to
this dance club...
On St. Patrick's Day.
...on St. Patrick's Day.
And you left it there.
And I left it there.
And you never thought
you'd see it again.
And I never thought
I'd see it again.
Funny how sometimes you just...
find things.
♪ Will I see you tonight?
Hi.
♪ Every night
♪ It's just the same ♪
♪ All upon a downtown train.
And that, kids...
is how I met your mother.
That's it?
That's it.
No. I don't buy it.
That is not the reason
you made us listen to this.
Oh, really?
Then what's the reason?
Let's look at
the facts here.
You made us sit down
and listen to this story
about how you met mom.
Yet mom's hardly
in the story. No.
This is a story
about how
you're totally in love
with Aunt Robin.
And you're thinking
about asking her out,
and you want to know
if we're okay with it.
I can't believe this.
I kept this story short
and to the point,
and you guys still missed it.
The point of the story
is that...
Is that you totally, totally, totally
have the hots for Aunt Robin.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
You're grounded.
Wow, you are really
into Aunt Robin.
You're grounded, too.
Okay, suppose I were interested
in Aunt Robin in that way--
it's not like
I'd do anything about it.
I got you guys to think about.
My gosh,
we love Aunt Robin.
Whenever she comes over
for dinner, you guys
are so obvious.
Come on, Dad.
Mom's been gone
for six years now.
It's time.
What, I just...
just call her up on the phone
and ask her out on a date?
Yes.
And that... that's something
you guys would want?
Yes!
All right, I'll give her a call.
Do it.
I am.
Call her.
I'm calling her.
Great.
Here I go.
Or...
All right, home sweet home.
Oh. Wait one second.
Okay.
Stay.
We'll work on that.
Television, display
front door security.
Television, dis...
Oh, for Pete's sakes.
♪ May come and go
♪ Our crooked dreams
♪ Will always flow
♪ Remember
♪ Remem...
♪ Ber
♪ All we fight for
♪ Remember
♪ Remem...
♪ Ber
♪ All we fight for
♪ Remember
♪ Remem...
♪ Ber
♪ All we fight for
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh...
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net