Well, that party was a dud.
I think I struck out
with, like, 20 girls.
And...
my condom expired.
We are losers!
We've tried everything.
We're covered
in Drakkar,
I've got fresh
new white socks,
and I thought our
mime work in there
was excellent!
What?
Um, are we in a zombie
movie right now?
Boys...
today is your lucky day.
Because today...
I'm gonna teach you
how to...
...live.
Who's got gum?
♪ How I Met Your Mother 9x17 ♪
Sunrise
Original Air Date on February 3, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Kids, for a brief period
when I was seven,
my best friend was a balloon.
It was the classic story:
boy meets balloon,
boy and balloon become friends,
boy loses balloon
when Mom sets out hot dogs
in the backyard.
No!
Decades later, boy's new
best friend finds out
about the whole thing and never
lets him live it down.
I hate you so much.
The whole thing
taught me a lesson.
If you love something,
you can never let it go,
not even for a second,
or it's gone forever.
Well, at least
I still got my hot dogs.
No!
It was a lesson that took me
nearly 30 years to unlearn.
Where could Barney be?
Oh, relax.
He always finds his way home.
St. Patrick's
Day, 2008.
He did not find his
way home that night.
That Dumpster was
a block from his apartment.
I call that a win.
Also, that isn't the filthiest trash
he's ever slept with.
Ho! My future
husband, folks!
Or maybe he bailed
on the wedding.
Oh, come on.
Don't even
think like that.
Well, he's terrified
of commitment--
although, ironically,
loves being tied down...
Look, as the run-offee
at my own almost-wedding,
I can tell you
you are fine.
Barney is no Stella.
Mmm.
Hey, have you talked
to her in a while?
Stella?
Yeah.
The woman who
broke my heart
and embarrassed me
in front of
all my friends
and loved ones?
Uh... no.
That was a lie.
A few days earlier,
I had talked
to Stella on the phone.
Because, as you may recall,
I'm kind of
the wedding gift master.
Okay, I'm gonna stop you.
Do you not hear
how weird this all sounds?
What part of this is weird?
You're going to your
ex-girlfriend's wedding.
It's not weird at all.
Where you'll be the best man...
Utterly not weird.
And now, less than
a week before the wedding,
you're calling the woman
who left you at the altar
and moved three time zones away
on the razor-thin chance
that I somehow ended up
with her grandmother's locket?
You know what's weird, Stella?
Not seeing Star Wars
until you're 30.
You're trying
to blow up the wedding.
You called C-3PO "the Tin Man."
He is made of tin!
It's Tatooine scrap metal!
This is not an argument
you are gonna win.
Now, do you have
the locket or not?
Look, I might have it somewhere
in one of my old boxes
in our storage locker,
but even if I did, I cannot get
out there this week.
I'm totally swamped.
One ticket to Los Angeles,
please.
So the reason someone
can't come up
to fix the air conditioning
is that the ghost
of Captain Dearduff,
who haunts this room,
likes it muggy?
That's correct.
Although, now that
I say it out loud,
it does sound
kind of ridiculous,
because there's
no such thing as ghosts.
Right?
You have outflanked me,
Front Desk Guy!
Victory is yours!
The truth is, there was
a ghost in that room.
You see, minutes earlier,
Marshall had been in the middle
of the worst fight
of his marriage,
when all of sudden,
Lily stormed out.
Damn it, Lily.
This is so unfair.
I know!
Storming out in
the middle of an argument?
So childish!
Thank you,
Ghost Lily.
I'm glad at least
you see it that way.
Although, let's be honest,
I did you a favor.
You were gonna lose.
I... what?
I was gonna lose?
Uh, check your spectral
scorecard, Ghost Lily.
I had you on the ropes.
That's why you ran out.
I ran out because
you brought up San Francisco.
It was a valid point.
It's ancient history.
If you're mad at anyone,
you're mad at 2006 Lily.
Well, I can't very well
have an argument with 2006...
Is nice!
Do people still say that?
I'm sorry,
how exactly
are you gonna
teach us how to live?
The journey to awesome
starts with a single...
Actually, lots of singles.
We're going to a strip club.
Strip club?
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
There is always
a strip club.
Hey, are you a little worried
this guy might kill us?
We just put a down payment
on adult bunk beds.
Would getting killed
really be so bad?
Good point.
I got a weird feeling.
I mean, there's
something off about...
Whoa!
Question: why does this sign
say "gentlemen's club"?
Answer: because The Crab Shed
is a place for gentlemen.
A gentleman
tips generously.
A gentleman uses
the complimentary
bathroom cologne...
...but not too much.
Oh. This is
important.
Your instinct may be
to avoid the free buffet.
Your instinct is wrong.
Don't sleep on the meatballs,
gentlemen.
They are
exquisite!
Come on!
You know,
I liked Stella.
Even though she
broke your heart,
I'd still put her
in your top five.
Which are...?
All right, number five, Stella.
Mm-hmm.
Number four,
Zoey.
Number three, uh,
the Slutty Pumpkin.
Ah.
Number two,
Marshall,
that time you guys
pretended to be a couple
when Barney was trying
to sell the apartment.
And number one,
Victoria.
Well, you've given
this some thought.
Well, we all have.
There's kind of a running
e-mail chain about it.
But the pastry chef
was the best.
No question.
I do miss her
sticky buns.
Uh, euphemism?
Nope.
Can I be honest?
Um, it was kind of crazy
how all of sudden
it was just... over
between you and Victoria.
I mean...
you guys were seven
years in the making.
She left her fiancé
for you.
What... why would
you break up?
What happened?
We, um...
we broke up because of you.
Oh, my God,
this is amazing!
I ruined my pants, but
it's totally worth it!
Best meatballs ever!
Mmm!
I'm gonna ask
a serious question
right now.
Can a person live
in a strip club?
Yes.
For the next few years,
your strip club
will be like home.
Then, one day,
you'll date a stripper
and almost marry her,
and after that,
you'll realize
you're done with strip clubs.
In the sense that you'll dial it
back to, like, once a week.
I feel like I can talk to women now.
Yeah.
You just stick
a dollar bill in your mouth,
and the conversation
starts itself.
You know, I think we're ready
to go back to that party
and meet some ladies.
Yeah!
You! Are!
Not! Ready!
Your training is complete
when I say
your training is complete!
Come on, let's go.
You-you broke up with Victoria
because of me?
She didn't want us
to be friends anymore,
so I had to let her go.
Ted...
I just...
Wow, I...
And-and you haven't
talked to her since?
Haven't talked to her since.
Also a lie.
Unbelievable.
And I assume this is
all in the hopes
that Robin'll ditch
her own wedding
and run off with you?
What? No.
I would never.
You would never
run off with a girl
on the day of her wedding?
Ri...
Okay, that's a fair point.
I'm not done.
...ight.
So, do you have it?
I'm looking at it right now.
What?
Oh, uh... stay there.
I'm-I'm on my way.
I'm in Germany.
Danke schon!
I see.
Look, if it means
that much to you,
as soon as I'm done
here at the bakery,
I'll overnight it.
It'll be there in 24 hours.
Thank you.
So this bakery,
what kind of, uh...
You want me to send you
some chocolate truffle
streuselkuchen?
Yes, please,
you're the best, thank you.
But then, 24 hours later...
disaster.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mosby.
It says here your package
was delivered earlier today.
Your wife signed for it.
My... what?
I... I don't have a wife.
So, then, who's Jeanette Mosby?
Oh, you're kidding me.
Oh, my gosh,
2013 me!
So many questions!
How many MySpace friends
do I have now?
Has James Blunt
put out
the steady stream
of number one hits
we all expect from him?
And why are we in
this hotel room?
We're here for Barney's wedding.
Barney's wedding?
Oh, God.
What desperate ho-bag
is handcuffing herself
to that time bomb?
My dad did a real
number on me.
Okay, uh... Ghost Lily,
seven-years-ago Ghost Lily,
can we get on with this
so I can win the argument
and we can move on to my
regularly scheduled fantasy
of you two making out
with each other?
Sure.
Just so you know,
I really like it when...
I know.
I'm you.
And I don't like
that anymore.
Okay, yes,
seven-years-ago Lily,
maybe I am wrong
for still being mad at you
about San Francisco
and our breakup.
But the truth is,
when you left me,
that was the saddest
I've ever been in my life.
Really?
The saddest you've
ever been in your life?
Saddest I've ever been
in my life.
I mean, I am
sitting right here.
Look, Dad, yes, obviously,
losing you was way worse,
but I'm trying to make
a bigger point here.
And what point is that?
Because she hurt you once,
you now get to hurt her?
It's not how it works
in a marriage.
Ooh...
You're totally gonna lose.
I can't believe
you're open at this hour.
I'm always open
for my friends.
What are we doing here?
We should go back
to the party.
In relaxed-fit domestic denim?
I'm sorry,
is this a costume party,
and you're going as 1994?
Would you be a peach
and bump this, please?
Who cares
about any of this?
They're just clothes.
Just clothes? Ted--
sorry, force of habit--
boys, suits are cool.
Exhibit A.
I don't care
how well-dressed I am.
The real challenge is walking
up to a girl
that I've never met before
and somehow talking to her
with words from my mouth.
I've looked at it
from every possible angle.
There's just no way to do it.
What's your name?
Justin.
Have you met Justin?
Uh, no. Hi, I'm Julie.
So simple, so elegant.
Hmm.
That's it?
You just walk up to someone
you don't know
and introduce them
to your buddy?
I don't know.
That sounds kind of...
Have you met Kyle?
Hi, Kyle.
Are you Jesus?!
I would have understood,
you know?
I mean, if you told me
that we couldn't be friends
anymore,
I-I wouldn't have liked it,
but I, God,
I would have understood.
I could never do that.
Why not?
Ted, okay, I insist
that you tell me why not.
No way.
Answer the question.
It's... it's for the bride.
I'm not gonna answer
the question,
because you know the answer.
You want to talk
about my top five?
There's no top five, Robin!
There's just a top one,
and it's you.
And the only reason I'm saying
any of this is 'cause
I know that it's not gonna
change anything.
You and Barney are getting
married today.
If I have to hold the shotgun
myself, it's happening.
I thought you don't like guns.
I'm the best man.
I swore on the Bro Code.
I don't want to go to Bro Hell.
Bro Hell sounds bad.
I'm sure Barney's got
a whole thing about Bro Hell.
But what about when we
get back from our honeymoon?
What about our first night out
at the bar?
But what then?
I mean, is it gonna be weird?
No.
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm not gonna be there.
I'm moving to Chicago.
You're moving to Chicago?
That's right.
I'm gonna work
for Hammond Druthers.
The penis-building guy?
They're not all penis buildings.
They just designed
this clamshell amphitheater
for the St. Louis Symphony.
That one, it doesn't look
like a penis, anyway.
I can't believe
you're leaving New York.
Wait, is this be--
is this because of me?
No, it's not because of you.
Well, maybe at first
it was, but...
It's been a really long week.
Some stuff has happened and...
it's just made me feel like
it's, it's time to move on.
Yes, good things happened
to me in New York,
but bad things happened, too.
Like your top five
worst relationships?
Okay, come on. Let me hear it.
Number five, Blah Blah.
Mm-hmm.
Number four,
boats, boats, boats.
Number three, Karen.
Mm.
Number two, uh, Zoey.
She made both lists.
Number one, by a landslide,
Jeanette.
Jeanette, of course.
By the way,
have you talked
to Jeanette lately?
- I haven't talked to her.
- Liar.
So I was at your apartment
stealing your mail,
and apparently there's
some chick named Victoria
sending you jewelry
from Germany?
Somebody owes somebody
an explanation.
Jeanette, that locket
is a wedding gift for Robin.
Robin?! Oh, God, this again?
That I'm giving
to her as a friend
because I'm kind
of the wedding gift master!
Now bring it back
to me right now!
Fine. Meet me
at the Bow Bridge
in Central Park in one hour.
And by the way,
I want Kenny back.
Who's Kenny?!
My pet tarantula.
By the way, I love your hair.
I love your hair!
Imaginary women, right?
I need everyone
to just be quiet, please.
Look, I know that I could
have handled all of this better.
But setting aside the fact
that all of our friends are here
and that we don't speak Italian,
if we stay in New York, we both
get to follow our dreams.
Are we really gonna go someplace
where only one of us gets
to do that?
Of course not.
Well, then how can you...?
Wait-- what?
We're not moving to Italy.
We have a baby.
It makes sense to stay here.
Even I know that.
You do?
So... I win?
Well, then, ho, hey, ho.
In your ethereal face,
Ghost Lily.
Oh, yeah, the Convincer
right here!
She thought I was gonna lose.
You are gonna lose.
You're gonna lose this.
If you keep lying to me,
if you keep cutting me out
of decisions,
if you keep using words
like "winning" and "losing"
when you talk
about our marriage.
It's not like it'll happen
all at once,
but if you keep acting
this way,
little by little,
you're gonna lose me.
Is that what you want?
No, of course not.
You're not my enemy.
You're my wife.
My wife!
Right?
No. Sorr... sorry.
We should
probably head back.
Do you want to watch
the sun come up?
Sure.
Thanks for meeting me here.
I'm heading over to the East
Side to stuff a dead squirrel
into a different
ex-boyfriend's mailbox,
so, you know, this made sense.
Of course.
So, can I have the locket?
No.
What? Jeanette...
Ted, listen to me.
You're being crazy.
I'm being crazy?!
Yes! How long have you been
hung up on Robin?
Eight years?!
And you're still
killing yourself
to fetch dumb little trinkets
for her. That's crazy!
That's more than crazy.
I don't think there's a word
for what that is!
Actually, there is a word
for that. It's "love."
I'm in love with her, okay?
If you're looking for the word
that means caring about someone
beyond all rationality
and wanting them to have
everything they want,
no matter how much
it destroys you, it's love!
And when you love someone,
you just, you...
you don't stop, ever.
Even when people roll their
eyes or call you crazy.
Even then. Especially then!
You just-- you don't give up!
Because if I could give up...
if I could just, you know,
take the whole world's advice
and-and move on and find someone
else, that wouldn't be love.
That would be...
that would be some other
disposable thing
that is not worth fighting for.
But I--
that is not what this is.
So, please, can I have
the locket?
Cuckoo.
I think we should
get back together.
And... new day.
Yep, new day.
♪ Close your eyes...
Okay, you need to get
at least a little sleep.
♪ Do you feel
my heart beating? ♪
♪ Do you understand?
♪ Do you feel the same?
A few final thoughts.
Don't get married
until you're 30.
Play laser tag once a week.
Give at least as many high fives
as you get.
Teacup pigs are lady magnets,
but very hard to care for.
Not worth the effort.
The same goes for dogs
and babies.
And most importantly,
whatever you do in this life,
it's not legendary
unless your friends are there
to see it.
Good luck, boys.
Take care of
the game for me.
We will.
Did you ever get
his name?
No. What'd he give you?
I don't know,
but I think it's important.
♪ I don't want to lose
this feeling ♪
Lil-Lily...
I love you. And I'm so sorry.
It doesn't matter
where we live.
I just want us
to be together.
We're staying in New York.
What? No.
Yes.
It just makes sense.
I've missed you so much.
♪ Am I only dreaming?
I have to let go now.
♪ Is this burning
I know you do.
♪ An eternal flame?
♪ Close your eyes,
give me your hand, darling ♪
♪ Do you feel
my heart beating? ♪
♪ Do you understand?
♪ Do you feel the same?
♪ Am I only dreaming?
When we went out
on our first date,
at the end
of the night,
did you want me
to kiss you?
Yeah, I did.
Damn it!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net