Kids,
there's nothing   more wonderful
than new york city   in the winter...
except   the view of new york city
in the winter   through your apartment window.
In the winter of 2006,
marshall,lily,robin and I were all deep
in couple hibernation mode.
Sadly,
this left uncle barney   out in the cold.
Okay. All-night rave,
abandoned tire factory  in newark.
We're on the list.
Who's in?
- Nope.
- No.
Private jet.
Teeterboro airport,skinny-skydiving.
- Who's in?
- Nope.No,thanks.
One beer.Bar,
downstairs,15 second walk.
Who's in?
Lily went sleepy-bye.
It got so bad,
barney   tried to be his own wingman.
Hi.
Have you met me?
A@   finally,
he decided   to bring in reinforcements.
No.
Yes.
And do you know why?
Hang on to your bedsores,
grandparents from willy wonka,
because guess who's  on his way up
to this apartment right now?
My...
wait for it...
brother,
james.React.
Hey!
- You have a brother?
- Yeah.
He's the "awesome-est," most best "looking-est,
"  greatest guy ever.
He's exactly like barney.
That's what I just said.
Well,barney and his brother  aren't exactly alike.
- James is gay.
- Really?
I neve  r in amillion years
would I picture you  with a gay brother,
that's awesome.
Yeah.
I just wanted you  to have a heads up,
so you don't  act all surprised
when he gets here.
Here he is.
What up,
new york.
Thanks for the heads up.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
HOW I MEET YOUR MOTHER
Season 02  Episode 10
What did it never come up  that barney has a  gay,
black brother?
Is he black?
I guess I'm the kind  of person
that focuses  on who people are
on the inside  rather than the
color  of their skin.
I'm kidding,
I just  wanted to see your face.
Yeah,so now the  wedding's back on.
Anyway,james,
how have you been?
Awesome,as per "yoozh.
"  I just went  skinny-skydiving.
Legendary.
And my laser tag team,
just made it to  regional finals.
"Legendarier.
"  And by now you've  noticed the suit--
go 'head,
touch it.
Handcrafted  by pietro dellacamera,
milan's famous  101-year-old tailor
who upon completing  the very last
stitch  in this suit  dropped dead,
which is ironic  because that is
how  gorgeous I look  in it.
C'mon.
gimme five.
- Is "gimme five" back?
- Oh,yeah.
I put it in my  blog this morning.
Guys,
"gimme five"  is back!
Oh,james,
this is  my girlfriend,robin.
- Hey.It's so nice to meet you.
- You,too.
So,I have to ask,
there's a story here.
Please.
Be the truth is,
barney and james   got a lot of...
different explanations
from their mom over the years.
Well,boys,
you  look different  because
when I was  pregnant with you,
I only ate  vanilla ice cream.
And when I was  pregnant with you,
can you guess what kind  of ice cream I ate?
Coffee?
No,james,
I ate chocolate  ice cream.
But I did drink  tons of coffee
when I was pregnant  with both of you.
Can't smoke  without my coffee.
I don't know,boys,
I guess  it's just one of those things.
Stop asking me!
You know what  you two are?
You're little racists!
So what are you guys  gonna do tonight?
I'll tell you  what james is gonna do.
He's gonna do the job
you've been neglecting.
And,as always,
he'll do it  a lot better
than you ever did.
Ted...
james is my wingman now.
Okay.
Last time james  was in town,
barney got slapped once,
lucky twice,
and...
whose penthouse hot tub
did you end up in?
Ah,public figure,
confidentiality agreement.
But I will say this:
Way more back hair than any guy
who can afford laser hair
removal should have.
And then there was the time
they scored the  brother/sister combo.
It was everything  we ever dreamed
of when watching   donnie and marie.
She was a little bit country.
He was a little bit  way into black guys.
Yeah,barney and james together
was a lethal combination.
Since there was never
any crossover in targets,
james was always there
for barney with the assist.
Whoa.
Your scarf...
it is fierce!
Thanks.
H & M.
What?I would never know,'cause it is so hot
that my eyes are melting.
Oh,I can't see.
Hey!You know,speaking of things
that would look good  wrapped around you,
have you met my straight  brother,
barney?
Oh,he is fab--
don't you go nowhere--
"ulous.
" Okay?
and barney always returned   the favor.
Help,I don't think  he's breathing.
Does anyone know  mouth-to-mouth?
Oh,my god,
I do!
Okay,great.
How  'bout you instead?
Oh,man,
I am so  excited that you're here!
It has been forever  since I have
been around  anyone even remotely fun.
Uh,yes offense.
You guys are still going out  with us tonight,
right?
- No.Jammies.
- I don't think so.
Tonight?
It's after 9:00  and...
I have  warm soup belly.
Oh,no,no,no,no,no.
Guys...
you are young,attractive people here
in the greatest city on earth.
There are boys and girls  in nobody cares,
wyoming,
wishing they could be here.
But instead,they are  in someone's basement
drinking bad malt liquor,
debating  whether or not they're going
to spend their saturday night
in the parking lot  of the feed store
or in some other dude's  basement.
You owe it to them  to rise up and shimmy
your lazy asses  into something hot,
and you go out there
and you live their dream!
Can I get a "hell,
yeah"?
- Hell,
- yeah!
- Can I get a "hell,yeah"?
- Yll,yeah!
- Can I get a "woo-woo"?
- Woo-woo!
- Go do it for wyoming!
- yes!
Testify!
So that night,
barney got his wish.
We all went out.
Daddy's home!
Yeah.
All right,bro.
What do you like?
Guy in super  tight black t?
Super tight black guy?
Guy who looks like mr.    T?
yes,yes,and...
talk to me  after two martinis.
Let's focus on you,
my man.
I'm feeling lazy.
How 'bout girl with  the chocolatini?
Oh...boom,
back tattoo.
Hero and the pig?
Let's ride.
Fo' 'sho.
Damn baby,
nice tramp stamp!
Get off me,
you pig!
Hey!
Her body art  is not an invitation  to grope her,
it's an expression  of her inner self.
I'm sure,in many ways,
she is  the dolphin encircled  by flowers.
- What?
- Cool.
- ***************
Let me know if he  bothers you again.
Thanks.You should stay close...
just in case.
Sure.
If it'll make  you feel safer.
I'm barney.
Now,kids,when you're out   at a noisy,
crowded bar,
you can always tell   the difference
between the singles
and the couples.
You just have to look   for the signs.
- Break.
- Boiling hot.
Singles stay on their feet
for maneuverability.
- Hey!
- Hi,how are ya?
Have you met my brother?
Oh,hello.
Have a drink.
Nice to meet ya.
Couples,exhausted   by the sheer
act of leaving   the house,
are obsessed   with finding   a place to sit down.
There are a lot of other indicators,
too.
From choice   of social lubricant...
To basic body language.
But the point is,
there are many ways to tell
whether someone has   single stamina
r couples coma.
I wish I would've wo sneakers.
I just got finished running  from some fat,
hairy guy  who was periscoping
out of his pleather pants.
Permission  to come aboard denied.
I miss my jammies.
I can't believe i  wore a bra for this.
Bras suck.
They're so  confining and unnatural.
Yeah,they're like  a boobie zoo.
Well,why don't you  take it off
then and let  those puppies breathe?
Oh,please go sweat  on someone else.
Poor guy.
Poor guy?
Poor my boobs.
Well,it takes a lot  of guts to approach
a girl and you  just crushed him.
Oh,yeah,yeah.
He looks  all broken up inside.
Whatever,you guys have  no idea what
it's like  to be on the  receiving end.
"Oh,poor me.
I'm a pretty girl
"and everybody everywhere  wants
to buy me  drinks and have  sex with me.
"Oh,poor me.
I get  to order yummy,
pink drinks  "with chunks of real
fruit  that guys secretly like,
but can't order because  they'll be made fun of.
- "  Dude.
- They're delicious!
Excuse me.
Join me in a shot?
Oh,no thanks.
I've had enough.
He's too in shape,
we'd spend all night  talking
about  his body fat content.
Now,if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go have  a yummy,
pink drink  with fruit in it...
because I can.
You know,that was,like,the third hot
guy  that james  blew off tonight.
Yeah,he's turning  down shots,
he's yawning,
he's  whining about his feet.
He's as bad as we are.
He is.
Wait,he's exactly  as bad as we are.
You guys don't think  that james is...
in a relationship?
No.There's no way.
He's barney's brother.
Look at that.
He's texting!
Oh,my god!
He is in a couple.
This is gonna kill barney.
What's gonna kill me?
What's going on?
B-barney?
Have you noticed  anything...
different about james?
No.I mean,he's glowing from his  peel,
if that's what you mean.
We have reason  to believe that james is,
uh,maybe hiding  something from you.
I-I know you're not gonna  like hearing this,
but...
barney...
your brother is...
Monogamous.
That's ridiculous!
Just because  he's a little sleepy,
and he hasn't had sex  with anyone
in a bathroom stall...
He hasn't had sex with
in a bathroom stall.
And,barney...
I hate to be the one  to tell you this,
but...
he's texting.
No,he...
no!
That...
is impossible.
Excuse...excuse...
ex...
- hey,bro.
- Don't change the subject.
- Let me see your phone.
- Why?
I just want to  see your phone.
Let me see  your phone.
No,it's just a phone.
It's just a phone!
And it's got internet access,
and it's got a camera on it,
and you can surf the web  and do the whole thing.
It's so amazing how far  technology has come.
What kind of phone  do you have?
I got...
who is this?
And the answer better be:
"I don't remember his name.
"  That is tom.
And he's my fianc?
hi
I don't support this.
Gay marriage?
Not gay marriage--
marriage!
how can you do this?
We were raised in the same  house,
with the same values!
Believe me,
I fought this for a long time.
Come on,
it's embarrassing.
Look,this felt unnatural  to me,
too,at first.
But I fell in love.
And tom and I realized  you can't fight love.
Oh,god.
Is that what  you two do together?
You sit around the house  and talk about love?
I think...
I'm gonna be sick.
Okay,okay,look,I need you
to wrap your head  around this,
okay?
Because it is happening.
And I want you  to be my best man.
What?
No way.
Well,I'm sorry  you feel that way.
I hope you  change your mind.
Two beers,
one shot.
Oh,it's a freaking epidemic.
oh,sweetie!
Did you make that for me?
Yes.
Clam bake.Staten island.
Who's in?
Okay,I didn't   havehigh hopes for that one.
Okay,here's my thing.
If gay guys  start getting married,
then suddenly the whole world's
gonna be doing it.
That's how it works.
They start something,
then six months later,everyone follows.
Like now everyone  gets manicures.
I don't get manicures.
Okay,then like how...
like getting your chest waxed.
:  You get your chest waxed?
You know what I mean!
Gay marriage is going to cause  single life,
as we know it,to die out.
Think of how the american family
will be strengthened.
Barney,
I'm sorry you're upset,
but you got to suck it up
and be a man about this.
No.
It's always been  me and him together,
being awesome,
while the rest  of you walked two-by-two
onto your ark  of sexless boredom.
Just because  james is getting married
doesn't mean things  are going to change.
Yeah.
Like things haven't changed  with you people.
Look,my sister married  a guy I didn't like.
Sandals and socks--
come on,buddy.
But I took her out,
we celebrated.
It was the right  thing to do.
You got to support him.
You're right,ted.
This is a cause for celebration.
We need to take him out
and celebrate the commitment
he and tom are about to make.
yeah.This is where we're  celebrating the
commitment  that tom and i  are about to make?
What?
Yeah!
See,
that cage represents  your commitment.
oh,my god.
Freedom has never tasted  so delicious.
Hey.
You work out?
I do.
And thank you  for noticing.
You're obviously  in very good shape yourself.
Well,I try.
So you want  to dance?
You know what?I'm very flattered,
and,objectively,
you're a very  attractive man,
but this is actually  my fiancéE.
I'm sorry.
You know,I saw  your drink and I...
no,no,this isn't my drink.
This is hers.
No,it isn'T.
Whatever.
How 'bout you?
Oh,I'm straight,
too.
But I thank you  for your time,
and I appreciate  your interest in my body.
U@ryou see that?
Being hit on doesn't  have to be terrible.
I feel flattered,
and everyone  left with their dignity.
hey,I really  like your sweater.
You actually do,don't you?
You're notchecking[
my boobs or anything.
My name's gay ken,
what do you think?
I love this place!
Let's dance!
And not be groped!
Whoo! Thank you.
Damn.
Thank you!
- We're hot.
- Totally.
and then tom says
to the dealer
that the handmade georgian clock
has a chip on the corner.
Blam,we get that puppy half price.
What up?!
Bam!
sounds like you really rocked
that arts and crafts fair.
Oh,yeah,oh,yeah.
Hey,oh,my god.
This is so liberating,being
able to talk about this to you.
I cannot wait
for you to meet tom.
And I cannot wait for you
to meet my good friend...
this guy.
Excuse me,do you know anyone
who would like to buy my incredibly muscular,fun,
large-handed brother a drink?
Eh,eh,eh,let's focus
on you,barnaby.
Okay.
all right.
I spy a group of women who have
let their defenses down
because they are
in a gay club.
You see that chick
right there?
She looks like she'd fall for
sports agent and football player.
Okay,I'm in.
Which one am I?
please.
He's very shy,
loves tennis and brazil,
and drops his pants
after three dirty martinis.
Now go,man,go!
I just never thought I'd
see barney so vulnerable.
Well,I guess no one wants to feel like
they're going through the world alone.
Look at me,in a yummy sandwich!
Okay,we're actually right in the middle
of something right now,so...
ooh,I know what I want to be
in the middle of. Thoughts?
God,can't two straight guys
come to a gay dance club,
enjoy some techno and good conversation
without being bothered?
How's it going,guys?
Still enjoying the attentions of men?
That's like the eighth guy
who's hit on us in ten minutes.
It's like,hello,
my eyes are up here.
and it's never the hot ones.
It's always the losers. Bums me out!
Looks like the boys
learned their lesson.
Do you totally miss
being hit on?
Oh,totally.
Let's go find a sports bar.
James,james,since you like
arts and crafts,
look at what charles here made
with cherry stems.
He did it with
his tongue.
Yeah.
Barney.
So,charles,why don't you put your number
in my brother's phone,
and once he's in
a funner mood...
barney,barney,i
don't want his number.
I don't want anyone's
number,okay?
I'm getting married.
- Best of luck to you both.
- Thank you.
My number's in here.
I'm very discreet.
Okay,okay,
excuse me.
Barney,family talk.
Okay,dude,you have
got to stop this,okay?
I know that my getting married is threatening
to your way of life...
oh,so now it's
my way of life?
I thought it was
our way of life.
You've completely
turned your back on it.
Look at you,
not even suited up.
Do you remember why
we suit up,james?
To get laid.
To show people
that we are different
from the millions of t-shirt
and jeans lemmings out there.
The suit shows that we are a force
to be reckoned with,
a two-person army
that plays by its own rules.
But you've taken off the uniform,
you've crossed enemy lines,
and you've abandoned me.
Well,I'm not gonna let you do that.
It's not too late to back out
of this stupid marriage thing!
You don't have to do this,bro!
- Yes,I do.
- Why?!
Because tom and I are
gonna have a baby.
What? There's gonna be a baby?
Yes.
We're adopting.
Oh,my god.
I'm gonna be an uncle?
For the rest
of your life.
And that's how barney
became uncle barney.
A year later,at james's wedding,
barney could not  have been more proud.
To james and tom.
May you have a long
and happy life together.
And may I always have
the skin and libido of a much younger man.
- Cheers.
Nice one.
Thanks. I decided to leave out
the hetero college phase.
No one wants to hear about that.
It was perfect.
You even made tom's dad cry.
Might have been doing that
because he's a republican.
whoa.
It's 9:00.
We should be getting back.
You guys want to split a cab?
Uh,no,I think I'm gonna
stay a little bit longer.
Yeah,me,too. I'm
not tired at all.
All right,well,it's getting late.
Got to get the wife home.
Oh,stop calling me that.
It makes me sound fat.
**************
Ugh,it's a freaking epidemic.
See ya.
- may I?
- Yeah.
hey,buddy.
Your parents are married.
Now,listen,you.
Just because you're being
raised by married people
doesn't mean you have to choose
that lifestyle. High-five.
Luckily,you got me.
In 20 and a half years,
you'll be 21,
and I will be...
well,I haven't decided
how old I'll be yet.
But we are gonna bro out,
uncle and nephew style.
Stick with me,kid.
I am gonna teach
you how to live.
Great suit,
by the way.
who is the cutest?
I don't get it.
Tom liked my breasts
in tenth grade.
Why doesn't he like them now?
Why?
Rosa,why always be attracted
to the unavailable ones?
Why not accept the fact that you're a
beautiful woman who is worthy of love?
Are you brave enough
to hear that?
You...
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
HOW I MEET YOUR MOTHER
Season 02  Episode 10
www.tvsubtitles.net