???
had been together
for nine wonderful years,
until she dumped him
and ran off to San Francisco.
The healing process
was taking a long time.
(groans)
Then, one night,
he made a giant leap forward.
All right, I'll
see you guys later.
I'll walk you out.
MARSHALL:
See ya.
You just checked out
Robin's ass.
What? No!
N-No, Barney, I was...
Dude, that's awesome.
You're finally
forgetting
-about that short redhead.
-Lily.
Yes, Lily. Thank you.
That was going to drive me
crazy all night.
Hey, Ted, Marshall just checked
out your girlfriend's ass.
-I did not, Ted, I...
-That's awesome.
You're finally
getting better.
This is the moment
I've been waiting for.
Starting tonight, I am going
to teach you how to live.
Ted, you had your chance.
You're out; Marshall's in.
-Yes!
-Oh, God.
Marshall, being a single guy
in New York City is like...
-What's something everybody likes?
-Candy.
Yes, it's like being
in a candy store.
You just walk right in
and grab yourself some Whoppers.
(groans)
Yeah.
Is Whoppers the best one?
Mounds.
Milk Duds.
Gobstoppers.
This went on for another hour;
I'll just skip to the end.
-Dubble Bubbles.
-Nice!
Marshall.
We're doing this.
I am not taking no
for an answer.
-Fine.
(chuckles)
-Hey, Robin.
Marshall checked out your ass.
Ted, what is wrong with you?
He checked out my ass.
Hey, tell him thanks.
I felt like I was having
a bad ass day.
Cool, see ya.
Lily.
It is a great ass.
www.1000fr.com Present
Sync:knlight
???
in three months.
There were so many
unanswered questions,
so many things to say.
Your hair is adorable.
(both giggling)
Meanwhile, Barney was taking
Marshall out to meet women
for the first time
since he was 17.
Just wing it.
Come on.
Hi. Have you
met Marshall?
-Hi.
Look how sweaty my hands are.
It's weird, right? Uh, sweat?
Like, this smelly water
coming out of your skin.
Eww.
It was nice meeting you.
I-I-I hate to
interrupt, but, uh,
do you like magic?
Um, I guess.
(gasps)
Oh, my God!
(laughing)
Anyway, Marshall
here is awesome.
Salad in a bag? His idea.
Dude!
You were awesome last night.
You were charming,
you were funny, you were totally
working that girl.
You went home with her.
Yes, I did.
But she told me
that if it wasn't for me, you
would have had a shot with her,
so, in hypothetical terms,
you scored last night.
All right!
Hypothetical high five.
Nice.
All right. Tonight, we're going
to go to the bar...
Barney, no, I am not going
out with you ever again.
-Come on! I'll, I'll teach you
all of my strategies.
-Oh, really?
My favorite, number seven:
create a mystery about yourself.
That way,
they become so intrigued,
they have to hang out
with you all night.
Oh, come on, does
that really work?
Maybe it does,
and maybe it doesn't.
Damn it, that's intriguing.
Okay, I'm in.
I have something you've
got to hear.
You will not
believe what just happened.
You go first.
I found a 1939 penny
on the subway.
Just imagine
the kind of history
this little copper guy...
Lily's back in town.
And you let me go first?
Have you seen her?
Uh, yeah. I actually went
apartment-hunting
with her today.
How's she doing?
You're not going to like it.
I am doing great.
This summer,
best thing ever!
San Francisco is so
happening right now.
She's happy?!
Marshall had the worst
summer of his life,
and she's happy.
Yeah, and I suppose
her art program
was all fulfilling or whatever.
Oh. The art program--
best thing ever.
Oh, my God.
This is your best work.
In all my years teaching,
I've never seen
anything so...
Needless to say,
this is art.
(chuckles)
I can't teach you anything.
(gasps)
(chuckles)
But the best part of S.F.--
Oh, that's what
we call San Francisco--
the people.
Even just riding around
on the bus all summer.
It was like a human tapestry.
Hi, I'm Mike.
I'm a Buddhist monk slash
adventure-traveler writer.
I'm Paula. I sing in a
punk band for children.
Yeah.
I'm Dan, I'm a neurosurgeon.
You are stunning, by the way.
Wow. I'm so happy for you.
Oh, she's such a...
After what she did to Marshall,
she should come back here
devastated,
crawling on all fours
over the broken glass
of her own shame and regret.
You never chose sides.
I respect that.
She's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
Unbelievable?
What's unbelievable?
Oh. Listen, Marshall.
Ted found a penny
on the subway,
and it's old, and
that's interesting.
Way to go.
Okay, first of all,
that is interesting.
Second, we have
to tell him.
No, we don't.
He's just starting to get
better, going out with Barney.
I mean, how do you think
he's going to feel
when he hears
Lily's moved on?
She's moved on?
It happens.
I've fallen out of love
faster than that before,
sometimes, boom, with
no warning whatsoever.
One day we're in love,
the next day, he's dead to me.
But we're great. Honey.
Now, let's review
Barney's rules for
mating without dating.
Lesson two, corollary five.
Make a beautiful woman feel
self-conscious and unattractive,
and she'll be
putty in your hands.
Excellent.
Have you chosen your entree?
I have. Sweet brunette,
eight o'clock.
Nine o'clock. Ten... thirty.
She's walking to the bar.
Her? Really?
Yeah.
No, you're right.
Ambition is the enemy
of success.
Okay. Hit it.
(smacks lips)
What's the matter, four eyes,
you got astigmatism
or something?
I'm sorry, I was trying
to playfully disarm you,
but I just got out
of a long relationship.
I have no idea
what I'm doing.
I'm Marshall.
Hi, Marshall. Amy.
Don't worry. I've been there.
Hold on.
Nice recovery.
I think it's working.
Um, Amy.
This is my friend, Barney.
Barney, this is Amy.
Hi, Barney.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
Amy, do you like... magic?
-I hate you.
-I am so sorry.
It's a sickness.
I'm the real victim here.
Twice.
Twice in a row,
you took my candy.
That was my candy.
I know, but tonight...
No.
Forget it.
You're such a jackass.
I thought you were gonna
call me a jerk.
All right, I'm sorry.
I will make it up to you.
Tonight, we'll go
to a college bar
near NYU--
The Scorpion and the Toad.
I figure
in a younger crowd
you'll seem more mature,
more worldly
and, as a third-year
law student, more smarter.
Okay, but no magic.
How did you do that?
I'm taking a leak, dumb ass.
Robin and I met Lily
outside the next apartment
she was seeing.
But I need the freedom
to really chase my passion,
which was painting,
but now I think
it's music
or spoken word-- maybe both.
God! Isn't life amazing?
It is so great
to see you, Ted.
I'm going to get the key
from the lockbox.
What?
She's miserable.
She's realized she's
made a huge mistake.
Her and Marshall will be back
together in a week.
-I love it!
-Um, no. You just
want Lily to be miserable.
The truth is, she's happy.
Trust me. I've known
Lily for nine years.
Trust me. I'm a girl.
Yeah, but you're Canadian.
Why do you always
have to bring that up?
You're our weird
neighbors to the north.
You bring it up every time.
All right,
five bucks says
she still wants Marshall.
You're on.
-Five American bucks.
-Damn it.
Okay, so how do we get
the truth out of her.
Tequila. It's
her weakness.
Three shots, she'll tell you
the truth about anything.
I hope this is my new home.
Yeah, I'm going to take
that first apartment.
(knocking)
Marshall Eriksen, suit up!
-No way.
-Yeah, you're good in that.
Let's go.
(clears throat)
Wait.
Empty your pockets.
Come on.
Come on, let's...
(clears throat)
Sleeves.
There is nothing in my...
Oh, is that right?
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
(clears throat)
Behind my ear.
There is nothing behind your...
BOTH:
Oh.
WOMAN:
Yeah, I'm in pre-law.
The workload's
killing me, though.
Oh, tell me about it.
I'm third year
at Columbia Law, so...
Hmm.
if the workload
does kill you, I can
probably get a conviction.
(both laughing)
Yeah.
You must be majoring in
chemistry,
'cause what I'm picking
up between us is, uh...
College lesbian phase.
Listen, I got to go,
but it'd be great
to see you again.
Yes, it would.
It really would.
Well, maybe I'll
see you here sometime.
Probably not.
I'm never here, so...
You know, I do have
a phone number.
Great. Nice.
Hi, I'm Barney.
Oh, no.
Do you...
mind giving my friend
your phone number?
Sure.
Whoo!
I did it! I got
a girl's phone number.
Oh, and her handwriting
is so cute, look.
Oh, I'm gonna take
her out for Chinese food
and then maybe we'll
walk through the park.
It'll be so... what?
Sorry, buddy, I'm
taking this one, too.
I'll kill you!
And then, I discovered
this area, North Beach.
Best beach ever!
Oh, I've been
blabbering on about my summer.
How are you guys doing?
And hey, how's Marshall?
Give me the card!
I'm not giving you any card.
I swear...!
You are not getting...!
Terrific.
That is so good to hear.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, hold on.
This could be
about the apartment.
(ringing continues)
Okay, we're way past
truth-telling-Lilly
and about to hit
Cinco-de-Mayo-1998-Lilly
and I'm not cleaning
that up again.
So, congratulations,
you win.
She's happy.
I didn't get it.
That first apartment, I...
I waited too long and...
somebody else got it.
(crying)
Interesting.
Wow, Lily,
you, uh...
seem to be having a
pretty strong reaction
on losing an apartment.
I wonder if it's
because it reminds you
of something else
you lost because
you couldn't commit.
(continues crying)
No, Lily,
you're crying
over the crown molding
and the real
hardwood floors.
There's no
deeper meaning.
Right, Lily? Just quit
crying and tell him.
(crying continues)
The apartment is a metaphor
for Marshall.
-stop it.
-You don't want to see
what I'm like
when I'm angry.
Stop! Hold on!
If we can't settle
this like gentlemen,
then no one
gets the number.
(screams)
Stop the cab.
Wha...?
(tires screech)
No, wait. Come on.
Marshall!
(door closes)
81st and First, please.
Ah, she does have
cute handwriting.
TED:
The thing about a hangover
is that everyone has their
own special remedy.
WAITER:
Morning, guys.
What can I get you?
Shh!
Bring me the dirtiest,
greasiest tuna melt you got.
And a milkshake.
For you, sir?
Gravy.
You want that gravy
on something?
Surprise me.
I'd take you with gravy
if my boyfriend wasn't
sitting right here.
Just kidding. I'm good.
What are you so chirpy about?
She's still drunk
from last night.
I don't think so.
Whoo!
Look, if you want
Marshall back so bad,
how come it took you two
days to even ask about him?
I was dying to ask.
I was just trying
to play it cool.
But really...
But it's good, I mean,
work is great...
LILY:
Come on, say something
about Marshall.
Where's Marshall?
How's Marshall?
What's Marshall
doing right now?
Shut up and talk
about Marshall.
Shut up
and talk about Marshall.
Shut up and talk
about Marshall.
Marshall, Marshall,
Marshall, Marshall...
I've got to ask!
And hey, how's Marshall?
It was such an awful summer.
I just wanted to get
back here and see him.
But I thought
your summer was great.
Not exactly.
Oh, my God.
This is you best work?
In all my years teaching,
I've never seen anything
so needless.
To say this is... art...
I can't teach you anything.
So all those interesting people
you met on the bus?
Yeah, um...
Hi. I'm Mike.
I'm a Buddhist monk slash
adventure travel writer.
(imitating woman):
I'm Paula. I sing
in a punk band for children.
(deep voice):
I'm Dan. I'm
a neurosurgeon.
You are stunning,
by the way.
I never got in touch
because I was too embarrassed.
I screwed
everything up.
I have no job,
no place to live.
I lost the love of my life.
I know I have no right
to ask this,
but do you think Marshall
would take me back?
In a heartbeat.
If you called
him up, yeah,
he'd take you back
with open arms.
Wow. So maybe I should call him.
Maybe.
No! This is... Ow!
Hold on.
Look, if you're going
to go back to him,
I don't want to hear
the word "maybe."
"Maybe" cannot be
in your vocabulary.
This breakup
almost killed him.
And he cannot go through
it again.
So, unless
you're absolutely certain,
stay the hell away from him.
This guy likes pennies.
Hi, Marshall.
No, go away. I don't
want to talk to you.
Okay, I know what I did
a couple nights back
is in a moral
gray area.
But the great news is,
she loved you.
If things had
gone your way--
you'd gone out
a couple times,
I think she definitely would
have had sex with you.
There's no "would"
in sex.
(both chuckle)
You're right, I totally...
I'm just no good
at this, Barney.
I'm good at being
in a couple,
Lily's boyfriend.
Being single-- forget it.
Come on, you can't
give up now.
What if I told you that
you could relive that night
with the exact same
conversations,
the exact same jokes
only this time, you
get her and I don't.
That's not possible.
Oh, but it is.
She has... wait for it...
(voice rising):
...here it comes...
(high-pitched):
...almost there...
an identical twin.
Yes!
A twin isn't
the same person.
Of course it is. What do
you think identical means?
"Ident"-- same,
"ical"-- person.
Same person.
Hey, we could
double date.
Fine.
But you have to promise me,
you're not going to steal
my new twin, and leave me
with your old, used-up twin.
Used up?
They're a human
being, Marshall.
So Uncle Marshall
and Uncle Barney
went out on a double date
with the twins.
How you doing?
Great.
Amazing.
This is so much fun.
And I think me and the
girl are really clicking.
You are,
you definitely are.
Listen, you're going
to have to leave now.
I just talked
with the twins, and get this,
I'm going home
with both of them.
Yeah. That's happening.
It is impossible
that you're doing
this to me again.
But they're twins.
You-- you said to me
that being single
would be like being
in a candy store.
Well, it's not, it's not
like a candy store.
It's a lawless,
postapocalyptic wasteland.
I may be your
best friend...
Actually Ted's my best friend.
But in this world, it's
every hombre for himself.
That's what being single is.
And after nine years
in captivity,
that is the single greatest
lesson I can teach you
about surviving in the wild.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I have two unique breasts
and two duplicates
waiting for me.
(chuckles)
Oh, bad news-- Marshall got
food poisoning.
What?
Oh, no.
That's too bad.
I really liked him.
Yeah. well, I guess
we're just a threesome tonight.
Lily, what are you doing here?
Oh, oh, I was just
walking by. I wasn't...
Oh, you mean New York?
My program ended.
It was just great.
Just lots of fun...
It was awful.
It was the worst mistake
I ever made.
I'm so sorry, Marshall,
and... hello.
Lily, this was the
worst summer of my life.
I know. It was the worst
summer of my life.
It was the hardest
thing that I've ever
had to go through.
Can we please get back together?
All that crap you
said to me about,
"we need to figure out
who we are outside of us,
and we need to learn
to do things on our own,"
it broke my heart.
Three months ago,
you broke my heart.
Can we please
get back together?
Lily, you were right.
All that crap was right.
So, no.
No, we can't
get back together.
We shouldn't.
At least, not right now.
Wow.
Okay. Yeah.
Well...
Will we still see each other?
Yeah, yeah.
I think so.
I don't know.
This is all really
new to me.
I just got out of
a long relationship.
I like your hair.
Thanks.
I figured new city,
a different color...
* ...Wide open road *
* It was love to us *
And the pizza there,
worst pizza ever.
I'm so glad to be
back in New York.
Listen, if there's
anything I can do
to even begin to make
things up to you...
Actually there may be something
that you can do for me,
but you can never
ever ask me why.
So then I was promoted
to assistant m\nage-er...
Manager--
why do I keep doing that?
Lily?
You gave me chlamydia,
you jerk.
So where was I?
Ah, yes, assistant m\nage-er...
I did it again.
I can't believe it.
You gave my twin sister
chlamydia.
You slime!
Wha... wait, I know magic.
Well, played, Eriksen.
Well played.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net